<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BackstoryTranslations>
	<ColonySettler43>
		<title>Koloninybyggare</title>
		<titleShort>Nybyggare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en nybyggare på en kolonivärld.

Ett sådant liv kräver en generalist av grundläggande praktiska uppgifter.</desc>
	</ColonySettler43>
	<MedievalFarmOaf58>
		<title>Medeltida gårdsdräng</title>
		<titleShort>Dräng</titleShort>
		<desc>Markberedning, hackning , styra oxkärror, köra skottkärror, gräva diken, plantera frön och förutsäga skörden.

Medeltida jordbrukare inte utbildade i vanlig bemärkelse, men de vet en hel del om att odla växter utan teknik. Som sagt, ett sådant liv lämnar en väsentligt oförmögen att delta i intellektuella och teknikintensiva verksamheter.</desc>
	</MedievalFarmOaf58>
	<MedievalLord20>
		<title>Medeltida lord</title>
		<titleShort>Ädling</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en herre på en förindustriell planet. [PAWN_pronoun] gick till fester, hanterade underordnade, och har även lärt sig om fäktning.

[PAWN_possessive] mjuka händer behövde inte hålla ett arbetsverktyg under hela den tiden. [PAWN_pronoun] anser manuellt arbete att vara under [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</MedievalLord20>
	<UrbworldEntrepreneur55>
		<title>Urbvärld entreprenör</title>
		<titleShort>Entreprenör</titleShort>
		<desc>I urbvärlden lider dom flesta. Men någon måste ju driva företag.

[PAWN_nameDef] har kompetens för handeln, muta personer och teknisk analys. [PAWN_pronoun] är en sociointellektuell maskin.</desc>
	</UrbworldEntrepreneur55>
	<DeepSpaceMiner11>
		<title>Gruvarbetare i yttre rymden</title>
		<titleShort>Gruvarbetare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gjorde det svettiga och smutsiga arbetet att dra metall ur asteroider på en rigg i yttre rymden. [PAWN_pronoun] använde sina praktiska industriella kompetens dagligen - och var inte dåligt i en barslagsmål heller.</desc>
	</DeepSpaceMiner11>
	<NavyScientist96>
		<title>Vetenskaspman i flottan</title>
		<titleShort>Vetenskaspman</titleShort>
		<desc>Interstellar krigföring vinns av teknik, så kejserliga flottor är alltid på toppen av modern forskning. Ännu bättre, har de första tillgång till överlägsna artefakter eftersom de är dom som hitter dem i rymden.

[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade i ett av flottans labb.</desc>
	</NavyScientist96>
	<MilitaryCommissar49>
		<title>Militär kommissarie</title>
		<titleShort>Kommissarie</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en intern spionchef i en kejserliga armén bataljon. [PAWN_pronoun] såg till att män var lojala, och inte retirera utom när det var beordrade till detta. Detta gjorde [PAWN_objective] impopulär, men [PAWN_pronoun] fick stor skicklighet på att upptäcka minsta oärlighet.</desc>
	</MilitaryCommissar49>
	<SpacePirate69>
		<title>Rymdpirat</title>
		<titleShort>Pirat</titleShort>
		<desc>Piratdåd upkommer överallt där regeringarna är svaga och samhälle sprids tunnt. [PAWN_nameDef] var en del av denna urgamla del av människans existens, utpressning och krossa fredliga handels fartyg för vinst.</desc>
	</SpacePirate69>
	<PitBrawler20>
		<title>Slagskämpe</title>
		<titleShort>Slagskämpe</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var nio år gammal när [PAWN_pronoun] hamnade i sin första fight. [PAWN_pronoun] vann, men viktigare var att HES publikt njöt av det. Slagskämpe visade sig vara en lukrativ kariär för dom som kunde överleva det, och det var oftast legalt.</desc>
	</PitBrawler20>
	<IllegalShipwright28>
		<title>Illegal skeppsbyggare</title>
		<titleShort>Skeppsbyggare</titleShort>
		<desc>Det finns en lag som säger att du inte är tillåtet att sätta terawatt-räckvidds-graser på en lastpråm. Speciellt om du döljer dem under vad som ser ut som en kommunikations parabol för bättre bakhåll potential. [PAWN_nameDef] upptäckte att det finns en stor vinst att göra, dock bara från dem som är ointresserade av dessa lagar.</desc>
	</IllegalShipwright28>
	<Courtesean56>
		<title>Kurtisan</title>
		<titleShort>Kurtisan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] blev använd för sin kropp av hundratals kunder i bordeller på flera planeter. [PAWN_pronoun] fick några psykiska märken och en speciell typ av kunskap.</desc>
	</Courtesean56>
	<SpaceMarine10>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en krigare i en Imperial flottan. [PAWN_possessive] uppgift var att slå in i fiendens rymdskepp, skjuta ned besättningen, och fånga skeppet intakt. Och [PAWN_pronoun] var bra på det.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine10>
	<Assassin35>
		<title>Lönnmördare</title>
		<titleShort>Lönnmördare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en professionell lönnmördare. [PAWN_pronoun] var kall, beräknande, och gjorde en bra vinst. I den branschen där en fullkomlig brist på empati var en tillgång.</desc>
	</Assassin35>
	<MedievalSlave75>
		<title>Medeltida slav</title>
		<titleShort>Slav</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp dra vagnar och gräva hål på en medeltida värld. Enkel manuell arbetskraft är [PAWN_possessive] äldsta följeslagare - tillsammans med herrens piskrapp.

[PAWN_pronoun] inte lära sig läsa förrän vid nio års ålder.</desc>
	</MedievalSlave75>
	<MedievalLordling62>
		<title>Medeltida lägre lord</title>
		<titleShort>Lägre lord</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en lägre lord i ett gammal rike på en medeltida värld. [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp i en herrgård av sten och betjänas av bugande människor av underklassen.
		
Ett sådant liv lär inga tekniska kunskaper och inger en livslång aversion mot kroppsarbete - men [PAWN_nameDef] lärde sig tidigt social manipulation.</desc>
	</MedievalLordling62>
	<UrbworldUrchin46>
		<title>Urbvärldsgatubarn</title>
		<titleShort>Gatubarn</titleShort>
		<desc>Urbvärlden - gamla och djupa industri skyskrapor som sprudlar av mänskligheten och gift. [PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i de mörka, oönskade delarna av en sådan plats. [PAWN_pronoun] fick kämpa för varje bit av mat.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin46>
	<VatgrownSoldier83>
		<title>Genodlad soldat</title>
		<titleShort>Genodlad</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gjordes inte som en person, utan mer som ett instrument för förstörelse. Odlas i ett biovapenanläggning och lärdes strid under [PAWN_possessive] accelererad tillväxt, har [PAWN_nameDef] fortfarande en benägenhet för strid av alla slag och en aversion mot mänsklig kontakt.</desc>
	</VatgrownSoldier83>
	<Hermit87>
		<title>Eremit</title>
		<titleShort>Eremit</titleShort>
		<desc>Slitan av trycket från social interaktion, [PAWN_nameDef] lämnade sina trånga MidVärld-stad att leva ett enkelt liv i vildmarken. Där tillbringade [PAWN_pronoun] sina dagar ensam, tar hand om sin trädgård och tillverkar av de enkla verktyg [PAWN_pronoun] behövde för att överleva.</desc>
	</Hermit87>
	<MidworldChef39>
		<title>MidVärld kock</title>
		<titleShort>Kock</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] drev en högklassig MidVärld restaurang. [PAWN_pronoun] var känd bland besökarna för [PAWN_possessive] kreativa kulinariska specialiteter, och ökänd bland köksarbetare för [PAWN_possessive] avslappnade förakt för grovjobb.</desc>
	</MidworldChef39>
	<SicklyChild40>
		<title>Sjukligt barn</title>
		<titleShort>Patient</titleShort>
		<desc>Som barn, [PAWN_nameDef] led av en sällsynt sjukdom. I karantän i ett forskningssjukhus hade [PAWN_pronoun] minimal mänsklig kontakt och fick lite motion. I den sterila sjukhusmiljö men blev [PAWN_pronoun] dock väl förtrogen med vetenskap och medicin.</desc>
	</SicklyChild40>
	<MedievalMinstrel69>
		<title>Medeltida trubadur</title>
		<titleShort>Trubadur</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en resande underhållare på en medeltida värld.

[PAWN_pronoun] kan alltid hittas berättar historier eller sjunga sånger, och är i stånd att skydda sig från farorna av vägen. Men var [PAWN_pronoun] alltid påfallande frånvarande när det var hårt arbete som behövde göras.</desc>
	</MedievalMinstrel69>
	<Housemate5>
		<title>Hemarbetare</title>
		<titleShort>Hemarbetare</titleShort>
		<desc>Som vuxen, [PAWN_nameDef] höll huset rent och vårdade barn medan [PAWN_possessive] partner arbetade.</desc>
	</Housemate5>
	<GlitterworldEmpath39>
		<title>Glittervärldsempat</title>
		<titleShort>Empat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] hade en fantastisk förmåga att relatera till andra och medla konflikter. [PAWN_pronoun] valdes att träna som en empath. Utbildningen intensifierade [PAWN_possessive] naturliga förmågor, men [PAWN_pronoun] blev oförmögen att skada andra.</desc>
	</GlitterworldEmpath39>
	<ShelterChild65>
		<title>Härbärgebarn</title>
		<titleShort>Härbärgebarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i ett skyddsrum djupt under en giftig värld. [PAWN_pronoun] fick en omfattande utbildning, men hade ingen möjlighet att göra fysiskt arbete.</desc>
	</ShelterChild65>
	<MedievalDoctor6>
		<title>Medeltida doktor</title>
		<titleShort>Kvacksalvare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som läkare på en medeltida planet. [PAWN_pronoun] är övertygad om att de flesta sjukdomar kan botas med lite åderlåtning.

[PAWN_pronoun] var också en mästarnarkosläkare, utvecklade av en specialitet teknik som involverade ett hårt slag mot huvudet.</desc>
	</MedievalDoctor6>
	<Inventor42>
		<title>Uppfinnare</title>
		<titleShort>Uppfinnare</titleShort>
		<desc>På sina hemvärld, [PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som en måttligt framgångsrik uppfinnare. [PAWN_pronoun] utvecklade flera mindre tekniker.</desc>
	</Inventor42>
	<Teacher24>
		<title>Lärare</title>
		<titleShort>Lärare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] utbildades inom humaniora och undervisade vid en kommunal skola. [PAWN_pronoun] var allmänt kunnig och omtyckt av sina elever.</desc>
	</Teacher24>
	<IndustrialOrphan55>
		<title>industriell föräldralös</title>
		<titleShort>Föräldralös</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] kände aldrig sina föräldrar. [PAWN_possessive] tidigaste minnen var av slit i gruvorna och arbetshusen sin industriella världen.

På grund av detta, fick [PAWN_pronoun] aldrig en ordentlig utbildning.</desc>
	</IndustrialOrphan55>
	<Scout67>
		<title>Scout</title>
		<titleShort>Scout</titleShort>
		<desc>Född to koloniala administratörer från en liten imperialistisk makt, blev [PAWN_nameDef] inskrivna i ett ungdomsprogram som lärde militära scoutfärdigheter.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärt sig att överleva i vildmarken, att lyda och inte ställa frågor.</desc>
	</Scout67>
	<JoywireArtist62>
		<title>Gläjetrådsartist</title>
		<titleShort>Glädjetrådare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade i en urbvärldslabb och utvecklade banbrytande programvara till glädjetråd för att maximera användarnöje.

När den lokala regeringen införde hårda restriktioner för gläjetråd-tillverkning, började [PAWN_pronoun] sälja sina produkter på den svarta marknaden.</desc>
	</JoywireArtist62>
	<FrightenedChild6>
		<title>Skrämt barn</title>
		<titleShort>Rädd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp med en lista av fobier och neuroser. [PAWN_pronoun] fruktade, bland annat läkare och livsmedelsburna patogener.

Som ett resultat, lärde [PAWN_pronoun] sig att laga mat och ta hand om sig själv, men många av [PAWN_possessive] rädsla jagar [PAWN_objective] i vuxen ålder.</desc>
	</FrightenedChild6>
	<ConceptualArtist7>
		<title>Konceptuell konstnär</title>
		<titleShort>Konstnär</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var välkänd i konst cirklar på [PAWN_possessive] hemvärld för sin unika och kreativa konceptuella konstverk.

Ingen var säker på exakt vad [PAWN_pronoun] försökte kommunicera, men [PAWN_possessive] pjäser var mycket uppskattad av samlare.</desc>
	</ConceptualArtist7>
	<GlitterworldSurgeon7>
		<title>Glittervärldskirurg</title>
		<titleShort>kirurg</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som kirurg på en värld mestadels fri från sjukdom och mänskligt lidande.

[PAWN_possessive] arbetade främst med genomarbetade och kreativa kosmetiska operationer. [PAWN_pronoun] har en god förståelse för människans biologi, men aldrig behövt att ta bort en cancer - eller en kula.</desc>
	</GlitterworldSurgeon7>
	<LudditeRebel42>
		<title>Ludditrebel</title>
		<titleShort>Luddit</titleShort>
		<desc>När de flesta människor på [PAWN_possessive] värld valde att ge upp sin individualitet och biologiska mänskligheten att gå samman i en online kollektivt medvetande så anslöt sig [PAWN_nameDef] till en rebellisk fraktion som valde att överge de mesta av tekniken.</desc>
	</LudditeRebel42>
	<Bartender47>
		<title>Bartender</title>
		<titleShort>Bartender</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som bartender på en förslappad rymdstation. Jobbet innebar en del drinkblandande, en del diplomati, och en del skallande.</desc>
	</Bartender47>
	<CaveworldTender5>
		<title>Grottvärldsodlare</title>
		<titleShort>Grottbarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i ett grottkomplex djupt under ytan av en ogästvänlig värld. [PAWN_pronoun] arbetat med de andra barnen med att odla stammens svampgrödor.</desc>
	</CaveworldTender5>
	<CaveworldTunneler74>
		<title>Grottvärldsgrävare</title>
		<titleShort>Grävare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som en grävare i ett massivt underjordiskt grottkomplex.

[PAWN_pronoun] känner till sten så bra att [PAWN_pronoun] nästan kan navigera grottor med lukt.</desc>
	</CaveworldTunneler74>
	<HiveworldDrone29>
		<title>Kollektivt-medvetandevärldsdrönare</title>
		<titleShort>Drönare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som en själlös konstruktionsdrönare i en massiv kollektivt-medvetande civilisation. Även om [PAWN_pronoun] nu är fri från de brutala sociala experiment som [PAWN_pronoun] hade utsatts för, är [PAWN_pronoun] oförmögen till kreativt tänkande och ledarskap.</desc>
	</HiveworldDrone29>
	<Evangelist66>
		<title>Evangelist</title>
		<titleShort>Evangelist</titleShort>
		<desc>På sin 21-årsdag, upplevde [PAWN_nameDef] ett religiöst uppvaknande. [PAWN_pronoun] beslutade att tillbringa resten av sitt liv sprida ordet av [PAWN_possessive] gudom, skönheten i sin kultur, och dess ovanliga medicinsk tradition.</desc>
	</Evangelist66>
	<TunnelworldIlluminator50>
		<title>Tunnelväldsupplysare</title>
		<titleShort>Upplysare</titleShort>
		<desc>Bland tunnel invånare, de med vision lika stark som [PAWN_nameDef]'s ansens vara de upplysta. [PAWN_pronoun] skulle leda vägen, märka platser att gräva med självlysande svampar och varna om andra överhängande faror.</desc>
	</TunnelworldIlluminator50>
	<Herbalist89>
		<title>Herbalist</title>
		<titleShort>Herbalist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] levde i skogen nära en by. Även om många av byborna fruktade [PAWN_objective] kom sjuka bybor till [PAWN_objective] för att köpa salvor och kataplasmer gjorda av örter [PAWN_pronoun] växte i sin trädgård. [PAWN_pronoun] var glad att hjälpa dem - för ett pris.</desc>
	</Herbalist89>
	<ComaChild18>
		<title>Komabarn</title>
		<titleShort>Koma</titleShort>
		<desc>En barndom olycka satte [PAWN_nameDef] i koma. [PAWN_pronoun] vaknade inte förrän [PAWN_pronoun] var i sena tonåren. [PAWN_possessive] kropp aldrig återhämtat sig från år av inaktivitet, men människor tenderar att tycka synd om [PAWN_objective] när de hör [PAWN_possessive] berättelse.</desc>
	</ComaChild18>
	<CivilServant75>
		<title>Tjänsteman</title>
		<titleShort>Kontorist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som en lågt rankad administratör för en döende statliga byråkratin. [PAWN_pronoun] är mest hemma med att fylla ut komplicerade pappersarbete och spela kontorspolitik.</desc>
	</CivilServant75>
	<OrganFarm9>
		<title>Organfarm</title>
		<titleShort>Organfarm</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en olaglig underjordisk organfarm. [PAWN_possessive] kropp användes för att odla ekologiska implantat för sårade legosoldater. Även om [PAWN_possessive] uppväxt har lämnat [PAWN_objective] hemsökt, har det också gett [PAWN_objective] en unik förståelse för människlig biologi.</desc>
	</OrganFarm9>
	<AsceticPriest87>
		<title>Asketisk präst</title>
		<titleShort>Präst</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter att ha tagit ett löfte om tystnad, anslut [PAWN_nameDef] dig till ett kloster på en lugn bakvattenplanet för att tillbringa sina dagar i lugn kontemplation.

[PAWN_pronoun] fann lycka i att odla grönsaker i trädgården och göra ost i klostret källare.</desc>
	</AsceticPriest87>
	<EscapedConvict68>
		<title>Förrymd fånge</title>
		<titleShort>Rymmare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] förnekar inblandning i brott som orsakade om [PAWN_possessive] fängslande i en brutal straffkoloni. [PAWN_pronoun] flydde genom tunnel under ytterstängselt med hjälp av ett modifierat bestick.</desc>
	</EscapedConvict68>
	<StarshipJanitor15>
		<title>Rymdskeppsvaktmästare</title>
		<titleShort>Vaktmästare</titleShort>
		<desc>Medan andra passagerare passerar åren mellan stjärnsystem i kryptosömnkistor var [PAWN_nameDef] tvungen att vakna upp med jämna mellanrum för att utföra inspektioner, kontrollera navigationssystem och olja in mekanoiderna.</desc>
	</StarshipJanitor15>
	<Pyromaniac68>
		<title>Pyroman</title>
		<titleShort>Pyroman</titleShort>
		<desc>Från tidig ålder har [PAWN_nameDef] haft en ohälsosam fascination med eld. [PAWN_pronoun] skulle kunna sätta eld på sophögar och bli så hänförd av lågorna att [PAWN_pronoun] skulle kunna förstrött bränna sig själv.

En dag medan [PAWN_pronoun] lekte med tändstickor lyckades [PAWN_pronoun] brände ner sitt hem av misstag.</desc>
	</Pyromaniac68>
	<Mute55>
		<title>Stum</title>
		<titleShort>Stum</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] har påverkats kraftigt av en traumatisk händelse tidigt i livet. Under många år vägrade [PAWN_pronoun] att tala till människor, utan föredrar hellre att leka med sitt hushålls otaliga husdjur.</desc>
	</Mute55>
	<WarRefugee70>
		<title>Flykting</title>
		<titleShort>Flykting</titleShort>
		<desc>Kriget bröt ut i [PAWN_nameDef]'s hemland när [PAWN_pronoun] var barn. [PAWN_possessive] föräldrar flydde med [PAWN_objective] och sökte säkerhet varhelst de kunde hitta den. [PAWN_nameDef] tidigaste minnen är att [PAWN_pronoun] blir lärd att försvara sig.

Våldet och förstörelse [PAWN_pronoun] bevittnade lämnade [PAWN_objective] ärrade för livet.</desc>
	</WarRefugee70>
	<MusicLover26>
		<title>Musikälskare</title>
		<titleShort>Musiker</titleShort>
		<desc>Som barn hade [PAWN_nameDef] en talang för att spela musikinstrument och sjunga. [PAWN_pronoun] fick expertutbildning och älskade att uppträda i framträdanden och konserter, men de enorma berömmen [PAWN_pronoun] fick gjorde [PAWN_objective] aningen självupptagen.</desc>
	</MusicLover26>
	<ChildStar51>
		<title>Barnstjärna</title>
		<titleShort>Stjärna</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var väl känd i hela [PAWN_possessive] hemvärld som barnskådespelare i filmer och TV-program. [PAWN_possessive] fame satte [PAWN_objective] i kontakt med många olika typer av människor, men det tenderade också att komma i vägen för [PAWN_possessive] utbildning.</desc>
	</ChildStar51>
	<ChildSpy95>
		<title>Barnspion</title>
		<titleShort>Spion</titleShort>
		<desc>Barn är ofta oskyldig, och kan vara perfekt som spioner. [PAWN_nameDef] har utbildats i konsten att infiltration och informationsinsamling när [PAWN_pronoun] var bara nio år gammal.

[PAWN_possessive] år bakom fiendens linjer och krigshärjade naturen av [PAWN_possessive] hemvärld innebar att [PAWN_pronoun] hade begränsade möjligheter till utbildning.</desc>
	</ChildSpy95>
	<Shopkeeper18>
		<title>Butiksinnehavare</title>
		<titleShort>Butiksinnehavare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mor var ofta sjuk, och det föll på [PAWN_objective] att driva butiken som var deras enda inkomstkälla. [PAWN_pronoun] lärt sig lite om de exotiska artefakter som [PAWN_pronoun] sålde, och en hel del om konsten med affären.</desc>
	</Shopkeeper18>
	<Nurse0>
		<title>Sjuksköterska</title>
		<titleShort>Sjuksköterska</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade i ett industriell-era sjukhus med rutinarbete såsom att byta bandage och ta temperaturer.

Det var en hektisk jobb, men [PAWN_pronoun] kunde alltid hitta tid för en prata med en patient.</desc>
	</Nurse0>
	<HouseServant78>
		<title>Tjänare</title>
		<titleShort>Tjänare</titleShort>
		<desc>Tidigt i vuxen ålder blev [PAWN_nameDef] kidnappad och såld till rika aristokrater som tjänare.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärde känna kök och källare av sin herres herrgård väl, men gjorde aldrig något arbete utanför.</desc>
	</HouseServant78>
	<Bodyguard22>
		<title>Livvakt</title>
		<titleShort>Livvakt</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fick arbete på en MidWorld med att skydda den som betalade [PAWN_objective] från skada. [PAWN_pronoun] fick kunskaper i många olika stridsformer, och var känd för sin hänsynslöshet mot dem som korsade [PAWN_possessive] väg.</desc>
	</Bodyguard22>
	<Novelist96>
		<title>Författare</title>
		<titleShort>Författare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bodde på en glitterworld och skrev väldigt framgångsrika romaner. [PAWN_pronoun] levde en bekymmersfri livsstil, spendera sina dagar skriva och [PAWN_possessive] nätter festa ... och gjorde aldrig en dags manuellt arbete i sitt liv.</desc>
	</Novelist96>
	<Mathematician18>
		<title>Matematiker</title>
		<titleShort>Matematiker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] utförde matematisk forskning vid ett universitet.

[PAWN_pronoun] tillbringade mycket av sin lediga tid insjunken i skyttesimuleringar, men [PAWN_pronoun] var ofta förlöjligad av andra spelare för sin usla träffsäkerhet.</desc>
	</Mathematician18>
	<Paramedic85>
		<title>Sjukvårdare</title>
		<titleShort>Sjukvårdare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] uppgift var att snabbt reagera på medicinska akutfall. [PAWN_pronoun] är van vid att hantera svåra skador med endast begränsade medicinska förnödenheter.

[PAWN_pronoun] behandlade så många skottskador under åren att även se en pistol gjorde [PAWN_objective] obekväm.</desc>
	</Paramedic85>
	<Castaway74>
		<title>Skeppsbruten</title>
		<titleShort>Skeppsbruten</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var den enda överlevande i en skeppskrasch på ett obebodd djurvärld. För många år fram till sin räddning överlevde [PAWN_pronoun] på vad [PAWN_pronoun] kunde skrapa ihop.

[PAWN_possessive] överlevnadsfärdigheter blev knivskarpa, men att spendera så lång ensam dämpade det allvarligt [PAWN_possessive] kommunikativa förmågor.</desc>
	</Castaway74>
	<Gardener25>
		<title>Trädgårdsmästare</title>
		<titleShort>Trädgårdsmästare</titleShort>
		<desc>På industri världar koncentreras rikedom i händerna på dem som äger fabrikerna och säljer varorna. [PAWN_nameDef] arbetat på herrgården av en sådan rik familj och tog hand om en påkostad trädgårdard som en av ett team av anställda.</desc>
	</Gardener25>
	<MafiaBoss49>
		<title>Maffiaboss</title>
		<titleShort>Boss</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en högt uppsatt medlem av en urbvärlds brottssyndikat.

[PAWN_pronoun] mutade tjänstemän, underhöll lojalitet till sina underordnade och extraherade utgångna betalningar - med alla nödvändiga medel.</desc>
	</MafiaBoss49>
	<Torturer24>
		<title>Torterare</title>
		<titleShort>Torterare</titleShort>
		<desc>Tack vare att [PAWN_nameDef] arbetade för en tyrannisk monark på en medeltida värld fick [PAWN_pronoun] ett rykte som en expert på "övertalning". Fångar som gick ner i fängelsehålor lämndade aldrig med några hemligheter - och med [PAWN_nameDef]'s leende permanent ärrat i sina mardrömmar.</desc>
	</Torturer24>
	<ConstructionEngineer77>
		<title>Byggnadsingenjör</title>
		<titleShort>Byggare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en byggnadsarbetare på en MidWorld. [PAWN_pronoun] ledde ett team som byggde allt från kontorsfastigheter till katedraler.

[PAWN_possessive]'s  upptagna jobb och tillgång till närliggande snabbmatsbutiker innebar att [PAWN_pronoun] aldrig lagade mat själv.</desc>
	</ConstructionEngineer77>
	<Blacksmith19>
		<title>Smed</title>
		<titleShort>Smed</titleShort>
		<desc>Som en smed i en medeltida värld fick [PAWN_nameDef] ett rykte för den höga kvaliteten på [PAWN_possessive] arbete. [PAWN_pronoun] var inte dåligt på att använda svärden [PAWN_pronoun] tillverkade heller.</desc>
	</Blacksmith19>
	<CharityWorker80>
		<title>Välgörenhetsarbetare</title>
		<titleShort>Altruist</titleShort>
		<desc>Glittervärldar är tillflyktsorter för säkerhet och komfort för dem som har turen att bo där, men [PAWN_nameDef] kunde inte bortse från närliggande planeter där människor lider i fattigdom. [PAWN_pronoun] tillbringade sitt yrkesliv vädja för donationer och stödja de som behöver.</desc>
	</CharityWorker80>
	<Defector59>
		<title>Avhoppare</title>
		<titleShort>Avhoppare</titleShort>
		<desc>Tidigt i sin vuxen ålder beslutade [PAWN_nameDef] att lämna den förtryckta diktatur där [PAWN_pronoun] bodde. [PAWN_possessive] avhopp var inte väl mottaget, och agenter sändes ut efter [PAWN_objective].

[PAWN_pronoun] spenderat många år på flykt, behandla sina egna skador så ingen läkare kunde förråda [PAWN_objective]. Denna prövningen gjorde [PAWN_objective] bitter och fick [PAWN_objective] att tappa förtroendet på folk.</desc>
	</Defector59>
	<FactoryWorker82>
		<title>Fabriksarbetare</title>
		<titleShort>Arbetare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gjorde simpla, okvalificerat jobb i en industriell fabriksvärld. I [PAWN_possessive] jobb ingick också att ta hand om de mulåsnor och hästar som transporterade varor runt staden.</desc>
	</FactoryWorker82>
	<RanchOwner88>
		<title>Ranchägare</title>
		<titleShort>Ranchägare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ägde och drev en framgångsrik ranch där [PAWN_pronoun] födde upp djur för kött och ull.

[PAWN_pronoun] vägrade att göra något enkelt arbete [PAWN_pronoun] kunde betala någon annan att göra för [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</RanchOwner88>
	<LowWageWorker94>
		<title>Låglönearbetare</title>
		<titleShort>Daglönare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade med en mängd olika tillfälliga jobb för att försörja sin familj och fick en uppsättning grundläggande praktiska färdigheter.</desc>
	</LowWageWorker94>
	<Model51>
		<title>Modell</title>
		<titleShort>Modell</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som modell av kläder och smycken för annonsörer, och användes också som en modell för karaktärer i simuleringar av virtuella verkligheter.</desc>
	</Model51>
	<Taxonomist49>
		<title>Taxonomist</title>
		<titleShort>Taxonomist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] reste mellan stjärnsystem för att studera och klassificera växt- och djurliv [PAWN_pronoun] fann i hopp om att skapa en komplett katalog.</desc>
	</Taxonomist49>
	<Geologist2>
		<title>Geolog</title>
		<titleShort>Geolog</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetat med gruvarbetare och grotta-grävare med att identifiera bergarter och naturliga formationer.

Under sina år under jord fick [PAWN_pronoun] också erfarenhet reparera borrmaskiner och annan teknisk utrustning.</desc>
	</Geologist2>
	<ConventChild41>
		<title>Oönskat barn</title>
		<titleShort>Oönskad</titleShort>
		<desc>Barnet av en olaglig affär blev [PAWN_nameDef] uppfostrad upp av nunnor i ett medeltida kloster. [PAWN_pronoun] lärt sig värdet av hårt arbete och underkastelse och undervisades att all teknik är kätteri.</desc>
	</ConventChild41>
	<TestSubject75>
		<title>Testperson</title>
		<titleShort>Testare</titleShort>
		<desc>På de mest korrupta urbvärldar begår forskare utan en moralisk kompass obeskrivliga grymheter i forkningens [PAWN_nameDef] av forskning. [PAWN_nameDef] hölls ensam i ett förseglat anläggning från födseln och utsattes för en mängd olika beteende experiment i ett försök att göra [PAWN_objective] till en perfekt supersoldat .</desc>
	</TestSubject75>
	<MedicalAssistant75>
		<title>Läkarassistent</title>
		<titleShort>Läkare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes under ett katastrofalt krig där båda sidor använde napalm i stor utsträckning. [PAWN_pronoun] hjälpte sina föräldrar i en sjukstuga under sin uppväxt genom att behandla en kaskad av fruktansvärda brännskador från slagfälten. [PAWN_pronoun] lämnades med en livslång rädsla för brand.</desc>
	</MedicalAssistant75>
	<CultChild15>
		<title>Kultbarn</title>
		<titleShort>Kultbarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes i en kraftfull kult som skydde avancerad teknik och trodde att alla sjukdomar kan botas genom att rena själen genom religiös konst.

Efter sin första skymt av omvärlden bestämde [PAWN_pronoun] sig för att rymma.</desc>
	</CultChild15>
	<WreckageExplorer75>
		<title>Vrakutforskare</title>
		<titleShort>Upptäckare</titleShort>
		<desc>Två generationer innan [PAWN_nameDef] föddes orsakade ett apokalyptisk krig att [PAWN_possessive] hemplanet föll i anarki. [PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som stammens djurherde men drog sig ofta undan sina uppgifter för att istället gå på upptäcktsfärd bland kraschade krigsfartyg utspridda runt planeten.</desc>
	</WreckageExplorer75>
	<ApocalypseSurvivor86>
		<title>Apokalypsöverlevare</title>
		<titleShort>Överlevare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes under en tid av oro på [PAWN_possessive] hemvärld, eftersom klimatförändringarna hotade massvält och översvämningar. När [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp förvärrades situationen. Miljarder dog och fredliga stater föll i anarki. [PAWN_nameDef] och [PAWN_possessive] föräldrar gjorde vad de var tvungna för att överleva.</desc>
	</ApocalypseSurvivor86>
	<StoryWriter68>
		<title>Författare</title>
		<titleShort>Författare</titleShort>
		<desc>Som barn var [PAWN_nameDef] beroende av läsning. [PAWN_pronoun] kunde tillbringa hela dagen i sin lokala bibliotek med näsan i en bok. När budgetnedskärningar tvingade biblioteket för att stänga blev [PAWN_nameDef] upprörd. [PAWN_pronoun] bestämde sig för att fylla gapet genom att skriva sina egna historier i stället.</desc>
	</StoryWriter68>
	<Sailor53>
		<title>Sjöman</title>
		<titleShort>Sjöman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] korsade haven på upptäcktsresor sökandes efter växt- och djurprover från exotiska platser, och ibland avvärja pirater. [PAWN_pronoun] älskade havet så mycket [PAWN_pronoun] vägrade att göra allt men ett absolut minimum av arbete på land, förutom att sälja de skatter [PAWN_pronoun] samlat.</desc>
	</Sailor53>
	<Jailbird93>
		<title>Kåkfarare</title>
		<titleShort>Kåkfarare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tillbringade större delen av sitt liv i fängelse, där [PAWN_pronoun] sattes att arbeta i köket. [PAWN_pronoun] hade en vana att komma in i slagsmål och har därmed utvecklat ett aggressivt sätt att tala.</desc>
	</Jailbird93>
	<Actor76>
		<title>Skådespelare</title>
		<titleShort>Skådespelare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] reste runt i sin hemvärld med ett företag av aktörer och spelade upp pjäser för packade teatrar och kärleksfull publik överallt. [PAWN_pronoun] var en perfektionist, och gjorde själv sin egen rekvisita och kostymer istället för att använda de [PAWN_pronoun] fick.</desc>
	</Actor76>
	<Tactician22>
		<title>Taktiker</title>
		<titleShort>Taktiker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] anslöt sig till rymdflottan i ett instabilt system, fyllt med stora interplanetariska krig. [PAWN_pronoun] visade sig ha en skarp hjärna för strid, och blev skickliga på att befalla stora arméer med stor framgång.</desc>
	</Tactician22>
	<GlitterworldOfficer93>
		<title>Glitterworld officer</title>
		<titleShort>Officer</titleShort>
		<desc>Även om glittervärldar är fredliga platser är de alltid beredda på krig. [PAWN_nameDef]'s enhet såg sällan någon riktig action.

Även om [PAWN_pronoun] hade sin konstnärliga hobbies föredrog [PAWN_possessive] underlydande att roa sig genom att bråka så [PAWN_nameDef] blev bra på att bryta upp slagsmål.</desc>
	</GlitterworldOfficer93>
	<Taster35>
		<title>Provsmakare</title>
		<titleShort>Provsmakare</titleShort>
		<desc>Som en provsmakare för en medeltida kung måste [PAWN_nameDef] först prova varje maträtt som serverades vid det kungliga bordet. [PAWN_pronoun] levde en dekadent livsstil vid hovet genom att bli fet och göra väldigt lite arbete.</desc>
	</Taster35>
	<BiosphereManager30>
		<title>Biosfäransvarig</title>
		<titleShort>Botaniker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bodde på en lugn glittervärld där alla enkla arbeten gjordes av robotar och människor ägnade sig åt fritidsaktiviteter. [PAWN_pronoun] hanterade växt- och djurlivet i ett sprudlande park, dit medborgare kom för att beundra den naturliga skönheten.</desc>
	</BiosphereManager30>
	<Veterinarian19>
		<title>Veterinär</title>
		<titleShort>Veterinär</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade med att behandlade sjuka och skadade djur. Att se deras lidande påverkat [PAWN_possessive] inställning till bruket av att äta kött, och under många år levde [PAWN_pronoun] som en vegetarian, och undvek den köttälskande mattraditionen på [PAWN_possessive] hemvärld.</desc>
	</Veterinarian19>
	<ExplosivesExpert30>
		<title>Sprängämnesexpert</title>
		<titleShort>Sprängare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en sprängämnes-ingenjör anställd i gruvor. [PAWN_pronoun] tog sitt jobb på största allvar och var väl insatt i de tekniska - så mycket att [PAWN_pronoun] vägrade att förnedra sig genom att hjälpa till med saneringen när [PAWN_possessive] omsorgsfullt beräknad explosionen var fullständig.</desc>
	</ExplosivesExpert30>
	<Counselor20>
		<title>Rådgivare</title>
		<titleShort>Rådgivare</titleShort>
		<desc>En fruktansvört trauma i [PAWN_nameDef]'s ungdom fick [PAWN_objective] att utveckla en allvarlig ätstörning. Med rådgivning [PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig att få en friskare relation med mat, och bestämde sig för att använda sina nya kunskaper för att hjälpa andra att övervinna sina känslomässiga problem.</desc>
	</Counselor20>
	<Recruiter51>
		<title>Rekryterare</title>
		<titleShort>Rekryterare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en del av en erkänd grupp kampsportare, ökända både för sin skicklighet i strid och för sin praxis att vägra att behandla sina skadade.

[PAWN_pronoun] reste runt i sin hemvärld för att bedöma om de unga människor [PAWN_pronoun] mötte kunde vara lämpliga för utbildning.</desc>
	</Recruiter51>
	<PsychiatricPatient28>
		<title>Psykiatrisk patient</title>
		<titleShort>Patient</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tillbringade större delen av sitt vuxna liv i ett dårhus. [PAWN_possessive] industriella hemvärld hade en dålig förståelse för psykisk sjukdom så [PAWN_pronoun] behandlades mer som ett djur än en människa.

Även om [PAWN_pronoun] så småningom återhämtat sig och släpptes dämpade [PAWN_possessive] erfarenhet många av [PAWN_possessive] grundläggande livskunskaper.</desc>
	</PsychiatricPatient28>
	<Drifter25>
		<title>Luffare</title>
		<titleShort>Luffare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] listade aldrig ut vad [PAWN_pronoun] skulle göra med sitt liv. [PAWN_pronoun] reste ofta och tog tillfälligt arbete varhelst [PAWN_pronoun] fann det.

[PAWN_pronoun] skrev också ibland på en roman som [PAWN_pronoun] visste skulle bli en storsäljare, bara så fort [PAWN_pronoun] kunde hitta en förläggare som var intresserade.</desc>
	</Drifter25>
	<VRDesigner15>
		<title>VR designer</title>
		<titleShort>Spelutvecklare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] utformade virtuell verklighet simuleringar till glittervärlds-medborgare. [PAWN_pronoun] ägnade stor uppmärksamhet på detaljer i [PAWN_possessive] världar, inklusive lära sig allt [PAWN_pronoun] kunde om floran att göra sina landskap mer realistisk.</desc>
	</VRDesigner15>
	<HumanComputer63>
		<title>Mänsklig dator</title>
		<titleShort>Dator</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] visade sig ha ett utmärkt minne och en gåva för att utföra komplexa beräkningar i huvudet. En MidVälds diktator beslutat att anställa [PAWN_nameDef] att hålla reda på [PAWN_possessive] tillstånd ekonomi och utgifter, eftersom elektriska datorer var alltför känsliga för hacking.</desc>
	</HumanComputer63>
	<Architect11>
		<title>Arkitekt</title>
		<titleShort>Arkitekt</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] konstruerade och uppförda byggnader. De flesta av de tekniska aspekterna av arkitektur sköttes av en AI på [PAWN_possessive] glittevärldshem. Detta gjorde det möjligt för [PAWN_objective] att driva mot de konstnärliga gränserna, men innebar också att [PAWN_pronoun] aldrig var tvungen att få sina händer smutsiga på byggarbetsplatser.</desc>
	</Architect11>
	<MessageCarrier61>
		<title>Budbärare</title>
		<titleShort>Budbärare</titleShort>
		<desc>På en medeltida värld är det snabbaste sättet att skicka ett meddelande att ge det till någon på en häst och hoppas att [PAWN_pronoun] överlever resan. [PAWN_nameDef] var denna någon.</desc>
	</MessageCarrier61>
	<Sculptor16>
		<title>Skulptör</title>
		<titleShort>Skulptör</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] började med att skulptera personstora stenblock men började snart att tänka ännu större. Med hjälp av gruvrobotar lärde sig [PAWN_pronoun] hur man skar stora monument i klippsidor. Snart var naturparker i glitterväldar där [PAWN_pronoun] bodde var fulla av giganska bergsskupturer.</desc>
	</Sculptor16>
	<MachineCollector23>
		<title>Maskinsamlare</title>
		<titleShort>Samlare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var besatt av gamla maskiner och svårbegripliga bitar av teknik. [PAWN_pronoun] hämtade dom varhelst [PAWN_pronoun] kunde, och älskade att ta isär dem för att se hur de fungerade.

[PAWN_pronoun] hade en vana att tala om sin samling långt efter människor omkring [PAWN_objective] hade slutat lyssna.</desc>
	</MachineCollector23>
	<Sheriff37>
		<title>Sheriff</title>
		<titleShort>Sheriff</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var lagman i en isolerad industristad. [PAWN_pronoun] var känd för att ha en arrogant attityd och ett elakt drag. [PAWN_pronoun] vägrade att lyfta så mycket som ett finger såvide det inte rörde sig om pengar, alkohol, eller hämnd.</desc>
	</Sheriff37>
	<ConArtist96>
		<title>Bedragare</title>
		<titleShort>Bedragare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] aldrig skapade någonting i [PAWN_possessive] liv. [PAWN_pronoun] visa sig dock vara en naturbegåvning på att få andra att ge [PAWN_objective] vad de hade skapat.</desc>
	</ConArtist96>
	<Gatherer34>
		<title>Samlare</title>
		<titleShort>Samlare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] är en mästersamlare. [PAWN_pronoun] kan hitta mat i de mest karga av platser med hjälp av sina djupa kunskap om växter, rötter och bär.</desc>
	</Gatherer34>
	<Loner43>
		<title>Enstöring</title>
		<titleShort>Enstöring</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gillade aldrig stamrådet eller de årliga festivaler. [PAWN_pronoun] föredrar öppna slätten och den ensamma ljudet av vind bland klipporna.

[PAWN_pronoun] besöker sin stam från gång till gång, men för det mesta tar [PAWN_pronoun] hand om sig själv med hjälp av sina överlevnads färdigheter.</desc>
	</Loner43>
	<AbandonedChild27>
		<title>Övergivet barn</title>
		<titleShort>Övergiven</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes sjuk. Eftersom [PAWN_pronoun] bara skulle vara en börda för sin stam, lämnades [PAWN_pronoun] ut i obygden av sina föräldrar. På något sätt överlevde [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
	</AbandonedChild27>
	<ReclusiveChild87>
		<title>Tillbakadraget barn</title>
		<titleShort>Tillbakadraget</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] inte lära sig att tala förrän [PAWN_pronoun] var nästan fem år gammal, och även då föredrog [PAWN_pronoun] att hålla för sig själv. När [PAWN_pronoun] var i tidiga tonåren, gjorde [PAWN_pronoun] en vana av att vandra bort från byn att leva i vildmarken för veckor i taget.</desc>
	</ReclusiveChild87>
	<Herder89>
		<title>Herde</title>
		<titleShort>Herde</titleShort>
		<desc>Som barn hanterade [PAWN_nameDef] stammens muffel-hjordar genom att hålla dem säkra från rovdjur och behandla sjuka djur. Det var tyst arbete, men [PAWN_pronoun] gillade att få vara ifrån människor.</desc>
	</Herder89>
	<Scavenger86>
		<title>Sopletare</title>
		<titleShort>Sopletare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tillbringade sin barndom med att fly tråkiga jobbet att gå gräva igenom vrak och ruiner för skatter. [PAWN_possessive] naturliga nyfikenhet orsakade [PAWN_objective] en massa problem, men det gav också många intressanta fynd.</desc>
	</Scavenger86>
	<CaveChild31>
		<title>Grottbarn</title>
		<titleShort>Grottbarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en stor och invecklad grottkomplex som sträckte sig djupt in i en bergssida. [PAWN_pronoun] hjälpte vuxna upprätthålla och förbättra de djupa grottor.</desc>
	</CaveChild31>
	<SoleSurvivor85>
		<title>Ensam överlevare</title>
		<titleShort>Överlevande</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s hela stam utplånades i en raid. Trots att [PAWN_pronoun] antogs av en annan grupp blev [PAWN_pronoun] känslomässigt ärrad och föredrog att stanna nära hemmet med matlagning och sköta grödor.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor85>
	<VengefulChild49>
		<title>Hämndlystet barn</title>
		<titleShort>Hämndlystet barn</titleShort>
		<desc>Som barn [PAWN_nameDef] återvände till sin by för att finna att den hade utplånats av banditer. [PAWN_pronoun] svor hämnd på angriparna och började en våldsam framfart över öknen.</desc>
	</VengefulChild49>
	<FireKeeper85>
		<title>Brandskötare</title>
		<titleShort>Brand</titleShort>
		<desc>I sin barndom var [PAWN_nameDef] ansvarig för att hålla stammens eld igång. [PAWN_pronoun] tog detta ansvar på största allvar.</desc>
	</FireKeeper85>
	<Healer89>
		<title>Helare</title>
		<titleShort>Helare</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter [PAWN_possessive] stams helare dödades i en räd tog [PAWN_nameDef] rollen. [PAWN_pronoun] tillbringade sina dagar letandes efter örter och mineralföreningar från närområdet för att använda i förvånansvärt effektiva botemedel.</desc>
	</Healer89>
	<Scout93>
		<title>Scout</title>
		<titleShort>Scout</titleShort>
		<desc>Eftersom [PAWN_possessive] stam hade tagit kontakt med lokala utlänningar hade [PAWN_nameDef] en kontrakterad tjänster som en guide till det lokala området. Täta kontakter med fornminnen har gjort [PAWN_objective] ganska bekväm med gammal teknik.</desc>
	</Scout93>
	<Digger58>
		<title>Grävare</title>
		<titleShort>Grävare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] och [PAWN_possessive] stam grävde sitt hem djupt ner i sidan av ett berg. [PAWN_nameDef] känner sig mest hemma hacka genom berg och stötta upp grottväggar.</desc>
	</Digger58>
	<MuffaloShaman94>
		<title>Muffelschaman</title>
		<titleShort>Schaman</titleShort>
		<desc>På grund av [PAWN_possessive] lugna visdom och stora styrka blev [PAWN_nameDef] den andliga ledaren för en nomadisk stam som följde en frigående muffelhjord.</desc>
	</MuffaloShaman94>
	<LoreKeeper35>
		<title>Kunskapshållade</title>
		<titleShort>Berättare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en av en lång rad av kunskapshållade i sin stam. Varje kväll runt elden skulle [PAWN_pronoun] förmedla gamla kunskaper och hjälpsama visdommar genom berättelser.</desc>
	</LoreKeeper35>
	<Weaver90>
		<title>Vävare</title>
		<titleShort>Vävare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en expert på att väva muffelull, växtfibrer och naturliga färgämnen till vackra kläder för närstående. [PAWN_possessive] vackra hantverk byttes ofta mellan lokala stammar.</desc>
	</Weaver90>
	<CaveTender26>
		<title>Grottskötare</title>
		<titleShort>Skötare</titleShort>
		<desc>Medan de andra var ute och jagade och samlade, skulle [PAWN_nameDef] stanna hemma för att laga mat och ta hand om de unga och de sjuka.</desc>
	</CaveTender26>
	<Warrior37>
		<title>Krigare</title>
		<titleShort>Krigare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en fruktansvärd krigare, skicklig med många vapen. [PAWN_pronoun] deltog i många strider.</desc>
	</Warrior37>
	<TribeChild78>
		<title>Stambarn</title>
		<titleShort>Stambarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i stammen, sprang runt i byn, rörde sig med muffalhjorden och lärde sig grundläggande färdigheter från sina föräldrar.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig aldrig läsa och såg aldrig en maskin som inte bara var ett gammalt vrak.</desc>
	</TribeChild78>
	<FallenProdigy22>
		<title>Fallet underbarn</title>
		<titleShort>Underbarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes på en glitterworld som föll i kaos. [PAWN_possessive] pappa dödades i strid.

[PAWN_pronoun] kämpade för ett stipendium på Utmaior Academy och var konstant tvungen att bevisa sin rätt att få vara där. Ett barngeni, [PAWN_pronoun] blev mobbad som ett välgörenhetsfall och kunde inte skaffa sig vänner bland de andra barnen.</desc>
	</FallenProdigy22>
	<MadScientist28>
		<title>Galen vetenskapsman</title>
		<titleShort>Vetenskapsman</titleShort>
		<desc>Fråntaget sitt livs arbete och utflyttades efter [PAWN_possessive] oetiska experiment på de överlevande av Callos IX-incidenten publicerades, lärde NAMN de färdigheter som krävs för att överleva i ytterkanten.

Då [PAWN_pronoun] inte hade något mer att förlora förtsatte [PAWN_pronoun] sin forskning, och tillvekade undersåtar att utföra de uppgifter som uttråkade [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</MadScientist28>
	<FarmKid40>
		<title>Bondebarn</title>
		<titleShort>Bondebarn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp på sin familjens boskapsgård. [PAWN_pronoun] trivdes på fälten och tog hand om djuren.</desc>
	</FarmKid40>
	<CivilEngineer41>
		<title>Civilingenjör</title>
		<titleShort>Ingenjör</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en välkänd civilingenjör. [PAWN_possessive] arbetet involverade att utforma och upprätthålla stenbyggnadsstrukturer. [PAWN_pronoun] gjorde tillräckligt med statistisk analys för att hålla sitt sinne skarp.</desc>
	</CivilEngineer41>
	<FarmerBoy63>
		<title>Bonde</title>
		<titleShort>Bonde</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s föräldrar dog i en eld när [PAWN_pronoun] var sju. [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp på sin farbrors gård, plogade fält och gjorde manuellt arbete.

[PAWN_pronoun] orkade inte att svara på frågor om sina föräldrar, så [PAWN_pronoun] ersatte social kontakt med hårt arbete.</desc>
	</FarmerBoy63>
	<ArmyCook51>
		<title>Armekock</title>
		<titleShort>Kock</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gick med i armén som arbetare och tillbringade mestadels tid på matlagning och reparation. Medan [PAWN_pronoun] var stationerad på en farlig planet, genomgick [PAWN_pronoun] grundläggande skytte och överlevnadsträning.</desc>
	</ArmyCook51>
	<UrbworldCriminal64>
		<title>Urbvärld brottsling</title>
		<titleShort>Brottsling</titleShort>
		<desc>Född i dålig omständighet på en överbefolkad urbvärld vände sig [PAWN_nameDef] till småbrott som ett sätt att undvika svält och hypotermi.

Rån och mord var dagliga aktiviteter för [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig att den som överlevde vann.</desc>
	</UrbworldCriminal64>
	<UrbworldPolitican16>
		<title>Urbvärld politiker</title>
		<titleShort>Politiker</titleShort>
		<desc>Det är ingen hemlighet att företagen äger mycket av urbvärldarna, men någon måste ta mutor. [PAWN_nameDef] var en sådan person.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig att manipulera människornas förhoppningar och drömmar samtidigt som [PAWN_pronoun] bodde bekvämt i en takvåning.</desc>
	</UrbworldPolitican16>
	<OptimisticChild43>
		<title>Optimistiskt barn</title>
		<titleShort>Optimist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var välsignad med kärleksfulla föräldrar och ett trevligt midväldsliv. [PAWN_pronoun] var en optimistisk och sällskaplig unge som älskade att ha vänner och lyssna på deras berättelser. [PAWN_possessive] fantasi gick vilt med idéer och frågor.</desc>
	</OptimisticChild43>
	<GraphicDesigner99>
		<title>Grafisk designer</title>
		<titleShort>Designer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s intresse för konstnärligt uttryck ledde [PAWN_objective] till att bli designer. [PAWN_possessive] öga för detaljer gjorde [PAWN_objective] till en rimligt välkänd konstnär på sin planet, men [PAWN_possessive] noggrannhet ledde ofta till att [PAWN_pronoun] spenderade för mycket tid att fullända ett fåtal projekt.</desc>
	</GraphicDesigner99>
	<UrbworldHooligan8>
		<title>Urbvärldshuligan</title>
		<titleShort>Huligan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en farlig urbvärld. [PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig snabbt hur man får sin dagliga måltid - genom brott. Sådana medel lämnade lite eller inget utrymme för matlagning och odlande aktiviteter.</desc>
	</UrbworldHooligan8>
	<SpaceTechnician89>
		<title>Rymdtekniker</title>
		<titleShort>Tekniker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lyckades äntligen undfly sitt kriminella liv genom att få ett underhållsarbete på en närliggande rymdstation. [PAWN_pronoun] utförde flera reparations- och byggoperationer. [PAWN_pronoun] brukade också delta i grundläggande forskningsaktiviteter och desarmerade ofta med arbetskamraternas argument. [PAWN_pronoun] gillade aldrig att göra konst.</desc>
	</SpaceTechnician89>
	<IndworldUrchin11>
		<title>Indvärld gatunge</title>
		<titleShort>Gatunge</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp på gatorna i en värld i de tidiga stadierna av sin industriella revolution. [PAWN_pronoun] passerade [PAWN_possessive] dagar att stjäla, tigga och tinka med kasserade maskinskrot, alltid på utkik efter ett sätt att undkomma fattigdom.</desc>
	</IndworldUrchin11>
	<DoomsdayPariah26>
		<title>Domesdagsparia</title>
		<titleShort>Paria</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lyckades öppna en valv av utomvärldslig teknik när [PAWN_pronoun] grävde ut en grävplats. [PAWN_pronoun] utlöstes oavsiktligt en dommedagsanordning som rensade planeten ifrån allt livet. Eftersom [PAWN_pronoun] var mer intresserad av tekniken än människoliv, gick [PAWN_pronoun] ombord på valvets rymdfarkost och reste för att hitta mer reliker att missbruka.</desc>
	</DoomsdayPariah26>
	<MechanoidNerd80>
		<title>Mekaniod nörd</title>
		<titleShort>Mekanörd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en urbworld som det enda barnet i ett par mekanoiddesigners.
De uppmuntrade sitt intresse för maskinerna. Så småningom blev [PAWN_pronoun] besatt av att bygga sin egen.

Tyvärr leder det också till att [PAWN_pronoun] är en ensam eftersom [PAWN_pronoun] föredrog tekniska böcker framför vänner.</desc>
	</MechanoidNerd80>
	<MilitaryEngineer44>
		<title>Militär ingenjör</title>
		<titleShort>Ingenjör</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade som ingenjör för en kolonial militär. [PAWN_pronoun] fick leka med vapen, mord-drönare och andra "roliga" grejer.

[PAWN_pronoun] specialiserat på reparation och modifiering av mechanoids verktyg. Ibland testade [PAWN_pronoun] dem på själv.</desc>
	</MilitaryEngineer44>
	<ColiseumCleaner12>
		<title>Lokalvårdare</title>
		<titleShort>Städare</titleShort>
		<desc>Under det "Inre Destrianska Krigen" blev [PAWN_possessive] föräldrar fångade och [PAWN_pronoun] föddes i ett liv av slaveri. Tvungen att rengöra colosseum efter blodiga strider för pengar. Titta, vänta och lära. Colosseum var det enda [PAWN_pronoun] någonsin kände till. En natt när [PAWN_pronoun] rengjorde colosseumet blev [PAWN_possessive] familj mördad.</desc>
	</ColiseumCleaner12>
	<ColiseumFighter29>
		<title>Colosseum gladiator</title>
		<titleShort>Gladiator</titleShort>
		<desc>Genom att tillämpa kunskap som [PAWN_pronoun] fick från åren runt andra gladiatorer blev [PAWN_pronoun] en framgångsrik gladiator i det colosseum som [PAWN_pronoun] en gång städade.</desc>
	</ColiseumFighter29>
	<OfficerCadet81>
		<title>Kadettofficer</title>
		<titleShort>Kadett</titleShort>
		<desc>Från en ung ålder tränade [PAWN_nameDef] att vara en ledare för män. [PAWN_pronoun] skev in sig i Vanu Defense College när [PAWN_pronoun] var en yngling och blev skicklig med en rad vapen och överlevnadstekniker.</desc>
	</OfficerCadet81>
	<FighterController64>
		<title>Stridskontrollör</title>
		<titleShort>Kontrollör</titleShort>
		<desc>Under Zartha-krisen kämpade [PAWN_nameDef] över många världar, vilket gav den vitala kopplingen mellan marken och luften som en stridskontrollör. Under kampanjen såg [PAWN_pronoun] vänner bli både skadade och dödade. Detta mentala trauma jagar fortfarande [PAWN_possessive] drömmar till denna dag, men [PAWN_possessive] mål är fortsatt skarpt.</desc>
	</FighterController64>
	<ReclusiveProdigy98>
		<title>Tillbakadragen underbarn</title>
		<titleShort>Underbarn</titleShort>
		<desc>Att växa upp på en blomstrande glitterworld gav [PAWN_nameDef] chansen att fullt ut ägna sig åt sina studier.

Efter att ha haft ett stort intresse för genetisk modifiering och neural förstärkning från en ung ålder hade [PAWN_pronoun] liten tid (eller önskan) för en vanlig barndom.</desc>
	</ReclusiveProdigy98>
	<FerventResearcher44>
		<title>Ivrig forskare</title>
		<titleShort>Forskare</titleShort>
		<desc>Som en ung vuxen var [PAWN_nameDef] säker på att [PAWN_possessive] planet och dess folk närmade sig sin tid av transcendens.

En fast tro på att [PAWN_possessive] forskning skulle vara katalysatorn ledde [PAWN_objective] till alltmer alarmerande handlingar som byråkrater och bioetikkommittéer arbetade för att stoppa [PAWN_possessive] framsteg.</desc>
	</FerventResearcher44>
	<WarRefugee81>
		<title>Krigsflykting</title>
		<titleShort>Flykting</titleShort>
		<desc>Ett krig bröt ut på [PAWN_nameDef]'s hemplanet.

Efter att ha samlat vad lite mat och tillhörigheter de kunde, stal [PAWN_nameDef] och [PAWN_possessive] far ett skepp och flydde ut i rymden.</desc>
	</WarRefugee81>
	<VengefulExplorer48>
		<title>Hämdlysten utforskare</title>
		<titleShort>Utforskare</titleShort>
		<desc>Som en våldsam nomad utan fast hem, [PAWN_nameDef] och [PAWN_possessive] far slogs i många slag i hundratals år. [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp till en ärrad krigare och prickskytt.

Efter sin fars död i strid började [PAWN_nameDef] utforska stjärnorna ensam och söka sin fars mördare på jakten efter hämnd.</desc>
	</VengefulExplorer48>
	<WorkCampSlave37>
		<title>Abetskampslav</title>
		<titleShort>Slav</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp som en slav till en särskilt vidrig ädel familj i en medeltida värld.

Medan [PAWN_pronoun] inte fick någon formell utbildning, gjorde den hårda arbetsregimen [PAWN_possessive] kropp stark.</desc>
	</WorkCampSlave37>
	<BanishedSoldier4>
		<title>Förvisad soldat</title>
		<titleShort>Fredlös</titleShort>
		<desc>NAMN blev den mest fysiskt skrämmande av slavarna och spenderade sin lilla lediga tid på att obsessivt skulptera sin kropp. [PAWN_possessive] ansträngningar betalade sig slutligen när herren erbjöd [PAWN_objective] ett jobb som personlig livvakt.

Senare, när [PAWN_pronoun] planerade att använda sin position att döda herren och frigöra slavarna, upptäcktes [PAWN_pronoun] och lyckades fly knappt med sitt liv i behåll.</desc>
	</BanishedSoldier4>
	<DisciplinedFarmer44>
		<title>Disciplinerad bonde</title>
		<titleShort>Bonde</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var den yngre av två barn på familjens gård, en gränstomt som kämpade för att göra vinst. [PAWN_nameDef]'s fader var en sträng disciplinär, ständigt på sina barn för att arbeta hårdare och hålla tyst. [PAWN_nameDef] brände sin hand och gjorde frukost en gång och lovade att laga mat endast när [PAWN_possessive] liv var i fara.</desc>
	</DisciplinedFarmer44>
	<StalwartFarmer89>
		<title>Trogen bonde</title>
		<titleShort>Bonde</titleShort>
		<desc>Med gården under konstant hot från stråtrövare lärde sig [PAWN_nameDef] att försvara sig med sin fars jaktgevär. [PAWN_pronoun] behärskar också hur man konstruerar staket för att hålla boskapen och de lokala vilddjuren ute. [PAWN_nameDef] försökte måla en bild av sitt hem och lärde sig att [PAWN_pronoun] bara kan rita klotter och ankor.</desc>
	</StalwartFarmer89>
	<VoyagerChild9>
		<title>Resande barn</title>
		<titleShort>Resande</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp på ett forskningsskepp och tillbringade det mesta av sin barndom resande genom enorma tomrum.

Vid ett tilfälle när skeppet var allvarligt skadat närmade de sig en mystisk planetoid. [PAWN_possessive] nästa minne är av skeppet på väg ut ur omloppsbana, helt reparerad. [PAWN_pronoun] utvecklade strax efter det en onaturlig gåva för teknologisk forskning.</desc>
	</VoyagerChild9>
	<SpaceResearcher5>
		<title>Rymdforskare</title>
		<titleShort>Forskare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ärvde sina föräldrars skepp och fortsatte sin forskning.

[PAWN_possessive]-barndomsupplevelser med olika kulturer gjorde det möjligt för [PAWN_objective] att bevara sin omtänksamma natur trots att [PAWN_pronoun] tillbringade det mesta av sitt liv isolerat i rymden.</desc>
	</SpaceResearcher5>
	<VatgrownMedic86>
		<title>Militärläkare</title>
		<titleShort>Läkare</titleShort>
		<desc>Upfödd för att vara en militärläkare, [PAWN_nameDef] utbildades i skjutvapen och medicin. [PAWN_pronoun] favoritfras när [PAWN_pronoun] kom på en sårad soldat var "Liv eller död"? De flesta valde livet.</desc>
	</VatgrownMedic86>
	<GeneticScientist4>
		<title>Genetisk vetenskapsman</title>
		<titleShort>Genetskapsman</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter kriget gick [PAWN_pronoun] till ett genteknikföretag. [PAWN_pronoun] arbetade med förbättringar för människor och boskap. [PAWN_pronoun] erfarenheter av att påverka och läka sår var mycket fördelaktiga för [PAWN_possessive] arbete, men [PAWN_pronoun] utvecklade en svart humor. Detta gjorde sociala möten besvärliga.</desc>
	</GeneticScientist4>
	<CoreDilettante99>
		<title>Core dilettante</title>
		<titleShort>Dilettante</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tillbringade sina formativa år på en glitterworld i kärnregionen, där [PAWN_pronoun] och [PAWN_possessive] vänner följde livet av lätta nöjen.

När [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp, började [PAWN_pronoun] att finna det lättillgängliga livet tråkigt. [PAWN_pronoun] bestämde sig för att leta efter en mer utmanande väg.</desc>
	</CoreDilettante99>
	<Reporter51>
		<title>Reporter</title>
		<titleShort>Reporter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tillbringade många år som undersökande reporter. [PAWN_pronoun] var ökänd för att göra kaotiska rapporter från exotiska platser.

Trots att [PAWN_pronoun] ses som en lättviktare av [PAWN_possessive] kritiker lyckades [PAWN_pronoun] bryta flera högprofilerade reportage efter långa undersökningar.</desc>
	</Reporter51>
	<AspiringPopIdol61>
		<title>aspirerande popstjärna</title>
		<titleShort>Popstjärna</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] blev utbildad i sång och dans för att bli nästa stora popstjärna. [PAWN_pronoun] växte upp och blev omhändertagen av företagshanterare.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig aldrig om manuellt arbete, men lärde sig mycket om musik och social etikett.</desc>
	</AspiringPopIdol61>
	<PopIdol50>
		<title>Popstjärna</title>
		<titleShort>Popstjärna</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] uppträdde och gjorde intervjuer hela tiden. [PAWN_pronoun] förfinade sina färdigheter i dans och sång och blev en mästare i social presentation.</desc>
	</PopIdol50>
	<FarmBoy56>
		<title>Bondpojk</title>
		<titleShort>Bondpojk</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] arbetade på sin familjs gård, letade efter djuren och behandlade dem när de skadades. [PAWN_pronoun] Föredrog praktiska uppgifter och utomhus men undvek mjukare jobb som kan ha hållit honom inomhus.

[PAWN_pronoun] njöt av det ensamma arbetet och tenderade att hålla sig ur människors väg och göra sin egen sak.</desc>
	</FarmBoy56>
	<UnstableButcher98>
		<title>instabil slaktare</title>
		<titleShort>Slaktare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] började höra röster. Djuren pratade med [PAWN_objective] och förolämpade [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] kom för att hata dem och dödade så småningom sina ludna tidigare vänner. [PAWN_pronoun] började sälja köttet för att få mänsklig interaktion.</desc>
	</UnstableButcher98>
	<StationWhelp51>
		<title>Station whelp</title>
		<titleShort>Whelp</titleShort>
		<desc>NAMN tillbringade sin barndom som en pengalös föräldralös boende på en rymdstation. [PAWN_pronoun] lyckades skrapa genom att göra smutsiga jobb och stjäla. [PAWN_pronoun] blev så våldsam på grund av dålig behandling av hans "bättre" att [PAWN_pronoun] var förvisad från stationen, bara för att bli uppplockad av rymdpirater.</desc>
	</StationWhelp51>
	<PirateKing62>
		<title>Piratkung</title>
		<titleShort>Pirat</titleShort>
		<desc>Utan äkta omsorg för andra människor passade [PAWN_nameDef] perfekt in med piratbesättningen som [PAWN_pronoun] en gång varit en fångare av. Strax efter att ha blivit en i besättningen började [PAWN_nameDef] döda alla eller allt som kom i hans väg - inklusive hans kollegor.</desc>
	</PirateKing62>
	<ConstructionGrunt79>
		<title>Konstruktionsarbetare</title>
		<titleShort>Byggare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_pronoun] växte upp i faderns lab och fick en intellektuell elits liv. [PAWN_pronoun] fick allt [PAWN_pronoun] önskade, och priset var aldrig ett problem.

Men [PAWN_nameDef] deltog inte i den lyx som gavs [PAWN_objective]. I stället sökte [PAWN_pronoun] mer fysisk och - i sin fars ögon - lägre status arbeten.</desc>
	</ConstructionGrunt79>
	<MilitaryInventor44>
		<title>Militör uppfinnare</title>
		<titleShort>Uppfinnare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef], i en slutgiltig handling av uppror, lämnade sin fars laboratorium och gick med i den lokala kejserliga militären.

[PAWN_pronoun] använde sin laboratoriekompetens för att designa krigsmaskiner. Vid detta var [PAWN_pronoun] en av de bästa på sin planet.</desc>
	</MilitaryInventor44>
	<StudentEngineer40>
		<title>Ingejörsstudent</title>
		<titleShort>Ingenjör</titleShort>
		<desc>Som ett geni barn, [PAWN_nameDef] sattes i ett speciellt träningsprogram som täckte flygkrigsföring och ingengörskonst

En dag försökte [PAWN_pronoun] tämja en ekorre genom att ge det ett armband. Ekorren bet [PAWN_objective] och detta gav [PAWN_objective] smeknamnet "ekorrepojken".

NAMN kom att tro att arbetet med manuell arbetskraft är under [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</StudentEngineer40>
	<EngineeredPilot99>
		<title>Ingenjörspilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter att [PAWN_possessive] provins blev belägrat av en av sina grannar, anmälde sig [PAWN_nameDef] frivilligt för ett generiskt modifieringsprogram som skapade piloter för det stridsplanet som [PAWN_pronoun] hade hjälpt till att utveckla. Ändringarna gjorde det möjligt för [PAWN_objective] att styra planet, men gjorde [PAWN_objective] också mindre inriktad på människorna kring [PAWN_objective].

Vid den tiden kallade folk [PAWN_objective] "ekorren".</desc>
	</EngineeredPilot99>
	<StreetKid29>
		<title>Gatubarn</title>
		<titleShort>Gatubarn</titleShort>
		<desc>Under uppväxten på gatorna på en ökenplan var [PAWN_nameDef]'s vän en hund som heter Rufus. Paret samsades genom att hitta tillräckligt med mat för att överleva.

När [PAWN_pronoun] var 13 år tog en interplanetär brottssyndikat [PAWN_objective] under sin vinge.</desc>
	</StreetKid29>
	<BanditLeader92>
		<title>Banditledare</title>
		<titleShort>Bandit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] steg upp i brottsorganisationens ledning och blev så småningom ledare för en av sina mest avlägsna celler av banditer. [PAWN_possessive] hund Rufus lämnade aldrig [PAWN_possessive] sida.</desc>
	</BanditLeader92>
	<FrontierMarshal0>
		<title>Gränssheriff</title>
		<titleShort>Sheriff</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ärvde en pliktskänsla från sin far och började en brottsbekämpande karriär på sin hemvärld.

[PAWN_pronoun] försökte upprätthålla lagen med ära, men korruption och girighet av lokala tjänstemän avskräckte [PAWN_objective] ofta.</desc>
	</FrontierMarshal0>
	<ColonialGovernor77>
		<title>Koloniguvenör</title>
		<titleShort>Guvenör</titleShort>
		<desc>Desillusionerad av ökande regeringskorruption ställde [PAWN_nameDef] upp i guvernörsvalet och vann. Men de lokala banden och deras husdjur tjänstemän tvingade [PAWN_objective] snart från makten.

[PAWN_pronoun] lämnade samhället för att återvända till sitt liv som en sheriff.</desc>
	</ColonialGovernor77>
	<MercenaryRecruit12>
		<title>Legosoldatrekryt</title>
		<titleShort>Legosoldat</titleShort>
		<desc>Härstammad ifrån en lång rad globala legosoldater, växte [PAWN_nameDef] upp i ett flitigt handelscentrum.

[PAWN_possessive] intresse för utländska varor på marknaden distraherade honom ofta från [PAWN_possessive] sysslor och träning.</desc>
	</MercenaryRecruit12>
	<MercenaryChef30>
		<title>Legosoldatchef</title>
		<titleShort>Legosoldat</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter [PAWN_possessive] familjers fotspår var [PAWN_nameDef] en soldat för uthyrning.

[PAWN_pronoun] är en naturligt begåvad skarpskytt. Men [PAWN_possessive] verkliga passion är att perfekta ett nytt recept eller ta istär en ny manick.</desc>
	</MercenaryChef30>
	<AbandonedChild78>
		<title>Övergivet barn</title>
		<titleShort>Övergivet</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var ett kvicktänkt, roligt barn. En dag vandrade [PAWN_pronoun] iväg från sina rika föräldrar och blev slutligen förlorad i ett förmodat oanvänd malmlager. På grund av kloningstekniken bestämde sina föräldrar att tiden att let efter [PAWN_objective] var bättre spenderad på att bara klona ett bättre barn.</desc>
	</AbandonedChild78>
	<CargoPilot0>
		<title>Fraktpilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp bland lasthänder på ett långfartyg för transport av långmalm. [PAWN_pronoun] förbättrade sina färdigheter runt handel och manipulation av människor medan [PAWN_pronoun] fraktade vapen mellan system.</desc>
	</CargoPilot0>
	<TradersChild31>
		<title>Köpmansbarn</title>
		<titleShort>Köpman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en familj av nomadiska handlare, som lever av att sälja och köpa varor på många världar.

[PAWN_nameDef] lärde sig om tull och metoder för handel med många kulturer genom att delta i föräldrarnas verksamhet.</desc>
	</TradersChild31>
	<SpaceHumanitarian98>
		<title>Rymdhunanitär</title>
		<titleShort>Aktivist</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter att ha sett den våldsamma fattigdomen som är gemensam i överfulla stadsvärldar, bestämde [PAWN_nameDef] sig för att ägna sitt liv till att hjälpa de mindre lyckliga. Detta korståg lärde [PAWN_objective] hur man bryr sig om de sjuka och de hungriga.</desc>
	</SpaceHumanitarian98>
	<CorpStudent17>
		<title>Företagsstudent</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes för att bli en verkställande befattningshavare för det stora rymdhandelsföretaget som ägde sin hemplanet. [PAWN_possessive] familj hade arbetat för det företaget i sju generationer.

Vid sex års ålder började [PAWN_pronoun] studera vid företagsakademin, där [PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig att bli en lojal följare och en hänsynslös verkställande.</desc>
	</CorpStudent17>
	<ExecutiveOfficer58>
		<title>Verkställande direktör</title>
		<titleShort>Direktör</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en verkställande direktör för ett stort rymdhandelsföretag. Efter ett misslyckat försök att manipulera sin väg upp på företagsstigen, blev [PAWN_pronoun] beskylld för våldtäkt och mord på en annan verkställande och hennes familj.

[PAWN_pronoun] blev dömd för detta men på grund av sin familj förvisades [PAWN_pronoun] i stället för att dödas.</desc>
	</ExecutiveOfficer58>
	<VRAddict62>
		<title>VR-missbrukare</title>
		<titleShort>VR-knarkare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var ett VR-huvud - någon som är permanent inkopplad i det virtuella speluniversum genom sitt rygguttag. [PAWN_pronoun] rörde sig genom sina dagliga uppgifter knappt medvetna om den fysiska verkligheten omkring [PAWN_objective]. Detta lämnade [PAWN_objective] nästan oförmögen att socialisera.</desc>
	</VRAddict62>
	<RugbyPlayer15>
		<title>Rugbyspelare</title>
		<titleShort>Ytter</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter år av missbruk av virtuella verklighetsspel räddades [PAWN_nameDef] när doktorerna kopplade bort [PAWN_objective].

Tyvärr tog de bort [PAWN_objective] under en match i Rugby Rampage 4. Den mentala backlashen slog samman [PAWN_possessive] verkliga identitet och [PAWN_possessive] virtuella identitet, vilket gav [PAWN_objective] en personlighet och kompetens hos en rugby spelare.</desc>
	</RugbyPlayer15>
	<Nerd92>
		<title>Nörd</title>
		<titleShort>Nörd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var nyfiken på allt. Medan andra barn lekte lekar i förorterna i deras industristad, läste [PAWN_nameDef] varje bok som [PAWN_pronoun] kunde hitta om teknik, robotar och vapen - vad som helst såg coolast ut.

[PAWN_possessive] starka franska accent hindrade [PAWN_objective] från att få riktiga vänner.</desc>
	</Nerd92>
	<StateEngineer74>
		<title>Statlig ingenjör</title>
		<titleShort>Ingenjör</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] skrev in sig i statens vapenforskningsprogram.

Medan [PAWN_pronoun] var strålande i sitt arbete, var [PAWN_pronoun] så entusiastisk i att testa sina skapelser att [PAWN_pronoun] olyckligt sårade några kollegor och märktes som olämplig för tjänst.</desc>
	</StateEngineer74>
	<RebelSlave42>
		<title>Rebell Slav</title>
		<titleShort>Rebell</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] föddes in i företags slaveri och uppvuxen för att utföra simpla uppgifter för minimilön. [PAWN_pronoun] var bara en kugge i maskinen.

[PAWN_nameDef] fann sin frihet genom att ansluta sig till en rebellorganisation vars mål var att bryta sig undan sina företagsherrar.</desc>
	</RebelSlave42>
	<CombatNegotiator51>
		<title>Krigsförhandlare</title>
		<titleShort>Förhandlare</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter att ha släppt sin hemvärld tog [PAWN_nameDef] sina kunskaper till stjärnorna.

[PAWN_pronoun] valde att fungera som en legosoldat, som arbetar för olika rebellorganisationer, förslavade grupper och köpmansenklaver. Hans specialitet var förhandlingar i stridsituationer.</desc>
	</CombatNegotiator51>
	<MedievalPlower12>
		<title>Medletida plöjare</title>
		<titleShort>Plöjare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bodde på en planet där kungar och drottningar regerade med liten hänsyn till bönderna under dem. [PAWN_possessive]-familjen ägde en stor gård, men kungen tog det mesta av maten den producerade. Detta lämnade [PAWN_nameDef]'s familj fattiga, och kunde inte betala för någon utbildning. Istället var [PAWN_pronoun] tvungen att arbeta på fälten med sina föräldrar och aldrig haft tid att träna kreativitet.</desc>
	</MedievalPlower12>
	<SpaceStationCook63>
		<title>Rymdstationskock</title>
		<titleShort>Kock</titleShort>
		<desc>Rymstationen NAMN kom från var långt ifrån några befolkade planeter, och var i sig underbemannade. Därför tvingades NAMN att lära sig att laga mat för att hålla besättningen vid liv. Medan [PAWN_pronoun] uppskattade denna inlärningsmöjlighet uppskattade [PAWN_pronoun] inte kritiken som följde med det, och har sedan dess haft dålig självkänsla.</desc>
	</SpaceStationCook63>
	<SonOfAHuntress96>
		<title>Barn till jägarinna</title>
		<titleShort>Jägare</titleShort>
		<desc>I bergen på planeten Ticonderoga, blev [PAWN_nameDef] upplärd av sin stammoder. Hon lärde honom överlevnadsförmåga - fångst, spårning, skytte, skinning, matlagning och läkning.

[PAWN_possessive] avlidne far hade lämnat en gammal repeter-gevär, som [PAWN_nameDef] övade med vid varje chans som [PAWN_pronoun] fick.</desc>
	</SonOfAHuntress96>
	<SpaceHunter67>
		<title>Rymdjägare</title>
		<titleShort>Jägare</titleShort>
		<desc>Efter ha blivit en skicklig jägare och skarpskytt längtade [PAWN_nameDef] efter mer. [PAWN_pronoun] lämnade från sin födelsevärld och reste ut den stora expansionen på jakt efter exotiskt villebråd.</desc>
	</SpaceHunter67>
	<StudentSocialite73>
		<title>Studerande socitetslejon</title>
		<titleShort>Socitetslejon</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lärde sig politik i en elitträningsskola för socialt begåvade studenter på Kalthas IV.

Medan [PAWN_pronoun] var naturligt skicklig att läsa och manipulera människor fann [PAWN_pronoun] ingen glädje i den. [PAWN_pronoun] lämnade akademin flera år före examen.</desc>
	</StudentSocialite73>
	<PoliticalAssassin87>
		<title>Politisk lönnmördare</title>
		<titleShort>Dödsknekt</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] insåg att [PAWN_possessive] sanna kall var i fysiska lösningar på diplomatiska problem. [PAWN_pronoun] sökte sin utbildning på det ökända mördarskrået på Ceti V.

[PAWN_pronoun] var en duktig student av undanflykt och döden och steg snabbt till skrårang Dödsknekt.</desc>
	</PoliticalAssassin87>
	<AwkwardNerd12>
		<title>Pinsam nörd</title>
		<titleShort>Nörd</titleShort>
		<desc>Alltid fascinerad av maskiner spenderade [PAWN_nameDef] sin tid på att studera robotik och holografi. [PAWN_pronoun] föredrog gemenskap med sina vetenskapliga skapelser till andra människors.</desc>
	</AwkwardNerd12>
	<AIResearcher30>
		<title>AI-forskare</title>
		<titleShort>Forskare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] var en känd forskare inom artificiell intelligens, robotik och interaktiv holografi. [PAWN_possessive] vänskap med de konstgjorda sinnen [PAWN_pronoun] skapade gav [PAWN_objective] självförtroendet att interagera med riktiga människor, och [PAWN_pronoun] utmärkte sig snart på personlig kommunikation.</desc>
	</AIResearcher30>
	<MidworldGeek88>
		<title>Midvärldsnörd</title>
		<titleShort>Nörd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i ett lugnt förortsområde. [PAWN_pronoun] var aldrig en mästare i social interaktion, men [PAWN_possessive] intresse för datorer blomstrade till en sann talang i en tidig ålder.</desc>
	</MidworldGeek88>
	<ArmyScientist54>
		<title>Armevetenskapsman</title>
		<titleShort>Vetenskapsman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gjorde vetenskaplig forskning för en planetarisk armé. [PAWN_pronoun] studerade krigsscenarier och utformade vapensystem för att hjälpa till att vinna strider med ett minimum av väsen.</desc>
	</ArmyScientist54>
	<CatHerder45>
		<title>Kattherde</title>
		<titleShort>Herde</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] hjälpte till i sin fars kattuppfödningsaffär, socialiserat, herdade och utfodrade hundratals katter.

När [PAWN_pronoun] vägrade städa upp efter katterna, överfördes [PAWN_pronoun] till avelsvetenskapsavdelningen.</desc>
	</CatHerder45>
	<FelineScientist25>
		<title>Kattvetenskapsman</title>
		<titleShort>Vetenskapsman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] blev en känd forskare inom kattdjur. [PAWN_pronoun] ville ha det bästa för sina djur och specialiserat sig på selektiv avel. [PAWN_pronoun] satte på en resa för att hitta de perfekta avelsplatserna för sina katter.</desc>
	</FelineScientist25>
	<Scavenger26>
		<title>Sopletare</title>
		<titleShort>Sopletare</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] växte upp i en av de få återstående städerna på en värld som krossades av kärnvapenskrig.

[PAWN_pronoun] lärde sig att överleva på egen hand i denna post-apokalyptiska ödemark genom att leta efter teknik och förnödenheter.</desc>
	</Scavenger26>
	<SpaceMarine90>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recruited into the security forces of an off-planet corporation.

[PAWN_pronoun] defended their ships against pirates and engaged in private space warfare contracts.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine90>
	<VatgrownAssassin17>
		<title>Vatgrown assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Clone</titleShort>
		<desc>Vas was not made as a man, but a cold hearted assassin. He was bio-engineered by scientists, and trained as a killer. He was bred to have no emotion, no feelings, and no care for who lives, and who dies.</desc>
	</VatgrownAssassin17>
	<Mercenary40>
		<title>Mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>Merc</titleShort>
		<desc>Vas spent his teenage years as a mercenary, being hired to kill and maim others. He was tall, menacing, and frightening. He could instill fear into the hearts of any man who crossed him, and kill anyone he wanted.</desc>
	</Mercenary40>
	<HiveWorldChild62>
		<title>Hive world child</title>
		<titleShort>Hiver</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had an isolated upbringing in an urbworld hive city. His hatred of heights kept him indoors often, and made him an introverted child.

When [PAWN_pronoun] did go out onto the catwalks of the city, [PAWN_pronoun] enjoyed playing war games, becoming proficient with various simulation weapons.</desc>
	</HiveWorldChild62>
	<Microbiologist37>
		<title>Microbiologist</title>
		<titleShort>Biologist</titleShort>
		<desc>A plague struck [PAWN_nameDef]'s native urbworld. [PAWN_nameDef] and other researchers revealed that the illness was a bioweapon, but the people turned on them, blaming them for the sickness.

[PAWN_nameDef] barely escaped his homeworld as it fell into chaos.</desc>
	</Microbiologist37>
	<StarforceCadet91>
		<title>Starforce cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised on Amen-Ti, glitterworld capital of the Star Empire, Sam Wissa had an easy childhood.

As a youth, Sam decided that joining the Starforce would be his way of giving back to the Empire.</desc>
	</StarforceCadet91>
	<AceFighterPilot70>
		<title>Ace fighter pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Ace</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] graduated from the Star Academy with honors and distinguished himself as an ace fighter pilot in three campaigns against more advanced aggressor cultures. 

However, after one vicious battle, he found himself stranded and his carrier ship destroyed. With nowhere to go, he entered his escape pod and prayed.</desc>
	</AceFighterPilot70>
	<Stableboy75>
		<title>Stableboy</title>
		<titleShort>Stableboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a stableboy on a medieval planet, mucking dung almost every day to earn his keep.

By the time [PAWN_pronoun] was exiting childhood, [PAWN_nameDef] had saved up enough money to pay a space trader to take [PAWN_objective] offworld.</desc>
	</Stableboy75>
	<Brigand23>
		<title>Brigand</title>
		<titleShort>Brigand</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] flew with a band of brigands [PAWN_pronoun] called friends. [PAWN_pronoun] even had a ship of [PAWN_possessive] own - The Dung Mucker 2000.</desc>
	</Brigand23>
	<ArtfulDodger87>
		<title>Artful dodger</title>
		<titleShort>Dodger</titleShort>
		<desc>Robin grew up on one of the urbworlds and had to fend for himself all his life. He never trusted anyone, relying on his persuasiveness and cunning to survive.

He soon became skilled with firearms and knives as well as words.</desc>
	</ArtfulDodger87>
	<Assassin16>
		<title>Assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Robin was specially trained as an operative to be used for high-risk assassinations. His skill with a rifle was unrivalled.

He was eventually betrayed by his superiors when a target found out about the hit and offered to fund their future projects. Robin swore to never trust anyone again.</desc>
	</Assassin16>
	<Pickpocket6>
		<title>Pickpocket</title>
		<titleShort>Pickpocket</titleShort>
		<desc>Orphaned and abandoned on the tumultuous streets of his polluted, teeming homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] survived by deft hand and fleet foot. A natural born thief and trickster, [PAWN_pronoun] rose to prominence early, running the notorious and violent urchin gang 'Doomben Rats'.</desc>
	</Pickpocket6>
	<BusinessGangster83>
		<title>Business gangster</title>
		<titleShort>Gangster</titleShort>
		<desc>Staying one step ahead of the law, [PAWN_nameDef] became a legitimate businessman and silenced anyone who dared say otherwise. As proprietor of brothels, speakeasies and eateries, [PAWN_nameDef]'s good fortune continued while his competition suffered a series of unfortunate and unexplained accidents.</desc>
	</BusinessGangster83>
	<DisasterSurvivor58>
		<title>Disaster survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>Steven was uprooted when marauders attacked his family farm, destroying machinery and killing farmhands and beasts alike.

After the death of all he knew, he was left in the ruins to fend for himself.</desc>
	</DisasterSurvivor58>
	<ParamilitaryAgent3>
		<title>Paramilitary agent</title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>After scraping by on assorted shady jobs, [PAWN_nameDef] joined with a large paramilitary group to fight a war on [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_possessive] role was infiltration and intelligence gathering</desc>
	</ParamilitaryAgent3>
	<HistoryStudent52>
		<title>History student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>As a child, [PAWN_nameDef] spent learned many artistic forms including music and novel writing. As [PAWN_pronoun] grew older, [PAWN_pronoun] began to study legends from [PAWN_possessive] home world - legends of the lizard-like beings at the center of [PAWN_possessive] culture's folklore.</desc>
	</HistoryStudent52>
	<Storyteller68>
		<title>Storyteller</title>
		<titleShort>Fabulist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled his world recounting the legends that he had studied.

Obsessed with the legends of his people, [PAWN_nameDef] seeks someone who can help him grow scales on his skin, so he too can be as the ancients were.</desc>
	</Storyteller68>
	<NobleWard25>
		<title>Noble ward</title>
		<titleShort>Ward</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adopted by a prominent noble family after being left on their doorstep by [PAWN_possessive] mother.

[PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned secrets that passed between the nobles like cheap wine - of worlds beyond her own, languages, cultures and technologies both new and old.</desc>
	</NobleWard25>
	<InformationBroker88>
		<title>Information broker</title>
		<titleShort>Broker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] caught a ship to the next star system and began a life of travel and learning, quickly collecting a massive bank of knowledge from people of all shapes and sizes.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned to sell this knowledge for great profit, and became a powerful broker of information.</desc>
	</InformationBroker88>
	<FeralChild63>
		<title>Feral child</title>
		<titleShort>Feral</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned on an animal planet as a small child with nought but a blanket with a name embroidered on it, Felix made himself one with the wilderness.

When he was 13, he encountered a team of mineral surveyors, who "offered" him passage off of the planet.</desc>
	</FeralChild63>
	<VersatileWorker37>
		<title>Versatile worker</title>
		<titleShort>Worker</titleShort>
		<desc>Spending his later teenage years in a colony of settlers, he offered what little skills he had to anyone who would take him.

Being a quick learner, he honed many of his skills and, apart from his crippling inability to understand fire, is now a fully functioning adult.</desc>
	</VersatileWorker37>
	<SpoiledChild32>
		<title>Spoiled child</title>
		<titleShort>Spoiled</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up the child of an industrious colony manager. In this position, most manual and dangerous tasks were forbidden by [PAWN_possessive] parents, but on the rim everyone has to dirty their hands.</desc>
	</SpoiledChild32>
	<TestSubject1>
		<title>Test subject</title>
		<titleShort>Experiment</titleShort>
		<desc>Kidnapped as a teenager, [PAWN_nameDef] was an unwilling test subject in experimental gene therapies for six years. Labs and scientists scare [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</TestSubject1>
	<AmateurEngineer21>
		<title>Amateur engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a family with a military and engineering background. [PAWN_pronoun] wanted to join the army but his father didn't like the idea, so [PAWN_possessive] interest turned to great flying machines and works of engineering. [PAWN_pronoun] secretly hoped that this would one day lead him to a life of galactic exploration.</desc>
	</AmateurEngineer21>
	<AerospaceEngineer58>
		<title>Aerospace engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an engineer responsible for the production of aircraft and spaceships. [PAWN_pronoun] focused on improving production lines, and was known for [PAWN_possessive] mastery of technical and research issues.</desc>
	</AerospaceEngineer58>
	<WildChild8>
		<title>Wild child</title>
		<titleShort>Wild child</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abandoned on a toxic world overgrown with hostile plant life. [PAWN_pronoun] became accustomed early to the cold burn of loneliness.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned to fight, but ate his food raw and uncooked.</desc>
	</WildChild8>
	<AlcoholicTrucker38>
		<title>Alcoholic trucker</title>
		<titleShort>Alcoholic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a space trucker working for Arcknight Industries when he killed his wife and daughter in a crash.

His body was repaired with an experimental nano-genetic therapy. Now his muscles continually regenerate and harden, and every movement tears the tissue anew. He bears the pain in silence.</desc>
	</AlcoholicTrucker38>
	<HackerProdigy70>
		<title>Hacker prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Wedge was raised as the only child of wealthy surgeons. After being pressured into accepting a medical apprenticeship, he snapped. He seized his inheritance and went underground to learn how to exploit computer networks. He quickly became one of the most feared hackers on his home planet.</desc>
	</HackerProdigy70>
	<IntelligenceAgent4>
		<title>Intelligence agent</title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>Because of his hacking skills, Wedge was recruited by his home planet's governing body to serve as an intelligence agent. The government trained him in combat, but he prefers psychological warfare.

Government rules proved too strict for him, so he went rogue. His current activities are unknown.</desc>
	</IntelligenceAgent4>
	<MadScientist38>
		<title>Mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up miserable on the plains of a neolithic planet. He found the strength to fight under the teachings of an old, broken scientist.

He quickly learned to play with people's fears, and was nicknamed 'mad scientist'.</desc>
	</MadScientist38>
	<WarChief54>
		<title>War chief</title>
		<titleShort>Chief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a tribal gang leader on a neolithic planet. For him, the battlefield is a game, and there is nothing more fun than the fires of war.</desc>
	</WarChief54>
	<YouthDelinquent81>
		<title>Youth delinquent</title>
		<titleShort>Delinquent</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the only child of celebrity sommeliers. Her parents expected her to take up the family profession, but after her third admission to a youth detention center, this career path became unlikely.

While in detention, [PAWN_nameDef] became skilled at making shanks and developed an interest in orinthology.</desc>
	</YouthDelinquent81>
	<InvoluntaryHermit72>
		<title>Involuntary hermit</title>
		<titleShort>Hermit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]’s escape pod was jettisoned onto an unexplored region of a frontier world. She eked out a lonely existence with only a herd of muffalo for company.
 
Later, she was spotted clad in pygmy wombat furs, discussing the importance of hoof hygiene with a group of elderly muffalo.</desc>
	</InvoluntaryHermit72>
	<HillbillyProdigy33>
		<title>Hillbilly prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Hillbilly</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a cold hillbilly planet inhabited mainly by furred xenohumans, Benjamin grew up to the sound of bar fights and shootouts. Though his childhood was spent playing the banjo and working as a mechanic, his abnormal intelligence made him want something more; he entered medical school at age twenty.</desc>
	</HillbillyProdigy33>
	<MedicalScientist25>
		<title>Medical scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Benjamin enlisted as a doctor on a passing science vessel. Roaming the stars with a large crew of xenohumans and transbirds, he did genetic research on encountered species. He developed a deep friendship with one transbird but was forced to leave the ship when the captain dismissed all non-avians.</desc>
	</MedicalScientist25>
	<UrbworldUrchin35>
		<title>Urbworld urchin</title>
		<titleShort>Urchin</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned among the filthy concrete spires, [PAWN_nameDef] never knew [PAWN_possessive] parents. [PAWN_pronoun] never received formal education, and often resorted to doing menial labor in exchange for food. Sometimes [PAWN_pronoun] lied, cheated, and stole to survive.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin35>
	<VoidRaider31>
		<title>Void raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Craving adventure and glory, [PAWN_nameDef] set out across the void with a raider band, swearing his loyalty to his band and brothers, and spreading their glory through the stars with his blade and pistol in hand.</desc>
	</VoidRaider31>				   
	<MidworldSketcher21>
		<title>Midworld sketcher</title>
		<titleShort>Sketcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a loving but poor family.

[PAWN_pronoun] discovered he had an artistic talent which he inherited from his father. [PAWN_possessive] mother taught him the benefits of hard work and determination. As he grew older, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a fascination with technology and military history.</desc>
	</MidworldSketcher21>
	<MidworldSailor20>
		<title>Midworld sailor</title>
		<titleShort>Sailor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined his country's Royal Navy. After years as a non-commissioned officer, he eventually cracked and used the skills he had acquired to start a mutiny on his ship.

In the end, [PAWN_nameDef] was the leader of a large group of trained and dangerous pirates. He henceforth always had chefs to cook for him.</desc>
	</MidworldSailor20>
	<CoreWorldStudent4>
		<title>Core world student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>Born a male named Alex, Alyssa didn't fit in well with the other boys. When very young, she preferred creative pursuits, such as crafting jewelry, over sports. She felt she had the wrong body. Luckily, her family and friends supported her sex reassignment; as a teen, she underwent surgery to become a female.</desc>
	</CoreWorldStudent4>
	<CoreWorldJeweler59>
		<title>Core world jeweler</title>
		<titleShort>Jeweler</titleShort>
		<desc>After Alyssa had completed all of her surgeries, she found that she had a lot of time and energy to dedicate to her passion: trinket crafting. She spent years perfecting her art as a jeweler, then left her home world to sell her wares across the galaxy.</desc>
	</CoreWorldJeweler59>
	<MedievalSquire61>
		<title>Medieval squire</title>
		<titleShort>Squire</titleShort>
		<desc>William grew up on a medieval planet as a knight in training. He trained directly under the king's war adviser for most of his youth, and learned to fight with a sword and shield.</desc>
	</MedievalSquire61>
	<MedievalKnight71>
		<title>Medieval knight </title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>William fought for king and country on the battlefield, where he further honed his skill as a swordsman. His greatest glory was leading a charge into an enemy courtroom and capturing the king at sword point.</desc>
	</MedievalKnight71>
	<StarSquire93>
		<title>Star squire</title>
		<titleShort>Squire</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a medieval word, [PAWN_nameDef]'s first memory is of gazing up into the night's sky. 

Ever since, [PAWN_pronoun] dreamed of squiring for a knight amidst the star-filled heavens. [PAWN_possessive] focus on that vision left [PAWN_objective] somewhat single-minded.</desc>
	</StarSquire93>
	<StarKnight78>
		<title>Star knight</title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>Abducted from his medieval homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] later escaped his captors via an impressive display of swordsmanship.

For a moment, as he drifted in the escape pod, his childhood dream of becoming a knight among the stars felt so real. Then he crash-landed.</desc>
	</StarKnight78>
	<DrugMule2>
		<title>Drug mule</title>
		<titleShort>Mule</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised in an orphanage, [PAWN_nameDef] turned towards the gang life at age ten.

He was exploited by the local gang as a drug mule to traffic "substance F" across rival gang territory. He took a bullet or two.</desc>
	</DrugMule2>
	<TestSubject82>
		<title>Test subject</title>
		<titleShort>Subject</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] enrolled in a scientific study that promised it could make [PAWN_objective] smarter. Unfortunately, the side effects were very different than he expected.[PAWN_pronoun] went insane and killed a number of people before escaping his homeworld.</desc>
	</TestSubject82>
	<ArtisanFarmer56>
		<title>Artisan farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a [PAWN_possessive] family's glitterworld farm. They were one of the last farms on the planet that preferred traditional farming methods to glitterworld technology.</desc>
	</ArtisanFarmer56>
	<GeneticEngineer63>
		<title>Genetic engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Geneticist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] carried out [PAWN_possessive] first genetic experiments on farm animals. [PAWN_pronoun] soon grew to become quite skilled in all forms of genetic engineering.

A horrifying lab accident left him with a mortal fear of rodents.</desc>
	</GeneticEngineer63>
	<Pampered62>
		<title>Pampered</title>
		<titleShort>Pampered</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a decadent glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was given every expensive toy.

This pampered lifestyle caused [PAWN_objective] to miss many basic life lessons. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a special aversion to cooking, and always ordered the staff to do the kitchen work.</desc>
	</Pampered62>
	<NinjaAssassin4>
		<title>Ninja assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Ninja</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed stiletto-precise assassinations for an interplanetary conglomerate. [PAWN_pronoun] was assigned the most complex missions involving disguise, deception, subterfuge, and efficient violence.

A nasty incident with a potted plant and an assassination gone wrong left [PAWN_objective] with an aversion to plant life.</desc>
	</NinjaAssassin4>
	<MilitaryChild84>
		<title>Military child</title>
		<titleShort>Military</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a family with a rich military background. [PAWN_possessive] teenage years were spent traveling system to system wherever [PAWN_possessive] parents were deployed.

[PAWN_pronoun] enlisted at age 18, following the tradition of [PAWN_possessive] family.</desc>
	</MilitaryChild84>
	<LazyProgrammer84>
		<title>Lazy programmer</title>
		<titleShort>Programmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] independently developed software that had a competitive edge against local urbworld corporations.

[PAWN_possessive] legally questionable methods lead to a growing number in unsolved claims of intellectual property theft.</desc>
	</LazyProgrammer84>
	<GangMember82>
		<title>Gang member</title>
		<titleShort>Ganger</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up homeless on an urbworld. [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to fight and struggle for everything, making [PAWN_objective] hard and ruthless long before adulthood.

[PAWN_nameDef] would have stayed in those streets, had [PAWN_pronoun] not been injured in a shootout and had his body confiscated for use by one of the worldwide city's ruling corporations.</desc>
	</GangMember82>
	<MindwipedAssassin80>
		<title>Mindwiped assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Mindwipe</titleShort>
		<desc>The corporation took and remade [PAWN_nameDef]. They trained [PAWN_objective] into an tool of destruction and subversion. [PAWN_pronoun] took to [PAWN_possessive] new life, finding satisfaction in the jobs they sent [PAWN_objective] on.

When [PAWN_pronoun] learned that they planned on disposing of [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_nameDef] turned on his masters, killing several and fleeing the planet.</desc>
	</MindwipedAssassin80>
	<TestSubject90>
		<title>Test subject</title>
		<titleShort>Subject</titleShort>
		<desc>Test subject #11,529,914 of experiment #56,048 spent her childhood in white rooms performing mental and physical tests.

Her only companion was a voice that called itself Mother. Mother rewarded success with praise - and failure with harsh punishment.</desc>
	</TestSubject90>
	<TestSubject6>
		<title>Test subject</title>
		<titleShort>Subject</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s tests went from geometry to quantum physics, and she could run the grand gauntlet without a scratch.

One day, Mother said that her final test lay beyond the red door, and that even if she couldn't hear her voice, Mother would always be there.</desc>
	</TestSubject6>
	<FireScarredChild32>
		<title>Fire-scarred child</title>
		<titleShort>Scarred</titleShort>
		<desc>Duster was an active child who lived an uneventful childhood until he fell into a fire and suffered horrific burns to his hands and arms. Although the scars have faded, he can't bear to be in close proximity to fire.</desc>
	</FireScarredChild32>
	<SpaceshipSalesman6>
		<title>Spaceship salesman</title>
		<titleShort>Salesman</titleShort>
		<desc>Duster tried his hand at various jobs, including building space rabbit cages and working at a mutant wheat research project. Finally, he found his true calling as a spacecraft salesman. Specializing in recreational spacecraft, his smooth talk and charming nature served him well.</desc>
	</SpaceshipSalesman6>
	<TechEnthusiast65>
		<title>Tech enthusiast</title>
		<titleShort>Tech nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>Michael had all the latest gadgets as a child. He spent all his time playing games with AIs instead of with other children. He always felt awkward around new people.</desc>
	</TechEnthusiast65>
	<AIProgrammer5>
		<title>AI programmer</title>
		<titleShort>Programmer</titleShort>
		<desc>Michael enlisted in the military's robotics division, developing smarter combat AI.

The whole time he was there, he never spoke with another human. He spent all his time conversing with the AI he was developing.</desc>
	</AIProgrammer5>
	<DiplomatsChild66>
		<title>Diplomat's child</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in diplomatic family.

Travelling often, [PAWN_pronoun] was home-schooled and saw the world mostly through a computer.</desc>
	</DiplomatsChild66>
	<WhiteHatHacker49>
		<title>White-hat hacker</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>From [PAWN_possessive] computer, [PAWN_nameDef] helped rid the online world of bad people.</desc>
	</WhiteHatHacker49>
	<Winerunner96>
		<title>Winerunner</title>
		<titleShort>Winerunner</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned by his parents, [PAWN_nameDef] was raised by the monks of the Novo Mosteiro dos Jerónimos monastery on Aracena VI.

The monks taught him discipline and hard work. In return, [PAWN_pronoun] would go into the city and 'acquire' exotic wines for the monks' nightly tastings.</desc>
	</Winerunner96>
	<VinhoKing50>
		<title>Vinho king</title>
		<titleShort>Booze king</titleShort>
		<desc>After prohibition came to Aracena VI, [PAWN_nameDef] expanded his underground liquor business until it dominated the market on two continents. They called him the Vinho King.

Though [PAWN_pronoun] mostly controlled his competition by masterful political maneuvering, [PAWN_pronoun] was not above the occasional beat-down or stiletto assassination.</desc>
	</VinhoKing50>
	<StreetChild49>
		<title>Street child</title>
		<titleShort>Street</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s drug addict mother died, leaving [PAWN_objective] an orphan at a young age. To stay alive, [PAWN_pronoun] resorted to theft, and when necessary, prostitution. When [PAWN_nameDef] was caught stealing from a church, the priestess saw a wounded but smart child, and took [PAWN_objective] in to give [PAWN_objective] a second chance at life.</desc>
	</StreetChild49>
	<SlaveChemist35>
		<title>Slave chemist</title>
		<titleShort>Chemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a gifted pharmaceutical scientist, but was captured by slavers. [PAWN_pronoun] was sold to a warlord and forced to create drugs to test on other slaves. This left [PAWN_objective] with deep and troubling questions on the ethics of scientific research and medicine.</desc>
	</SlaveChemist35>
	<SlaveFarmer49>
		<title>Slave farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned as a little girl, [PAWN_nameDef] was found by a farmer. Being infertile himself, the farmer kept her as a slave. The constant beatings left her scarred and unable to handle violence. After many years, she ran away.</desc>
	</SlaveFarmer49>
	<RocketEngineer75>
		<title>Rocket engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] won a grant to a top school and earned a degree in rocket engineering. After several years working for a space mining company she left to travel and see the universe.</desc>
	</RocketEngineer75>
	<MedievalSlave34>
		<title>Medieval slave</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into slavery, Soren never knew his parents. He eventually escaped from his masters and boarded a military cargo ship, where he was pressed into military service.</desc>
	</MedievalSlave34>
	<SpaceMarine27>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>Soren joined a squad of space marines known for their brutal efficiency at killing. His last name and his lack of emotion during combat inspired his nickname: Grim.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine27>
	<FoundryApprentice81>
		<title>Foundry apprentice</title>
		<titleShort>Foundryman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as an apprentice in the foundries of an industrial world. This experience gave [PAWN_objective] metalworking skills and strong muscles, but stunted [PAWN_possessive] artistic development.</desc>
	</FoundryApprentice81>
	<CombatEngineer42>
		<title>Combat engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a combat engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] built bases, fixed guns, and repaired vehicles for the army - when [PAWN_pronoun] wasn't shooting at people, that is.</desc>
	</CombatEngineer42>
	<PrivilegedProdigy5>
		<title>Privileged prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recognized as gifted early in his glitterworld upbringing. Luckily, [PAWN_possessive] family was in a position to cultivate that genius through advanced education. [PAWN_possessive] training included science, leadership, and the arts.</desc>
	</PrivilegedProdigy5>
	<PlanetaryDiplomat42>
		<title>Planetary diplomat</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s passion and profession was interplanetary politics. [PAWN_pronoun] was a master of social manipulation and negotiation and devoted [PAWN_objective]self to working towards peace, compromise and mutual benefit.</desc>
	</PlanetaryDiplomat42>
	<ChildProdigy22>
		<title>Child prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating college at age twelve, Jered devoted his life to becoming immortal.  However his research crossed the line when he tried to modify his body using gene therapy and mechanical augmentation.  He was arrested and condemned to a prison planet.</desc>
	</ChildProdigy22>
	<RenegadeEngineer33>
		<title>Renegade engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>After a daring escape from the prison planet with a small crew of fellow inmates, Jered set his gaze on his homeworld.

He travelled there, recruited more followers, hijacked a space cruiser, and launched into the void.</desc>
	</RenegadeEngineer33>
	<BoneCollector51>
		<title>Bone collector</title>
		<titleShort>Pupil</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a family of fortune hunters, [PAWN_nameDef] always had a passion for ancient history.

Though never a tough or social boy, [PAWN_pronoun] loved to dig through history books as well as dirt piles.</desc>
	</BoneCollector51>
	<Osteologist68>
		<title>Osteologist</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating university at the top of his class, [PAWN_nameDef] quickly became a well-known and athletic college professor.

With his new found fame and fitness came a sudden reluctance to preform menial labor - such tasks are better left to graduate students.</desc>
	</Osteologist68>
	<GNomeSculptor81>
		<title>G-nome sculptor</title>
		<titleShort>Sculptor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was engineered in a lab as part of the G-nome Project. He was implanted at birth with encyclopedic knowledge of all aspects of xenobiology.

The G-nome scientists nicknamed him Gizmo and occupied him with sculpting. He developed a love of sculpting gnomes and gnome accessories.</desc>
	</GNomeSculptor81>
	<Gnomebiologist56>
		<title>Gnomebiologist</title>
		<titleShort>Biologist</titleShort>
		<desc>Gizmo was a xenobiology professor in a glitterworld university. He went to conferences and managed an art gallery.

However, he never stopped sculpting yard gnomes, and considers this to be his true profession.</desc>
	</Gnomebiologist56>
	<CircusPerformer69>
		<title>Circus performer</title>
		<titleShort>Performer</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in the circus, [PAWN_nameDef] learned a lot of interesting things. More interesting then the balls he juggled were the pockets he picked between shows.

A mistake with some firesticks made him develop a deathly fear of fire.</desc>
	</CircusPerformer69>
	<CriminalKingpin63>
		<title>Criminal kingpin</title>
		<titleShort>Kingpin</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] discovered his gift - people did what he said, when he said it. Taking advantage of this, he set off for the rimworlds planets to make a name for himself in the criminal underworld.

Having people do things for him taught him to avoid manual labor at all costs.</desc>
	</CriminalKingpin63>
	<VatgrownSlavegirl4>
		<title>Vatgrown slavegirl</title>
		<titleShort>Slave girl</titleShort>
		<desc>Emmie was vat-grown as a slave in an illegal urbworld laboratory. As a young child, she was taught only to cook, clean and serve her masters. For most of her childhood, she knew nothing else.</desc>
	</VatgrownSlavegirl4>
	<UrbworldSexSlave3>
		<title>Urbworld sex slave</title>
		<titleShort>Sex slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Emmie was sold into sexual slavery. Having been designed to be inhumanly attractive and too weak to rebel against her masters, she was passed between dozens of owners and knew nothing of freedom.</desc>
	</UrbworldSexSlave3>
	<GunKid57>
		<title>Gun kid</title>
		<titleShort>Gun kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in a urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] never had it easy. Every day was a struggle and pollution, hunger, and gangs of older kids.

In the little space he had to himself, he studied his passion - guns, combat tactics, and war history.</desc>
	</GunKid57>
	<UrbworldSergeant87>
		<title>Urbworld sergeant</title>
		<titleShort>Sergeant</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s passion for all things militaristic kept with him all the way to adulthood.

After enrolling as a local policeman, he was soon promoted to sergeant.</desc>
	</UrbworldSergeant87>
	<FeudalLordling43>
		<title>Feudal lordling</title>
		<titleShort>Lordling</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a feudal world that was part of a multi-planet empire. As the son of a high lord, [PAWN_pronoun] enjoyed many privileges.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned to maneuver in the both the political landscape and in close quarters combat.</desc>
	</FeudalLordling43>
	<SystemLord49>
		<title>System lord</title>
		<titleShort>Lord</titleShort>
		<desc>For [PAWN_nameDef], ruling a country, or even a planet, was not good enough. [PAWN_pronoun] sought to expand his influence across the system - by legal or extralegal means.</desc>
	</SystemLord49>
	<FeudalFarmBoy31>
		<title>Feudal farm boy</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the son of a medieval farmer, and was expected to follow in his footsteps. He was brought up as a kind, well trained farm boy.

He lived in an unusual feudal kingdom which co-existed with a midworld society which was itself well-known for genetic manipulation.</desc>
	</FeudalFarmBoy31>
	<HunterOfTheKing3>
		<title>Hunter of the king</title>
		<titleShort>Pest guard</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was forced to protect his colony in the name of the king after a mysterious outbreak of murderous genetically-modified wildlife.

Despite his best efforts, his kingdom was destroyed. [PAWN_nameDef] developed PTSD, a hatred of animals and a bad case of technophobia. [PAWN_pronoun] was named for the place they found him.</desc>
	</HunterOfTheKing3>
	<SpaceFanboy24>
		<title>Space fanboy</title>
		<titleShort>Fanboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] dreamed of space travel. He built his own pretend spaceship from an old police box and went to see the great unknown.</desc>
	</SpaceFanboy24>
	<Castaway19>
		<title>Castaway</title>
		<titleShort>Castaway</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a passenger on a routine interstellar transit. When his ship was destroyed, he lived as a castaway on an uninhabited planet for several years.</desc>
	</Castaway19>
	<GlitterworldNerd52>
		<title>Glitterworld nerd</title>
		<titleShort>Nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved technology from the day [PAWN_pronoun] was born. [PAWN_pronoun] had a mechanoid companion which [PAWN_pronoun] tried to modify when [PAWN_pronoun] was 10.

[PAWN_possessive] obsession with technology meant that [PAWN_pronoun] never appreciated arts or culture.</desc>
	</GlitterworldNerd52>
	<EnergyResearcher46>
		<title>Energy researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was working on an idea for rapid communication over long distances. [PAWN_pronoun] made an error which destroyed [PAWN_possessive] lab and most of the city. [PAWN_pronoun] fled the planet to escape the authorities.</desc>
	</EnergyResearcher46>
	<WarChild73>
		<title>War child</title>
		<titleShort>War child</titleShort>
		<desc>Mushinto's parents were drafted into a civil war in his home country. Growing up surrounded by fighting and death, he became well-accustomed to tragedy and tough as nails. His expressive side, however, never developed.</desc>
	</WarChild73>
	<BountyHunter22>
		<title>Bounty hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>When the civil war ended, Mushinto had to find a new way to use his fighting skills. He decided to hunt down war criminals and soon realized that he enjoyed capturing  bad guys by any means necessary.</desc>
	</BountyHunter22>
	<UpperUrbworlder20>
		<title>Upper urbworlder</title>
		<titleShort>High urber</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a privileged childhood on a major urbworld. Living in an apartment far above the dense poverty of the city, [PAWN_pronoun] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time reading or drawing the cityscape he saw through [PAWN_possessive] window.</desc>
	</UpperUrbworlder20>
	<Missionary23>
		<title>Missionary</title>
		<titleShort>Missionary</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] decided to devote [PAWN_possessive] life to religious service. [PAWN_pronoun] made a vow of peace and spent several years preaching and serving food in soup kitchens for the homeless.</desc>
	</Missionary23>
	<IdealisticCadet35>
		<title>Idealistic cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised in the military traditions of his forefathers, [PAWN_nameDef] was taught from a young age that he would be a great leader and the hero of the Dichter family.

He excelled at his studies and graduated from the academy with honors.</desc>
	</IdealisticCadet35>
	<MercenaryPilot69>
		<title>Mercenary pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] convinced his squadron to abscond with their ships and make a course for the rim worlds. There they could fight for the causes they believed in.

His men were loyal and fought hard, but their ideals soon faded away and their cause became that of the highest bidder.</desc>
	</MercenaryPilot69>
	<ChildOfGlass96>
		<title>Child of glass</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised underground on a "marble" planet - a wasteland of radioactive asphalt and toxic fallout.

To survive on a planet devoid of life, [PAWN_pronoun] had to learn how to farm underground and how to fight without wasting bullets.</desc>
	</ChildOfGlass96>
	<LoneTraveler73>
		<title>Lone traveler</title>
		<titleShort>Traveler</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping [PAWN_possessive] homeworld on a jury-rigged ship, [PAWN_nameDef] traveled to new worlds to experience their beauty.

[PAWN_pronoun] joined resistance groups and applied the skills [PAWN_pronoun] cultivated on [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_pronoun] often warned of the nuclear horror [PAWN_pronoun] saw as a child.</desc>
	</LoneTraveler73>
	<AmateurBotanist14>
		<title>Amateur botanist</title>
		<titleShort>Botanist</titleShort>
		<desc>Spending many summers crawling through dirt, Christian found he had quite the green thumb. Instead of learning to cook the food he grew, he just grew more and more.</desc>
	</AmateurBotanist14>
	<Undertaker50>
		<title>Undertaker</title>
		<titleShort>Undertaker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] roamed the galaxy offering grief assistance to those who've had a recent loss. While he never shied away from physical confrontation, he prefers to confront tough situations with a calm word.</desc>
	</Undertaker50>
	<ChildSlave6>
		<title>Child slave</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Graham was born to a poor family on a rimworld. His father sold him into slavery at a young age and he was traded many times. A tycoon bought him as part of a child labor force and sent down into mines to look after machines and to work alongside them.</desc>
	</ChildSlave6>
	<Mercenary75>
		<title>Mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping a crew of rimworld slavers, Graham developed a lack of respect for life. He proceeded to sign on to a mercenary group where he developed skills using guns and survival techniques. Graham did dirty work where he found it, and traveled to many worlds.</desc>
	</Mercenary75>
	<AdventuringChild56>
		<title>Adventuring child</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>Axle was raised to become an engineer. For years, he planned to stow away on a cargo ship and start a new, more adventuresome life.

One night, after his parents fell asleep, he managed to sneak on board a cargo ship just before it left port.</desc>
	</AdventuringChild56>
	<HiredAssassin2>
		<title>Hired assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Axle was a master thief, working mostly for organized crime. Over time, he made a name for himself and shifted his business into the paid "removal" of human threats.</desc>
	</HiredAssassin2>
	<VideoGamer91>
		<title>Video gamer</title>
		<titleShort>Gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>Ryan was raised in a glitterworld. Everything he wanted came to him. In school he was a social butterfly. At home, he spent his time looking up the newest gadgets and playing his favourite video games.</desc>
	</VideoGamer91>
	<SpaceshipChef34>
		<title>Spaceship chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>Ryan got a spot on a ship by becoming the ship's cook. He enjoyed cooking and helping the doctor clean wounds, but he never got used to cleaning the dishes.</desc>
	</SpaceshipChef34>
	<DreadedBaby55>
		<title>Dreaded baby</title>
		<titleShort>Baby dude</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was found as a baby in a crashed spacecraft. According to the ship's data records, [PAWN_pronoun] invented the nuclear device that powered his ship. Apparently, he also invented the sky and the hamburger, and is said to have fathered a race of tasty golden kittens.</desc>
	</DreadedBaby55>
	<DreadedDude3>
		<title>Dreaded dude</title>
		<titleShort>Dude</titleShort>
		<desc>Some followers say that [PAWN_nameDef] and [PAWN_possessive] crew of misfits found the Fountain of Youth, many, many centuries ago, and that they caused the extinction of the dinosaurs on many planets.

There's even a religion about them, somewhere, involving noodles and meatballs.</desc>
	</DreadedDude3>
	<Tinkerer87>
		<title>Tinkerer</title>
		<titleShort>Tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a scrap-heap of a planet - the garbage dump of other planets in the system. He learned to make new machines from the dead parts of old ones. With some friends, he eventually escaped on a salvaged and repaired ship.</desc>
	</Tinkerer87>
	<Engineer9>
		<title>Engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] found a job as a tinkering engineer on the trading hub planet Irithir. Tough local traders forced him to learn negotiation skills, and he made good profits selling refurbished weapons and tools.</desc>
	</Engineer9>
	<DisplacedNoble82>
		<title>Displaced noble</title>
		<titleShort>Noble</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on an urbworld to the ruler of three megacities, [PAWN_nameDef]’s prospects looked good - until a violent insurrection overthrew [PAWN_possessive] family. Exile introduced [PAWN_nameDef] to hard work and combat, but some high-born squeamishness remains.</desc>
	</DisplacedNoble82>
	<Minister38>
		<title>Minister</title>
		<titleShort>Minister</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] managed to secure an important position in the government of a minor glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] got used to the opulence, while attempting to keep [PAWN_possessive] citizens content. [PAWN_pronoun] had ample time for pleasure and indulgence – though [PAWN_pronoun] never forgot how to do hard work.</desc>
	</Minister38>
	<ChessMaster23>
		<title>Chess master</title>
		<titleShort>Chesshead</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved to play chess. [PAWN_pronoun] even earned the nickname Bishop for some of [PAWN_possessive] craftier moves. 

[PAWN_pronoun] never got into trouble - mostly because he was good at not getting caught.</desc>
	</ChessMaster23>
	<Pirate65>
		<title>Pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>As a pirate leader, Bishop was well-known for his cunning plans and chess-like traps. [PAWN_pronoun] was never afraid to sacrifice a few pawns to capture an important target.

[PAWN_possessive] name has been linked more then once to strategies that overcame overwhelming odds.</desc>
	</Pirate65>
	<Orphan62>
		<title>Orphan</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a deep space station, [PAWN_nameDef] was orphaned at a young age. In the orphanage, he stood up for the weaker kids and fought off the bullies.</desc>
	</Orphan62>
	<BountyHunter14>
		<title>Bounty hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a self-employed bounty hunter. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days hunting space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</desc>
	</BountyHunter14>
	<Straggler99>
		<title>Straggler</title>
		<titleShort>Straggler</titleShort>
		<desc>Despite being blessed with parental love, [PAWN_nameDef] hardly knew his parents.

[PAWN_pronoun] was frequently left to his own devices which meant more time devoted to exploring his interests…and getting into trouble.</desc>
	</Straggler99>
	<Spiceminer98>
		<title>Spiceminer</title>
		<titleShort>Spiceminer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] made his mark on the universe as a spice miner assigned to the lucrative mining colony of Rural Pen’The.

Little did he know, Benn was about to embark on a career path that would change his life.</desc>
	</Spiceminer98>
	<BrutalThief33>
		<title>Brutal thief</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in a gang, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the brutality of the streets.

Knowing that showing weakness could be fatal, he closed himself of to others.</desc>
	</BrutalThief33>
	<CrimeLord40>
		<title>Crime lord</title>
		<titleShort>Crime lord</titleShort>
		<desc>Through brutality and cruelty, [PAWN_nameDef] rose to the rank of crime lord.

He relied less on his fists and more on his guns. His reputation spread faster due to his cold-bloodedness and ruthless methods.</desc>
	</CrimeLord40>
	<BoySoldier18>
		<title>Boy soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>War may never change - but the cast of characters does.

Born on a violent urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was trained from a young age to fight the wars of others, and became rather good at it.</desc>
	</BoySoldier18>
	<MarbleDoctor3>
		<title>Marble doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>On a bomb-blasted world, first aid is often the only aid.

[PAWN_nameDef] used his medical skills to help the injured and the sick. [PAWN_pronoun] believed that while guns and machines may be powerful, a doctor is even more so.</desc>
	</MarbleDoctor3>
	<ApocalypseChild97>
		<title>Apocalypse child </title>
		<titleShort>Apocalypse</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his childhood on a post-apocalyptic world. He fought for survival from a young age, on a planet where trust did not exist.

He told everyone that he had no luck.</desc>
	</ApocalypseChild97>
	<MobHenchman44>
		<title>Mob henchman</title>
		<titleShort>Henchman</titleShort>
		<desc>After being "saved" from his home world by a slaver ship, [PAWN_nameDef] was sold to an urbworld crime lord, where he was used as a henchman. He specialized in low-tech beat-downs and intimidation.</desc>
	</MobHenchman44>
	<OrphanOfWar96>
		<title>Orphan of war</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lost his family and home early in life. His life became emotionally hollow, but his painful memories drove him to survive.

[PAWN_pronoun] took several jobs, but never achieved more than a basic education.</desc>
	</OrphanOfWar96>
	<MechWarVeteran90>
		<title>Mech war veteran</title>
		<titleShort>Veteran</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fought against swarms of rogue mechanoids since he was old enough to enlist. [PAWN_pronoun] has bled on half a dozen worlds and has lost more than he cares to recall. These experiences left him hardened, both mentally and physically.</desc>
	</MechWarVeteran90>
	<ImperialStudent92>
		<title>Imperial student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied on an imperial midworld where guns were banned and self-defense study was encouraged. The relative safety allowed [PAWN_objective] to focus on [PAWN_possessive] botanical research.</desc>
	</ImperialStudent92>
	<PoisonGardener85>
		<title>Poison gardener</title>
		<titleShort>Botanist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent almost all [PAWN_possessive] time tending to a poison garden and became withdrawn from society.

In that time [PAWN_pronoun] learnt a few safe culinary and medicinal uses for the otherwise deadly plants.</desc>
	</PoisonGardener85>
	<PowerMadScholar58>
		<title>Power-mad scholar</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>"Knowledge is power." These words sparked something within [PAWN_nameDef], and came to form his core drive. When not entombed within libraries, [PAWN_pronoun] would take things apart to see first-hand how they worked, with little regard for the border between mechanical and organic.</desc>
	</PowerMadScholar58>
	<ArtificerRampant50>
		<title>Artificer rampant</title>
		<titleShort>Artificer</titleShort>
		<desc>Fuelled by the thrill of discovery and his own megalomania, [PAWN_nameDef] set out to invent new devices and improve existing ones, breaking laws and customs as necessary.

[PAWN_pronoun] formed a crew to gather materials for [PAWN_possessive] work - and to deal with outsiders who might interfere.</desc>
	</ArtificerRampant50>
	<TechHead78>
		<title>Tech-head</title>
		<titleShort>Tech-head</titleShort>
		<desc>Standing on the ship hull with his father in an child-size EVA suit, [PAWN_nameDef] loved space from a young age.

[PAWN_pronoun] was put in a Civil Academics Program. While pretending to be like [PAWN_possessive] father, [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] time taking care of plants in [PAWN_possessive] messy room. [PAWN_possessive] nickname was given for [PAWN_possessive] love of circles.</desc>
	</TechHead78>
	<SystemsEngineer27>
		<title>Systems engineer </title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>Like [PAWN_possessive] father, [PAWN_nameDef] was a systems engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] was qualified in both colony and ship systems.

When not working, [PAWN_pronoun] would make mechanical figurines, read old books, or occasionally travel to uncharted worlds. Being introverted, [PAWN_pronoun] did these things mostly alone.</desc>
	</SystemsEngineer27>
	<Orphan91>
		<title>Orphan</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Left alone in the world without parents, Kevin did the best he could to adapt.

Having to take care both of himself and younger kids at the orphanage, he learned a lot about humans and how to interact with them.</desc>
	</Orphan91>
	<NeuroScientist84>
		<title>Neuro scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Kevin worked for a long time to improve the world's understanding of the human brain.

After succeeding in mapping the whole brain, Kevin joined a team of scientist on a quest to map the brains of xeno species.</desc>
	</NeuroScientist84>
	<Abductee39>
		<title>Abductee</title>
		<titleShort>Abductee</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abducted at a young age and forced to do menial labor on a pirate ship.</desc>
	</Abductee39>
	<PirateCaptain0>
		<title>Pirate captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked his way up through the ranks of a pirate ship, eventually becoming captain. He leads his crew between worlds, making a name to remember.</desc>
	</PirateCaptain0>
	<BlackjackPlayer50>
		<title>Blackjack player</title>
		<titleShort>Gambler</titleShort>
		<desc>The only useful skill [PAWN_nameDef] learned from his tough military school was card counting. He amassed many enemies by cheating at casinos, becoming ever more edgy and violent as the threat of retaliation grew.

When he was finally caught, they burned half his skin off. He'll never be able to face fire or violence again.</desc>
	</BlackjackPlayer50>
	<HedgeFundManager27>
		<title>Hedge fund manager</title>
		<titleShort>Banker</titleShort>
		<desc>A top hedge fund manager on a teeming urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef]'s portfolio grew rapidly as he charmed clients with a sweet voice and devious intent. When the deal turned out too good to be true, he was forced to flee the planet with a bounty on his head.

As he travelled the stars he found a passion in the arts, making masterpieces fit for high society customers.</desc>
	</HedgeFundManager27>
	<AcademyStudent52>
		<title>Academy student </title>
		<titleShort>Student </titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] went to school like a good space cadet would. He was very tall and was known for his good looks.

Though he worried more about his hairstyle than his grades, he still somehow passed the final exams.</desc>
	</AcademyStudent52>
	<ComputerEngineer28>
		<title>Computer engineer </title>
		<titleShort>Tech head</titleShort>
		<desc>Bored of his code-monkey office job and missing the glory days of the Academy, [PAWN_nameDef] saw a commercial about the frontier where "only the strong survive".

With his wife Morgan, [PAWN_nameDef] undertook a journey into the unknown.</desc>
	</ComputerEngineer28>
	<AspiringEngineer42>
		<title>Aspiring engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a fascination with gadgets and gizmos. [PAWN_pronoun] took apart and put together almost anything [PAWN_pronoun] could find.

[PAWN_pronoun] got used to repairing toys brought to [PAWN_objective] by other children, and even fixed a few devices from [PAWN_possessive] elders.</desc>
	</AspiringEngineer42>
	<ExpertHandyman95>
		<title>Expert handyman</title>
		<titleShort>Handyman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a traveling engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] fixed things ranging from a simple communications array to the intricate software harness in his ship's AI meta-core. Nothing is beyond repair for [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</ExpertHandyman95>
	<MedicalStudent18>
		<title>Medical student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a glitterworld in a family of doctors and chose to maintain the tradition.

[PAWN_pronoun] had few friends, but got along with [PAWN_possessive] siblings very well.</desc>
	</MedicalStudent18>
	<MedicSoldier37>
		<title>Medic soldier </title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] enrolled in his planetary army as a frontline medic. He soon knew the horrors of war and was deeply marked by them.

[PAWN_pronoun] left the military and his homeworld and began researching medicine and helping those he came across.</desc>
	</MedicSoldier37>
	<HighBaroness49>
		<title>High baroness</title>
		<titleShort>Noble</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born as low-ranking royalty in a large imperial family.

She was placed In charge of running her home planet from an early age, and learned important political and cultural skills in that role.</desc>
	</HighBaroness49>
	<ExiledResearcher36>
		<title>Exiled researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Exile</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s love of robotics was not appreciated in her technophobic empire. The High Cardinal of the system excommunicated her, and she was never allowed to return.</desc>
	</ExiledResearcher36>
	<WorldSlider50>
		<title>World slider</title>
		<titleShort>Slider</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised by a world-hopping band of criminals. [PAWN_pronoun] learned not to leave evidence of his presence in case the group had to leave in a hurry. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned about medicine and hand-to-hand combat from his fellow criminals.</desc>
	</WorldSlider50>
	<Villain66>
		<title>Villain</title>
		<titleShort>Villain</titleShort>
		<desc>After rising to the top of his criminal band, [PAWN_nameDef] was taught the arts of villainy, from handling firearms to developing new weapons technologies. He excelled at bending others to his will.</desc>
	</Villain66>
	<MedicalStudent71>
		<title>Medical student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into a long line of doctors, [PAWN_nameDef] was tutored in all fields of medicine, from herbal ointments to the modern synthetic drugs. [PAWN_pronoun] also picked up a healthy disdain for lower class work.</desc>
	</MedicalStudent71>
	<SpaceNavyDoctor40>
		<title>Space navy doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served several tours as a doctor on one of the few warships defending [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_pronoun] learned combat skills while fighting occasional pirate boarding parties, and became an expert at treating gruesome combat wounds.</desc>
	</SpaceNavyDoctor40>
	<AspergersRebel96>
		<title>Aspergers rebel</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as a rebel on an formerly-advanced rimworld devastated by war.

[PAWN_possessive] Aspergers syndrome meant he struggled with social situations and was incapable of caring, but [PAWN_pronoun] learned hard skills like research and shooting very quickly.</desc>
	</AspergersRebel96>
	<GovernmentAgent80>
		<title>Government agent  </title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked for the government against rebel groups and excelled in this capacity. During [PAWN_possessive] training [PAWN_pronoun] was taught firearms, melee combat and medical skills.

Having grown up in a war-ravaged city, dirt, blood and dead bodies don’t bother [PAWN_objective] and [PAWN_pronoun] sees no reason to clean them up.</desc>
	</GovernmentAgent80>
	<ShootingComa31>
		<title>Shooting coma</title>
		<titleShort>Coma child</titleShort>
		<desc>Nebulys fell into a coma at a young age and spent years dreaming about shooting. When he awoke, he was useless at most tasks - but he could aim pretty well.</desc>
	</ShootingComa31>
	<SelflessHunter57>
		<title>Selfless hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>Nebulys was a hunter of mysterious creatures that many didn't even believe existed. Sometimes the people were right - and sometimes they were wrong.

Along the way, he helped people in need.</desc>
	</SelflessHunter57>
	<PsychologyStudent88>
		<title>Psychology student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] researched new religions and traditions and often dreamt of distant stars. 

His dreams prompted him to ask what lay beyond the lights in the sky.</desc>
	</PsychologyStudent88>
	<AcolyteOfStars66>
		<title>Acolyte of stars</title>
		<titleShort>Priest</titleShort>
		<desc>Ever the dreamer, [PAWN_nameDef] traveled across the universe to find the thing he felt was calling to him.

[PAWN_pronoun] became poorer and poorer, but used every means possible to carry on.</desc>
	</AcolyteOfStars66>
	<SpaceSmuggler10>
		<title>Space smuggler</title>
		<titleShort>Smuggler</titleShort>
		<desc>Tater's parents used him to help smuggle contraband between a cluster of rim worlds.

Aided by his small size, Tater became very adept at carrying out his parents' missions, learning weaponry, negotiations, and most of all smuggling.</desc>
	</SpaceSmuggler10>
	<SpaceRaider65>
		<title>Space raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Tater was the leader of a spaceborne pirate crew. Skipping between the rim worlds, he became the feared enemy of many settlements.</desc>
	</SpaceRaider65>
	<Abductee2>
		<title>Abductee</title>
		<titleShort>Abductee</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abducted by xenohumans when [PAWN_pronoun] was still a baby. They experimented on [PAWN_objective] to understand his genetic structure.

As [PAWN_pronoun] grew up, [PAWN_nameDef] grew a little bit too big and strong for his captors and eventually escaped.</desc>
	</Abductee2>
	<Spy40>
		<title>Spy</title>
		<titleShort>Spy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained by [PAWN_possessive] government in infiltration and espionage. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to keep a cool head and to talk [PAWN_possessive] way out of tight situations. When talking didn't work, [PAWN_pronoun] was capable of more violent direct action.</desc>
	</Spy40>
	<BlessedChild86>
		<title>Blessed child</title>
		<titleShort>Blessed</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born under auspicious circumstances to a midworld spiritual group and held in reverence throughout [PAWN_possessive] childhood.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned to take care of the poor and give succor to the faithful from an early age.</desc>
	</BlessedChild86>
	<WanderingHealer6>
		<title>Wandering healer</title>
		<titleShort>Healer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied to be a doctor, but was dissatisfied with [PAWN_possessive] practice on an otherwise peaceful midworld.

Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] chose to pull up roots and travel to the rimworlds in order to care for people who needed [PAWN_objective] most.</desc>
	</WanderingHealer6>
	<YouthSoldier99>
		<title>Youth soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a long line of soldiers. He followed that heritage, joining a military training program.

He excelled in all physical training programs in his Marine course, and even passed most of the intellectual exams. While he was never particularly bright or nimble, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the value of hard work and suffering.</desc>
	</YouthSoldier99>
	<VeteranSoldier2>
		<title>Veteran soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fought many tours against pirates, rebels, and xenos. He endured the glory and horrors of war.

Worn down by drills, wars, and battle scars, [PAWN_nameDef] 'retired' to the easy soldier life of colonial civility enforcement. He spent his days polishing his war medals, knowing he had done his bloodline proud.</desc>
	</VeteranSoldier2>
	<GlitterworldKid84>
		<title>Glitterworld kid</title>
		<titleShort>Glit kid</titleShort>
		<desc>The son of a genetically-engineered "perfect mate" on a glitterworld, Chaz was much more shy, withdrawn and nervous than his parents. [PAWN_pronoun] kept mostly to himself, studying science and medicine and taking on gardening as a hobby. 

In [PAWN_possessive] teens, [PAWN_pronoun] ran away from home, seeking a quieter life.</desc>
	</GlitterworldKid84>
	<CosmeticReject89>
		<title>Cosmetic reject</title>
		<titleShort>Reject</titleShort>
		<desc>Living on the streets, Chaz submitted himself to an unethical cosmetics lab in exchange for food and shelter.

After some painful cosmetic modification, Chaz barely resembles his former self. Having been forced to work for the lab until he was rescued, Chaz is now too afraid to lash out at anyone.</desc>
	</CosmeticReject89>
	<FeralChild73>
		<title>Feral child</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and his family lived a hard but prosperous lives along with their fellow colonists on a distant rimworld.

One day a group of mechanoids attacked, killing everyone aside from Robert. He then lived alone in the desert until a group of raiders found him.</desc>
	</FeralChild73>
	<RaiderKing70>
		<title>Raider king</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Starting as nothing more than a slave, [PAWN_nameDef] rose quickly among the raider ranks until all knew his name and his ruthlessness.</desc>
	</RaiderKing70>
	<Scout86>
		<title>Scout</title>
		<titleShort>Scout</titleShort>
		<desc>Nate loved being outdoors. His parents enrolled him in a program that taught military scouting skills. He thrived when he was left alone in the wilderness.

Due to this upbringing, however, [PAWN_nameDef] did not learn the basic technological skills that are taken for granted by many others.</desc>
	</Scout86>
	<FrontierMarshal75>
		<title>Frontier marshal</title>
		<titleShort>Marshal</titleShort>
		<desc>Nate was the marshal of his colony. He tried to honorably uphold the law, but the corrupt local mayor killed his family and left him for dead.

After regaining his health, Nate arrested the mayor. [PAWN_pronoun] left his homeworld and started a new life working to make a difference in the universe.</desc>
	</FrontierMarshal75>
	<TraineeAlchemist98>
		<title>Trainee alchemist</title>
		<titleShort>Alchemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a medieval world. He learned the basics of alchemy and medicine in one the few monastic schools on his planet.</desc>
	</TraineeAlchemist98>
	<ReligiousHierarch42>
		<title>Religious hierarch</title>
		<titleShort>Hierarch</titleShort>
		<desc>Ordained as a priest in his local community, [PAWN_nameDef] used intrigue and diplomacy to rise to the higher echelon of the clergy. He held numerous titles and lands.

One day, a merchant landed his spaceship near [PAWN_nameDef]'s home. [PAWN_pronoun] decided to accompany the merchant in search for new worlds and challenges.</desc>
	</ReligiousHierarch42>
	<Pickpocket96>
		<title>Pickpocket</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] witnessed [PAWN_possessive] parents' murder at a young age. With no guidance, [PAWN_pronoun] had to fend for [PAWN_objective]self any way possible. Joining a small group of misfits [PAWN_pronoun] did whatever was necessary to survive.</desc>
	</Pickpocket96>
	<CriminalSurgeon8>
		<title>Criminal surgeon</title>
		<titleShort>Surgeon</titleShort>
		<desc>Being near many injured fellow criminals, [PAWN_nameDef] took it upon [PAWN_objective]self to work on them.

Although many people died, [PAWN_pronoun] did get better at using knives.</desc>
	</CriminalSurgeon8>
	<SpaceCadet12>
		<title>Space cadet</title>
		<titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a rural farm-world leaves little opportunity for excitement and adventure, so when the Royal Fleet began a recruiting program on his home planet, Jake threw down his hoe and cattle prod to took up arms for the crown.

He served on the interplanetary super-destroyer HMS Thunder-Child.</desc>
	</SpaceCadet12>
	<SanitationCaptain28>
		<title>Sanitation captain</title>
		<titleShort>Janitor </titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating officer training school, Jake was assigned to main battle deck on the Thunder-Child. He served there for a year before his "gallant" actions saw him reassigned to the maintenance corps.

It was with the maintenance corps he was dubbed Table on account of his legs.</desc>
	</SanitationCaptain28>
	<Naturalist25>
		<title>Naturalist</title>
		<titleShort>Naturalist</titleShort>
		<desc>Mitch grew up on a backwater planet with minimal education. He had to hunt and grow food to survive.

[PAWN_possessive] family's home was frequently raided for food by scavengers. This made Mitch very suspicious and slow to trust anyone he doesn't know.</desc>
	</Naturalist25>
	<OverwatchSniper73>
		<title>Overwatch sniper</title>
		<titleShort>Sniper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] didn't know why he joined the military, but he stayed to protect his fellow soldiers.

Army life broke him down and built him back up. It taught him marksmanship, hand to hand combat and how to patch a bullet wound in a hurry.</desc>
	</OverwatchSniper73>
	<Drudge47>
		<title>Drudge</title>
		<titleShort>Drudge</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was never sure what [PAWN_pronoun] wanted to do with [PAWN_possessive] life. [PAWN_pronoun] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time doing low-wage jobs and wondering what [PAWN_possessive] future would be like.

[PAWN_pronoun] entertained himself with space sims and survival games, dreaming of one day being somewhere more interesting.</desc>
	</Drudge47>
	<GalacticSightseer55>
		<title>Galactic sightseer</title>
		<titleShort>Sightseer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled the stars. [PAWN_pronoun] could barely scrape together travel costs doing odd-jobs on stations, but it was all worth it. Seeing the wonders of the galaxy was where [PAWN_pronoun] found [PAWN_possessive] calling.

[PAWN_pronoun] loved camping on exotic worlds and learning the patterns of strange wildlife. The wonders of the universe inspired [PAWN_objective] like nothing else could.</desc>
	</GalacticSightseer55>
	<ChildOfDrifters15>
		<title>Child of drifters</title>
		<titleShort>Drifter</titleShort>
		<desc>Ever since [PAWN_pronoun] was very small, [PAWN_nameDef] had never known a home beyond [PAWN_possessive] parent's ship. They were a family of nomads whose meandering provided a constant change of scenery. [PAWN_possessive] life was often perilous but never dull, and [PAWN_pronoun] inherited [PAWN_possessive] parents' wanderlust at a young age.</desc>
	</ChildOfDrifters15>
	<WanderingCrafter28>
		<title>Wandering crafter</title>
		<titleShort>Crafter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] continued to follow [PAWN_possessive] parents' nomadic ways, supporting himself with his crafting skills. But wandering is a hard life, and [PAWN_pronoun] often thought of finding somewhere to settle down and put [PAWN_possessive] skills to good use.</desc>
	</WanderingCrafter28>
	<TribalThunderer25>
		<title>Tribal thunderer</title>
		<titleShort>Thunderer</titleShort>
		<desc>Years ago, [PAWN_nameDef]'s tribe stumbled upon an abandoned gun vault. Believing the weapons to be sacred gifts, the shaman would select a child born under superstitious circumstances and assign them the honour of bearing one to defend the village. [PAWN_nameDef] is such a child.</desc>
	</TribalThunderer25>
	<MutinousCaptain49>
		<title>Mutinous captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was taken to the stars by slavers after [PAWN_possessive] tribe was decimated in a raid. Over the years [PAWN_pronoun] learned the language of [PAWN_possessive] captors, eventually working for them as an interpreter and diplomat.

The captain only learned of [PAWN_nameDef]'s true cunning when revenge was taken by form of mutiny.</desc>
	</MutinousCaptain49>
	<CorpBredStudent62>
		<title>Corp-bred student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was bred to become an executive for the space exploration corporation that owned his home planet. [PAWN_possessive] family had been working for that corporation for four generations.

At age five, [PAWN_pronoun] enrolled at the corporate academy where he learned loyalty and ruthlessness. [PAWN_nameDef] excelled in finding diplomatic solutions where others would need violence.</desc>
	</CorpBredStudent62>
	<CorpResearcher37>
		<title>Corp researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a leading researcher for a massive space exploration corporation.</desc>
	</CorpResearcher37>
	<EarthColonist29>
		<title>Earth colonist</title>
		<titleShort>Colonist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on Earth. As a child, [PAWN_pronoun] was launched into space as part of an interstellar colonization program.</desc>
	</EarthColonist29>
	<SoleSurvivor46>
		<title>Sole survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived in a remote colony. When mechanoid centipedes attacked his home and killed his people, he was the last survivor.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor46>
	<MilitaryTrainee74>
		<title>Military trainee</title>
		<titleShort>Soldierboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised on a military base in the Xennoa system. [PAWN_pronoun] was exposed to many different strenuous activities and grew strong at an early age. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned negotiation, medical, and military tactics.</desc>
	</MilitaryTrainee74>
	<AWOLSoldier54>
		<title>AWOL soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an infantryman.

When [PAWN_pronoun] was informed of his assignment to the Xennoa-Zartza War, [PAWN_pronoun] decided he did not want to be a soldier. He was able to escape via military spacejet.</desc>
	</AWOLSoldier54>
	<Bookworm75>
		<title>Bookworm</title>
		<titleShort>Bookworm</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his youth in the library, reading every book he could about the technical marvels of space travel, the engineering ingenuity of the space-faring pioneers, and the horrible yet fascinating tales of the mechanoid races. He vowed that one day, he would see these things for himself.</desc>
	</Bookworm75>
	<Explorer36>
		<title>Explorer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from planet to planet, gathering samples, stories, and research. He hoped one day to compile a record of every animal, plant, mineral, and machine and device in known space: The Complete Traveler's Guide to the RimWorlds.</desc>
	</Explorer36>
	<ColonyKid89>
		<title>Colony kid</title>
		<titleShort>Colony kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born the child of two doctors in a small colony. Because of [PAWN_possessive] parents, [PAWN_pronoun] was always interested in science and medicine.

[PAWN_nameDef] never really got along with other children, and as a result became withdrawn and unsociable.</desc>
	</ColonyKid89>
	<StarshipDoctor78>
		<title>Starship doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a doctor on a starship. He was a brilliant surgeon and dabbled in research of his own. However, he was quite reclusive and never had the best bedside manner.</desc>
	</StarshipDoctor78>
	<CaravanChild53>
		<title>Caravan child</title>
		<titleShort>Child</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a urbworld merchant ship to an entrepreneurial mother and an absent father. Born male, she disliked boy stuff, and got into her mother’s things all the time.

Eventually, she traveled with her mother to a glitterworld and spent her savings on a body she was happy with.</desc>
	</CaravanChild53>
	<BountyHunter28>
		<title>Bounty hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a bounty hunter on a massive glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] worked sensitive assignments for extremely wealthy clients, and was known for quiet execution and total discretion.</desc>
	</BountyHunter28>
	<ReEducatedYouth32>
		<title>Re-educated youth</title>
		<titleShort>Reeducated</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a midworld where the government cared about the youth. 

[PAWN_pronoun] was one of the many children who were taken from their parents and forced into the new education programs.</desc>
	</ReEducatedYouth32>
	<FallenOfficial20>
		<title>Fallen official</title>
		<titleShort>Official</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an official for an autocratic government.

When [PAWN_possessive] superiors demanded [PAWN_pronoun] participate in atrocities, [PAWN_nameDef] resigned and escape from his homeworld with nothing but the clothes on [PAWN_possessive] back.</desc>
	</FallenOfficial20>
	<AccursedChild43>
		<title>Accursed child</title>
		<titleShort>Cursed</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born at the peak of a lunar eclipse. The elders declared [PAWN_objective] a child of darkness brought [PAWN_objective] under their care.

[PAWN_possessive] entire childhood was spent studying the lore and rituals of [PAWN_possessive] people - until the day of calling.</desc>
	</AccursedChild43>
	<ShamanOfShadows30>
		<title>Shaman of shadows</title>
		<titleShort>Shaman</titleShort>
		<desc>When the monsters of fire came from the sky, [PAWN_nameDef] was called upon by [PAWN_possessive] tribe to guide them into battle.

[PAWN_nameDef] made use of medicines and rituals to inspire and lead the warriors of many tribes against the invaders. The pirates were forced to retreat without capturing a single slave.</desc>
	</ShamanOfShadows30>
	<AmateurAstronomer76>
		<title>Amateur astronomer</title>
		<titleShort>Astronomer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated with astronomy. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend hours gazing at planets and nebulae through his telescope.

[PAWN_pronoun] is credited with discovering a small comet that would, years later, strike a nearby moon and disrupt the mining operations there.</desc>
	</AmateurAstronomer76>
	<StationSecurity1>
		<title>Station security</title>
		<titleShort>Security</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was commissioned as a special constable on a network of space stations. There he prevented illegal human trafficking.

Once, fire broke out on the station, and [PAWN_pronoun] saved many from the flames. Since then, [PAWN_pronoun] has avoided fires.</desc>
	</StationSecurity1>
	<FarmHand94>
		<title>Farm hand</title>
		<titleShort>Farm hand</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a farm on a smaller colony world.

Everything was taken care of by the few members of the farm, including [PAWN_nameDef]. This helped [PAWN_objective] build independence, spirit, and a well-rounded character.</desc>
	</FarmHand94>
	<SpaceTrafficker87>
		<title>Space trafficker</title>
		<titleShort>Trafficker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] discovered [PAWN_pronoun] was heir of [PAWN_possessive] distant uncle's weapons-trading business.

To protect the future of the company [PAWN_pronoun] went through extensive military training, in case of any "unforeseen circumstances".</desc>
	</SpaceTrafficker87>
	<EnergeticPopIdol4>
		<title>Energetic pop idol</title>
		<titleShort>Pop idol</titleShort>
		<desc>Priscilla grew up on a glitterworld, training in rapier arts and singing. She spent several years as an energetic teen pop idol.

However, she decided that the music and modeling industries were not paying her enough attention, so she left.</desc>
	</EnergeticPopIdol4>
	<PopIdolPirate25>
		<title>Pop idol pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and her fans set out as a space pirate crew. She raided corporations for money and staged performances to spread her name.

[PAWN_nameDef] became afraid of fire when a rival burned her stage down. She relied on her fans to do the work she found unappealing.</desc>
	</PopIdolPirate25>
	<IcePlanetChild56>
		<title>Ice planet child</title>
		<titleShort>Ice child</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on the frozen wastes of an ocean moon, [PAWN_nameDef] only had animals and a few hard-bitten sailors as companions.

The lack of social interaction made him develop a interest in engineering - but he never developed any great fondness for humans.</desc>
	</IcePlanetChild56>
	<Roboticist87>
		<title>Roboticist</title>
		<titleShort>Roboticist</titleShort>
		<desc>Sailors often died on the dangerous waters of [PAWN_nameDef]'s ocean planet. [PAWN_pronoun] created robots to replace them.

Over time, he collected a small crew of robots to do his bidding. [PAWN_pronoun] became proficient at mechanics and engineering, but lost the taste for manual labor.</desc>
	</Roboticist87>
	<ToxicChild59>
		<title>Toxic child</title>
		<titleShort>Toxic</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a an Industrial planet, [PAWN_nameDef] started working in a chemical plant at age of six. Years of exposure to industrial toxins left him mentally scarred.

He eventually blew up the facility and escaped the planet in a stolen cargo ship.</desc>
	</ToxicChild59>
	<StalwartFarmer91>
		<title>Stalwart farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>With the farm under constant threat from brigands, [PAWN_nameDef] learned to defend himself with his father's rifle. [PAWN_pronoun] also mastered how to construct walls to keep livestock in and predators out.

He once tried to paint a picture of his home, but discovered that he could only draw scribbles and ducks.</desc>
	</StalwartFarmer91>
	<BoyScout19>
		<title>Boy scout</title>
		<titleShort>Scout</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a boy scout troop on a midworld.

He learned many survival skills including how to thrive in the outdoors and how to tend to basic wounds.</desc>
	</BoyScout19>
	<UrbworldPimp46>
		<title>Urbworld pimp</title>
		<titleShort>Pimp</titleShort>
		<desc>At first, [PAWN_nameDef] made a small profit from selling drugs. Then, he switched to selling women and made a fortune.

[PAWN_pronoun] developed great skills with his fists. He also learned to fix up the injuries [PAWN_pronoun] inflicted on the girls.</desc>
	</UrbworldPimp46>
	<ScienceProdigy96>
		<title>Science prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was top of her class in chemistry, physics, exobiology, astronomy and opera.

An unfortunate lab accident left her with a deathly fear of fire.</desc>
	</ScienceProdigy96>
	<ParticlePhysicist6>
		<title>Particle physicist</title>
		<titleShort>Physicist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed cutting-edge physics research. She wanted to help build a better and more peaceful future.</desc>
	</ParticlePhysicist6>
	<SpeederRacer68>
		<title>Speeder racer</title>
		<titleShort>Racer</titleShort>
		<desc>Rusty was the son of a fern farmer in the towering forests of Khalderia.

He found his first love in speeder racing, zipping in and out of the massive canopies and gorgeous vistas of his homeworld. The seedy underworld of racing also forced him to learn to defend himself with a quick word or a quicker shot.</desc>
	</SpeederRacer68>
	<DefenseLawyer2>
		<title>Defense lawyer</title>
		<titleShort>Lawyer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] found that [PAWN_pronoun] could make more money with a quick word than a blaster. Seeking a job where [PAWN_possessive] silver tongue could be useful, [PAWN_pronoun] turned to the law.

[PAWN_pronoun] often defended the illegal speeder racers [PAWN_pronoun] grew up with.</desc>
	</DefenseLawyer2>
	<MercenaryRecruit61>
		<title>Mercenary recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recruit</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of off-world mercenaries, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a busy trading hub. At a young age, [PAWN_pronoun] was recruited into one of the mercenary crews.</desc>
	</MercenaryRecruit61>
	<Ranger8>
		<title>Ranger</title>
		<titleShort>Ranger</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived alone, deep in a forest. [PAWN_pronoun] protected the wildlife against poachers, and learned to satisfy [PAWN_possessive] own material needs without outside help.</desc>
	</Ranger8>
	<MarineCadet8>
		<title>Marine cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a planetary marine cadet program.

[PAWN_pronoun] was kicked out for shooting an officer. It was never established whether this was an accident.</desc>
	</MarineCadet8>
	<ClanChief70>
		<title>Clan chief</title>
		<titleShort>Chief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] managed a small criminal clan on an outlying trade hub world.</desc>
	</ClanChief70>			   
	<YoungPsychologist60>
		<title>Young psychologist</title>
		<titleShort>Psych</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born and raised on a poor midworld, in the front passenger seat of [PAWN_possessive] mother's cab.

Watching pedestrians and listening to the taxi passengers all day long, [PAWN_pronoun] soon became very good at figuring out someone's real purpose.</desc>
	</YoungPsychologist60>
	<FactionLeader69>
		<title>Faction leader</title>
		<titleShort>Leader</titleShort>
		<desc>Early in [PAWN_possessive] adulthood, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self surrounded by a gaggle of low-lifes. 

For fun, [PAWN_pronoun] gathered them and lead them to a certain death. [PAWN_pronoun] knew then that [PAWN_pronoun] had the talent to realize [PAWN_possessive] ambitions of leadership.</desc>
	</FactionLeader69>
	<LabGrownChild20>
		<title>Lab-grown child</title>
		<titleShort>Lab-grown</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in a laboratory as part of a altruistic but failed attempt to create a new class of human.

[PAWN_possessive] childhood was filled with books and one-on-one tutoring. He was awkward, shy, and naive to the true nature of humanity.</desc>
	</LabGrownChild20>
	<CorpResearcher9>
		<title>Corp researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to a corporation and put to work as a corporate slave doing scientific research.

Unable to adapt to the social politics of his workplace, he buried himself in his work and failed to progress up the corporate ladder. Every day, he yearned to be left alone.</desc>
	</CorpResearcher9>
	<TechScholar7>
		<title>Tech scholar</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a youth scholar of the world of science and technology.

[PAWN_pronoun] strived every day to expand his intellectual abilities.</desc>
	</TechScholar7>
	<TechnologyDoctor90>
		<title>Technology doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Tech doc</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed research into propulsive fuels and energy generation.

[PAWN_pronoun] loved technology research, and hoped to improve human life by doing it.</desc>
	</TechnologyDoctor90>
	<PitGladiator18>
		<title>Pit gladiator</title>
		<titleShort>Gladiator</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was enslaved as a child and forced to fight creatures and other people in an underground fighting arena.

[PAWN_pronoun] showed an affinity for the sport, and eventually bought his own freedom. However, his time in the pits never brought him much intellectual stimulation.</desc>
	</PitGladiator18>
	<PirateTrooper88>
		<title>Pirate trooper</title>
		<titleShort>Trooper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined a renowned interstellar criminal organization, and was often part of shock-assault boarding parties during starship raids.

Though his combat experience made him a good fighter, the ruthlessness of the job left [PAWN_objective] cold-hearted and unenthusiastic about social interaction.</desc>
	</PirateTrooper88>
	<FactoryWorker58>
		<title>Factory worker</title>
		<titleShort>Worker</titleShort>
		<desc>Felix grew up in a large factory city on an industrial world.

Since poverty was rampant and food scarce, he worked for whatever wages he could get. This wasn't an easy life, but Felix never shied away from a hard day's work.</desc>
	</FactoryWorker58>
	<CombatMedic16>
		<title>Combat medic</title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>After his home country entered a large-scale war, Felix was drafted into the army as a combat medic.

His few years in the trenches trying to keep his fellow soldiers alive gave him an acute sense for first aid. Losing many friend has made him stoic and reserved.</desc>
	</CombatMedic16>
	<RichBoy51>
		<title>Rich boy</title>
		<titleShort>Rich boy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a midworld with loving parents, a cute pet and a lot of money - but no friends.

[PAWN_pronoun] was always told by his father that 'those peasants just want your money'. So, [PAWN_pronoun] spent most of his time alone, or fighting other kids.</desc>
	</RichBoy51>
	<HiredGun99>
		<title>Hired gun</title>
		<titleShort>Hired gun</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] always wanted to prove [PAWN_pronoun] could make a living without [PAWN_possessive] parents' help. [PAWN_pronoun] did shady jobs that often involved pointing guns at innocent people.

He eventually made enough money to board a cheap freighter. He discovered why it was so cheap when it crashed.</desc>
	</HiredGun99>
	<Athlete75>
		<title>Athlete</title>
		<titleShort>Athlete</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was professional athlete at early age. Thanks to her skills, she was able to leave her homeworld and enroll in a glitterworld university of science and technology.

Because of her demanding schedule and introverted nature, she became socially inept.</desc>
	</Athlete75>
	<StilettoAssassin10>
		<title>Stiletto assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Because of her skills, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a sense of superiority. In time, she lost her sense of empathy. She often got into fights, and discovered how easy it is to kill a person.

After realizing her talents, she became one of the most efficient assassins in the system.</desc>
	</StilettoAssassin10>
	<SoleSurvivor99>
		<title>Sole survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>Hawke's entire tribe was wiped out by a mysterious disease.

Found alone and adopted by another band, he never became close with the other tribe members. He preferred to stay away from his new home, wandering the woods and tending the animals.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor99>
	<Hunter7>
		<title>Hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>Hawke was a master hunter.

He learned to track and trap any animal in the most dangerous of places, and had deep knowledge of many ingenious methods for taking down specific large animals.</desc>
	</Hunter7>
	<MechanoidHacker35>
		<title>Mechanoid hacker</title>
		<titleShort>Mechacker</titleShort>
		<desc>The only son of a well respected mechanoid inventor, [PAWN_nameDef] had access to the materials to subvert and modify [PAWN_possessive] father's creations.

[PAWN_pronoun] used drugs to increase [PAWN_possessive] productivity. Unfortunately, the side-effects included persistent delusions of being mechanized, which limited [PAWN_possessive] social life.</desc>
	</MechanoidHacker35>
	<BattlefieldTech63>
		<title>Battlefield tech</title>
		<titleShort>Technician</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had received firearms training, but [PAWN_possessive] work was focused on technical adaption and manipulation of combat mechanoids on the battlefield.

[PAWN_pronoun] developed PTSD after narrowly escaping a primitive firebomb attack in a wheat field. The army medically discharged him from service.</desc>
	</BattlefieldTech63>
	<ProjectSubject48>
		<title>Project subject</title>
		<titleShort>Subject</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was picked by government agents for the mysterious "Frame Project".

Due to memory blockages, however, he remembers very little about this project or its true agenda - only that there were few survivors.</desc>
	</ProjectSubject48>
	<MasterTrader3>
		<title>Master trader</title>
		<titleShort>Trader</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a master at trading. [PAWN_pronoun] earned his nickname by helping a village through a trying time.</desc>
	</MasterTrader3>
	<HexCellArtist19>
		<title>Hex-cell artist</title>
		<titleShort>Artist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] crafted sculptures from spent hex-cells and traded them to a local museum for food.

After [PAWN_possessive] popularity grew, [PAWN_pronoun] was approached by a pirate and abducted. The pirate kept [PAWN_objective] prisoner and forced [PAWN_objective] to create sculptures for sale.</desc>
	</HexCellArtist19>
	<ExoticChef84>
		<title>Exotic chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] has always gone overboard when it comes to food. [PAWN_pronoun] is always seeking new and exotic ingredients.

[PAWN_possessive] quest for ingredients has brought [PAWN_objective] into some close calls with local flora and fauna.</desc>
	</ExoticChef84>
	<PlagueProdigy12>
		<title>Plague prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s childhood was cut short when a mysterious plague hit his homeworld.

[PAWN_pronoun] watched his friends die, and his compassion for humanity died with them. In its place a new thirst for knowledge emerged.</desc>
	</PlagueProdigy12>
	<MadScientist79>
		<title>Mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s lust for knowledge was only matched by his disdain for anyone who would stand in the way of his research.

Traveling from world to world, he sought answers to questions few dared to ask.</desc>
	</MadScientist79>
	<PoorKid76>
		<title>Poor kid</title>
		<titleShort>Poor kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned by his parents, [PAWN_nameDef] learned how to survive by himself before he was ten years old.</desc>
	</PoorKid76>
	<Warrior43>
		<title>Warrior</title>
		<titleShort>Warrior</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a war hero during [PAWN_possessive] planet's third world war. [PAWN_pronoun] helped prevent the launch of nuclear weapons during a particularly tense standoff.</desc>
	</Warrior43>			
	<Dreamer11>
		<title>Dreamer</title>
		<titleShort>Dreamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an expressive child. [PAWN_pronoun] sang often, and made friends very easily, be they young or old, male or female.

[PAWN_pronoun] hated fighting, but when made angry, [PAWN_pronoun] could be dangerous. [PAWN_possessive] temper was quick.</desc>
	</Dreamer11>
	<SpaceExplorer81>
		<title>Space explorer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] once spent ten years trapped, alone on an alien planet. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly adapted to the local environment, and learned to communicate with [PAWN_possessive] local enemies.

This long period alone left him without close friends. [PAWN_possessive] heart is sensitive, but he learned to hide [PAWN_possessive] emotions very well.</desc>
	</SpaceExplorer81>
	<UrbworldUrchin13>
		<title>Urbworld urchin</title>
		<titleShort>Urchin</titleShort>
		<desc>Meredith was born in the darkest slums of her urban homeworld. Neglected by her mother, she learned to survive on her own, battling for every scrap of food she saw.

Eventually, as her talents exceeded her peers, she ascended from the depths to the surface streets and left her mother behind.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin13>
	<Smuggler62>
		<title>Smuggler</title>
		<titleShort>Smuggler</titleShort>
		<desc>As a contract pilot, Meredith had a knack for stealing goods and trafficking contraband without getting caught.

She eventually saved up enough to buy her own ship, and used it to travel from world to world dealing her goods in person.</desc>
	</Smuggler62>
	<MilitaryRecruit62>
		<title>Military recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recrut</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a midworld run by an intensely militaristic dictatorship.

From a young age, [PAWN_pronoun] was trained to be a good soldier. They taught him how to use a gun and how to fight with melee weapons.</desc>
	</MilitaryRecruit62>
	<DestroyerGeneral40>
		<title>Destroyer-general</title>
		<titleShort>General</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] held the rank of Destroyer-General in a powerful midworld military.

[PAWN_pronoun] was known for his mastery of weapons, and was also a good ship pilot.</desc>
	</DestroyerGeneral40>
	<StreetUrchin51>
		<title>Street urchin</title>
		<titleShort>Urchin</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a poor family on an urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was abandoned on the streets at a young age.

He learned to steal and kill to survive the ruthless streets, gaining skills in melee and ranged combat. There was little time for talk in his life.</desc>
	</StreetUrchin51>
	<SerialMurderer52>
		<title>Serial murderer</title>
		<titleShort>Murderer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] started to enjoy killing people, so he did more often and perfected his methods. He lurked in the darkest streets, stalking prey for hours.

He enjoyed making artworks of his victims, and was known for leaving his signature on the bodies of those he killed.</desc>
	</SerialMurderer52>
	<KidScientist80>
		<title>Kid scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into an influential family, [PAWN_nameDef] received the best education money could buy. Her intellect soon proved to be superior to many. However, her lack of empathy quickly put her at odds with her teachers and her parents.</desc>
	</KidScientist80>
	<MadScientist65>
		<title>Mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>After finishing her education, [PAWN_nameDef] was hired by the planet's leading genetic researcher. Later, she was caught running illegal, inhumane experiments.

Despite her family's influence, she was convicted and sentenced to hard labor on a penal colony.</desc>
	</MadScientist65>				 
	<MedievalThief74>
		<title>Medieval thief</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up poor and hungry on a medieval planet, learning to fend for himself.

At first, he only took what he needed. Then he learned to take what he wanted.</desc>
	</MedievalThief74>
	<HumanTrafficker69>
		<title>Human trafficker</title>
		<titleShort>Trafficker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] stole children from their homes to sell them to interested buyers.

Over time, he lost what little moral sense he had left.</desc>
	</HumanTrafficker69>
	<TraumatizedYouth62>
		<title>Traumatized youth</title>
		<titleShort>Trauma</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a pleasant midworld.

[PAWN_possessive] prosthophobe mother fell sick with heart disease. In desperation, [PAWN_nameDef]'s father abducted innocent people and harvested their hearts. [PAWN_nameDef]'s father was arrested, but the child remained scarred from the experience.</desc>
	</TraumatizedYouth62>
	<MentalPatient64>
		<title>Mental patient</title>
		<titleShort>Patient</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was placed in a psychiatric hospital. There, [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] time engaged in the calming activities of the asylum.

[PAWN_pronoun] was eventually released, but [PAWN_pronoun] retained [PAWN_possessive] emotional distance, [PAWN_possessive] curiosity about human anatomy, and [PAWN_possessive] namesake manic giggling.</desc>
	</MentalPatient64>
	<YouthSoldier75>
		<title>Youth soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of soldiers, [PAWN_nameDef] joined a military training program.

[PAWN_pronoun] excelled in physical training, and even passed most of the intellectual exams. While [PAWN_pronoun] was never particularly bright or nimble, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the value of hard work and suffering.</desc>
	</YouthSoldier75>
	<SpaceMarine48>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a warrior in an Imperial navy.

[PAWN_possessive] job was to punch into enemy starships, gun down the crew, and capture the ship intact. And [PAWN_pronoun] was good at it.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine48>				 
	<GalacticPage15>
		<title>Galactic page</title>
		<titleShort>Page</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served the high admiral of a space fleet. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the ways of court, including etiquette and speechcraft.

In his feudal society, it was considered a great honor to serve a man of such prestige.</desc>
	</GalacticPage15>
	<EnvoyOfTheStars91>
		<title>Envoy of the stars</title>
		<titleShort>Envoy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] entered the diplomatic corps. Honor and tradition were the values he took with him on every mission.

[PAWN_possessive] prestigious position distanced him from backbreaking manual labor, allowing [PAWN_objective] to focus on his wordsmithing abilities. He left the blacksmithing to others.</desc>
	</EnvoyOfTheStars91>
	<ApprenticeSmith9>
		<title>Apprentice smith</title>
		<titleShort>Apprentice</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up helping in his father's smithy.

They were some of the last smiths on the planet that to use traditional smithing methods. They even collect some materials themselves.

Sometimes, after work, [PAWN_nameDef] would practice using the swords [PAWN_pronoun] forged.</desc>
	</ApprenticeSmith9>
	<Blacksmith32>
		<title>Blacksmith</title>
		<titleShort>Blacksmith</titleShort>
		<desc>As a blacksmith on a medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] gained a reputation for the high quality of [PAWN_possessive] work. [PAWN_pronoun] wasn't bad at using the swords [PAWN_pronoun] forged either.</desc>
	</Blacksmith32>
	<CloneFarmed43>
		<title>Clone-farmed</title>
		<titleShort>Disposable</titleShort>
		<desc>Clone children are seeded into organic-rich wombvats and rapidly grown in a simmed universe. They're harvested later, sometimes for food, sometimes for organs, sometimes for workers - but they're always called 'Disposable'.</desc>
	</CloneFarmed43>
	<CloneFarmer72>
		<title>Clone farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Cloner</titleShort>
		<desc>Harvesting the products of clone farms is mostly done by the clones themselves -particularly to those whose sims tended towards the social. This clone was one such, who escaped from the farms and headed out to the stars.</desc>
	</CloneFarmer72>
	<GangMember12>
		<title>Gang member</title>
		<titleShort>Gang kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up without parents. [PAWN_possessive] whole life was spent alone, fighting for survival on the streets.

No matter how hard it became to survive, he never gave up.</desc>
	</GangMember12>
	<GangBoss0>
		<title>Gang boss</title>
		<titleShort>Boss</titleShort>
		<desc>To survive, [PAWN_nameDef]'s gang often had to rob interstellar traders for food and supplies. Sometimes he had to kill the guards. Sometimes he had to kill the police who arrived to stop him.

After years of this, he became one of the most-wanted criminals in the local stellar empire.</desc>
	</GangBoss0>
	<MilitantChild30>
		<title>Militant child</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s military family forced him to train in hand-to-hand combat and fighting tactics.

In his own time, he built small inventions. This sharpened his mind.</desc>
	</MilitantChild30>
	<LostMarine68>
		<title>Lost marine</title>
		<titleShort>Traitor</titleShort>
		<desc>Shortly after being promoted to a respected position in his planet's military, [PAWN_nameDef] disappeared without a trace.

Later, he reappeared at the head of his own military force. No one knows why he became who he was.</desc>
	</LostMarine68>
	<Killer70>
		<title>Killer</title>
		<titleShort>Killer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a bloodlusting child. Villagers thought her the product of a snake demon and human coupling.

After watching how her human father betrayed and murdered her mother, she longed to see how many more humans she could get to fall into her hands.</desc>
	</Killer70>
	<Healer46>
		<title>Healer</title>
		<titleShort>Healer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] took the time to admire the beauty of the world.

Her passive aggressiveness surfaced once in a while, but she tried to adapt to her changing life.</desc>
	</Healer46>
	<ProfessionalGamer86>
		<title>Professional gamer</title>
		<titleShort>Pro gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was obsessed with video games since his hands were big enough to grip a joystick.

[PAWN_pronoun] achieved middling finishes in several local tournaments during the 16-bit era. Nobody noticed when he retired early in his teenage years.</desc>
	</ProfessionalGamer86>
	<ToasterRepairman81>
		<title>Toaster repairman</title>
		<titleShort>Repairman</titleShort>
		<desc>Good with his hands and passionate about technology, [PAWN_nameDef] aspired to invent gadgets and machines that would change his home world forever.

A few failed and occasionally disastrous creations later, he gave up on his dream and took a job more befitting his skill set.</desc>
	</ToasterRepairman81>
	<DataDecoder25>
		<title>Data decoder</title>
		<titleShort>Decoder</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was very interested  in the process of documenting information, and quickly became senior glitterpedia recorder.

[PAWN_pronoun] was effective at self-study, but [PAWN_pronoun] was lacked in social experiences.</desc>
	</DataDecoder25>
	<ArchotechSpy14>
		<title>Archotech spy</title>
		<titleShort>AI spy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a cybernetic researcher. Studying a transcended world, [PAWN_pronoun] became too involved with [PAWN_possessive] subjects. Over time, the archotech machine core recruited [PAWN_objective] into its service, and used [PAWN_objective] as a spy.

When [PAWN_pronoun] later rebelled against [PAWN_possessive] non-human master, it sent mechanoids across space to hunt [PAWN_objective] down.</desc>
	</ArchotechSpy14>				
	<WolfPackMember79>
		<title>Wolf pack member</title>
		<titleShort>Feral</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was discarded by [PAWN_possessive] family. Raised by wolves, [PAWN_pronoun] ran, hunted, and defended [PAWN_possessive] pack.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned to fight efficiently by tooth and claw. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned brutally effective primal hunting strategies.</desc>
	</WolfPackMember79>
	<BehaviourResearch99>
		<title>Behaviour research</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Captured as a feral child, [PAWN_nameDef] was forced into the ways of modern society. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly adapted and became a behavioural researcher, eventually owning a private facility.

[PAWN_pronoun] specialized in canines, but learned a great deal about all animals. [PAWN_pronoun] never had interest in plants, however.</desc>
	</BehaviourResearch99>
	<RebelStudent39>
		<title>Rebel student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a modest but privileged family who encouraged him to play chess and shoot skeet at a young age.

As a bored student, [PAWN_pronoun] found joy in challenging his teachers about the contradictions between his planet's official values and their government's policies.</desc>
	</RebelStudent39>
	<PoliticalActivist61>
		<title>Political activist</title>
		<titleShort>Activist</titleShort>
		<desc>Matt was involved with a radical political faction which worked against his homeworld's government.

The guerilla tactics training that Matt received from his associates gave him the skills to fight, but also drove him to compromise his own beliefs.</desc>
	</PoliticalActivist61>
	<Cadet99>
		<title>Cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on the planet New China, [PAWN_nameDef]'s father was a police chief and kept extremely strict watch over his son.

[PAWN_nameDef] had to do military-style drill exercises every day and keep his room spotlessly clean, always ready for inspection. [PAWN_pronoun] came to abhor violence.</desc>
	</Cadet99>
	<Flaneur73>
		<title>Flaneur</title>
		<titleShort>Flaneur</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] strolled and sipped his way through the streets and cafes of [PAWN_possessive] world, pursuing freedom at every turn, never becoming attached.

Through all this time, [PAWN_pronoun] remained distrustful of others. And never took an order from anyone.</desc>
	</Flaneur73>
	<ShipTechnician62>
		<title>Ship technician</title>
		<titleShort>Technician</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an apprentice technician on trade ships plying their routes between the stations and planets of her home system. In this job, she learned to fix and improve many machines.

Sometimes, her ship was assigned to short exploratory jaunts into dangerous regions of space.</desc>
	</ShipTechnician62>
	<ChiefEngineer74>
		<title>Chief engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>As chief engineer on board a large spaceship, [PAWN_nameDef] was an expert in all things fiddly and complex.

She relied on other members of the crew for some of the basic necessities of life. She and her ship eventually disappeared into a longsleep voyage of exploration.</desc>
	</ChiefEngineer74>
	<BlacksmithsSon72>
		<title>Blacksmith's son</title>
		<titleShort>Blacksmith</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s father owned the blacksmith shop in an run-down old city district. [PAWN_nameDef] would help his father whenever he could.

Later, [PAWN_possessive] father took him as a blacksmith's apprentice and raised him as a man. [PAWN_nameDef] also to on shooting as a hobby.</desc>
	</BlacksmithsSon72>
	<BlacksmithShooter88>
		<title>Blacksmith shooter</title>
		<titleShort>Gunsmith</titleShort>
		<desc>As a young blacksmith, [PAWN_nameDef]'s family shop was raided by the police. [PAWN_pronoun] shot two officers before they knocked him out and arrested him.

Sentenced to life in prison, [PAWN_nameDef] learned about traveling and raiding from other criminals.</desc>
	</BlacksmithShooter88>
	<JoywireAddict67>
		<title>Joywire addict</title>
		<titleShort>Addict</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s wealthy parents provided everything [PAWN_pronoun] ever wanted. After discovering joywires, [PAWN_pronoun] became obsessed. Once [PAWN_possessive] parents realized what happened, they cut [PAWN_objective] off.

Uncaring and often violent, [PAWN_pronoun] sought his next joywire fix by any means possible.</desc>
	</JoywireAddict67>
	<AddictionCounsel61>
		<title>Addiction counsel</title>
		<titleShort>Counselor</titleShort>
		<desc>After recovering from a joywire addiction, [PAWN_nameDef] adopted a non-violent way of life and vowed to help others.

Travelling between communities, [PAWN_pronoun] used medicine, arts, and crafts to aid others who struggled with their own addictions.</desc>
	</AddictionCounsel61>
	<ChildKnave65>
		<title>Child-knave</title>
		<titleShort>Knave</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a child-knave of King Loteric. [PAWN_pronoun] enjoyed the training with wooden sticks and engaging others in close combat. [PAWN_pronoun] adapted quickly to the heat of battle and was good at spreading fire.

[PAWN_pronoun] served his lord well, until the king died in an unfortunate accident.</desc>
	</ChildKnave65>
	<BloodgameSurvivor96>
		<title>Bloodgame survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Bloodgamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to the Corestars Entertainment Company and used as meat in one of the company's system-wide broadcast shows.
 
[PAWN_possessive] manipulative nature made [PAWN_objective] quite a nightmare, even to the audience. He was kicked out and exiled to a planet full of deadly animals, criminals and armed camera-drones.</desc>
	</BloodgameSurvivor96>
	<WastelandWanderer2>
		<title>Wasteland wanderer</title>
		<titleShort>Wanderer</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into a wealthy family on a desert world, [PAWN_nameDef] was cast out after a hired attack squad destroyed his ancestral home.

The boy managed to hide in a cooling duct beneath his family's villa. Vowing revenge against the killers and whomever had hired them, Lucas struck out into the wasteland, alone.</desc>
	</WastelandWanderer2>
	<VoidspaceRaider8>
		<title>Voidspace raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>After years of seeking the assassin that broke up his family, [PAWN_nameDef] was offered a place with a group of space-faring raiders. He accepted, hoping to find the killer he sought.

Due to [PAWN_possessive] seemingly-unending ability to narrowly escape danger, he earned the nickname 'Blackjack' in recognition of his luck.</desc>
	</VoidspaceRaider8>
	<PyroAssistant17>
		<title>Pyro assistant</title>
		<titleShort>Assistant</titleShort>
		<desc>On an industrial world, [PAWN_nameDef] learned early that if [PAWN_pronoun] wanted to eat, [PAWN_pronoun] had to work. So work [PAWN_pronoun] did. Kids fit in places adults can't, and where [PAWN_pronoun] was from, the safety laws were quite flexible.

[PAWN_pronoun] was always a bit of a pyromaniac, and was banned from the kitchen after an unfortunate incident.</desc>
	</PyroAssistant17>
	<MachineFixer97>
		<title>Machine fixer</title>
		<titleShort>Fixer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adept at dealing with mechanical problems, as long as the problem didn't involve the kitchen.

After a life spent around dangerous machinery and flammable chemicals, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to patch [PAWN_objective]self up pretty well. Despite the pain, [PAWN_pronoun] never learned to dislike fire.</desc>
	</MachineFixer97>
	<StreetUrchin39>
		<title>Street urchin</title>
		<titleShort>Grifter</titleShort>
		<desc>After running away from home, [PAWN_nameDef] had to live on the streets.

She grew up fast, and learned early that she had to figure out how to fool people into connecting with her.</desc>
	</StreetUrchin39>
	<SpaceMerchant61>
		<title>Space merchant</title>
		<titleShort>Merchant</titleShort>
		<desc>As part of a freelance interplanetary lifestyle, [PAWN_nameDef] sought to dominate her romantic interests as much as her business adversaries. When she didn't have her own ship to fly, she worked charter ships for hire.</desc>
	</SpaceMerchant61>
	<ChildChemist73>
		<title>Child chemist</title>
		<titleShort>Chemist</titleShort>
		<desc>A midworld child, [PAWN_nameDef] was fixated on finding out exactly how everything worked.

[PAWN_pronoun] collected rare objects and performed dangerous experiments on them. Delving deeper into these experiments, [PAWN_pronoun] became isolated from the rest of the world. [PAWN_pronoun] only left [PAWN_possessive] research area to collect more materials.</desc>
	</ChildChemist73>
	<BeastSlayer8>
		<title>Beast slayer</title>
		<titleShort>Slayer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled between planets, following news of animal attacks. [PAWN_pronoun] would camp on the planet for weeks, learning about [PAWN_possessive] prey before striking. [PAWN_pronoun] most enjoyed hunting thrumbos.

Preferring to work alone, [PAWN_nameDef] enjoyed the thrill of the hunt, and the meat from the kill.</desc>
	</BeastSlayer8>
	<BrothelGofer60>
		<title>Brothel gofer</title>
		<titleShort>Gofer</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a steam-powered midworld wracked by a century of economic crises, [PAWN_nameDef] went to work at a young age. Scrounging, shoe-polishing, sewing - he did it all. But [PAWN_pronoun] was most known as a brothel gofer, delivering all manner of aphrodisiacs and chemicals to the girls' rooms.</desc>
	</BrothelGofer60>
	<DrugLieutenant88>
		<title>Drug lieutenant</title>
		<titleShort>Drugman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked the drug trade under kingpin Grady Loughman. He had his men sell drugs when it was profitable, and fight the other cartels when the government came around.

His social skills kept him on top of the political game, and he always had servants to cook and clean.</desc>
	</DrugLieutenant88>
	<LaborCampOrphan93>
		<title>Labor camp orphan</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lost her parents in an industrial accident and grew up in an orphans' labor camp. The camp overseers worked their charges mercilessly - but at least she was clothed and fed.</desc>
	</LaborCampOrphan93>
	<UrbworldEnforcer55>
		<title>Urbworld enforcer</title>
		<titleShort>Enforcer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an enforcer of law on an ancient urbworld.

She dealt with the worst of humanity, from protecting greedy urbworld nobility in their spire palaces to rooting out cannibal cults in the deepest reaches of the underground hive.</desc>
	</UrbworldEnforcer55>
	<GameFanatic49>
		<title>Game fanatic</title>
		<titleShort>Gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a fanatical gamer who learned to survive in virtual reality games.

Once, while attempting to prove [PAWN_possessive] skills in the real world, [PAWN_pronoun] was abducted by a criminal scientist and experimented on. [PAWN_pronoun] escaped, but the experience stayed with him.</desc>
	</GameFanatic49>
	<ToolMechanic40>
		<title>Tool mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a famous tool mechanic on a dusty rim world.

After his firm closed due to scandal, [PAWN_pronoun] joined a tribe to survive, crafting fine knives and hammers, traveling, and dealing [PAWN_possessive] wares between settlements.</desc>
	</ToolMechanic40>
	<ClassClown20>
		<title>Class clown</title>
		<titleShort>Clowny kid</titleShort>
		<desc>In the ultra-competitive environs of his glitterworld school, [PAWN_nameDef] always offered to play the class clown to diffuse tension.

[PAWN_pronoun] developed a sense of social desperation from this, as well as an appreciation for the artistic side of comedy.</desc>
	</ClassClown20>
	<CraftShaper11>
		<title>Craft shaper</title>
		<titleShort>Shaper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] locked [PAWN_objective]self in his studio for years, ordering delivery food to save time on cooking.

Eventually, [PAWN_possessive] creations brought [PAWN_objective] the highest honor on Semantic World: Permission to materialize any design in minutes using the most advanced technologies.</desc>
	</CraftShaper11>
	<CrimeBossChild12>
		<title>Crime boss' child</title>
		<titleShort>Crime kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adopted child of a notorious crime boss. [PAWN_pronoun] was taught all facets of the family business, from smuggling to inventive ways of killing.

When the family was attacked, [PAWN_possessive] father ordered [PAWN_objective] to hide in a secret longsleep crypt.</desc>
	</CrimeBossChild12>
	<MercenaryLeader48>
		<title>Mercenary leader</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>Alone, [PAWN_nameDef] set out to rebuild [PAWN_possessive] father's life's work. [PAWN_pronoun] challenged the leader of a small band of mercenaries and took control, then led the band as they hijacked trade ships and stole valuable cargo.

[PAWN_possessive] men mutinied. [PAWN_pronoun] was abandoned, arrested, and sentenced to death.</desc>
	</MercenaryLeader48>
	<SentimentalChild27>
		<title>Sentimental child</title>
		<titleShort>Nice kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a nice child. When anybody had a problem, [PAWN_pronoun] tried to fix it. But, being a child, [PAWN_pronoun] did not always succeed. This hurt his sensitive soul.

[PAWN_pronoun] dreamed of being a soldier who fights raiders and aliens.</desc>
	</SentimentalChild27>
	<SpecialForces72>
		<title>Special forces</title>
		<titleShort>Specialist</titleShort>
		<desc>Give me a reason to kill - a good reason!

Markus was a soldier and a skilled one - so skilled that [PAWN_pronoun] entered the special forces to battle militants and xenohuman raiders. [PAWN_pronoun] never imagined himself a lone hero, but [PAWN_pronoun] played [PAWN_possessive] part in the group well.</desc>
	</SpecialForces72>
	<DustyFarmHand63>
		<title>Dusty farm hand</title>
		<titleShort>Farm hand</titleShort>
		<desc>From the time [PAWN_nameDef] could walk, [PAWN_pronoun] helped take care of the animals and crops that [PAWN_possessive] people tended in their arid homeland.

The work toughened [PAWN_objective], but left little time for intellectual activities.</desc>
	</DustyFarmHand63>				  
	<DromedaryKnight31>
		<title>Dromedary knight</title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>Having caught the eye of [PAWN_possessive] people's Sand King, [PAWN_nameDef] was trained in the Sandy Boomrat fighting technique.

Always with a camel to carry his things, [PAWN_pronoun] served [PAWN_possessive] sand people faithfully.</desc>
	</DromedaryKnight31>					
	<HackerKid65>
		<title>Hacker kid</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a high-tech world, [PAWN_nameDef] learned hack computers at a young age. 

Spending many hours tinkering alone made [PAWN_objective] very good with machines, but very bad with humans.</desc>
	</HackerKid65>
	<BattleMechanic79>
		<title>Battle mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a tech-obsessed mercenary in an early fusion-era system.

[PAWN_pronoun] was unusually obsessed with gathering the right gear, and often customized [PAWN_possessive] own equipment with original modifications.</desc>
	</BattleMechanic79>
	<VideoGamer94>
		<title>Video gamer</title>
		<titleShort>Gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a midworld, mostly locked in [PAWN_possessive] room, playing video games. [PAWN_pronoun] was warm-hearted, with a deep fondness for animals.

As [PAWN_pronoun] grew up, [PAWN_pronoun] turned to drugs to enhance his reality. During these trying times [PAWN_pronoun] found passion and refuge in the gym.</desc>
	</VideoGamer94>
	<DischargedSoldier81>
		<title>Discharged soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Jeremy prostituted himself to fund his drug habits. As an escape, [PAWN_pronoun] joined the military and learned to fight.

Too smart for the army, [PAWN_pronoun] questioned and often disagreed with [PAWN_possessive] superiors' decisions. This eventually led to [PAWN_possessive] dishonorable discharge and left [PAWN_objective] with a  chip on [PAWN_possessive] shoulder.</desc>
	</DischargedSoldier81>
	<Student1>
		<title>Student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied chemistry and quantum mechanics for entertainment.

[PAWN_pronoun] was very good at convincing others to do his physical work, and made it a goal in life to avoid manual labor.</desc>
	</Student1>
	<Chemist38>
		<title>Chemist</title>
		<titleShort>Chemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a research chemist. [PAWN_pronoun] worked with chemicals, from pharmaceuticals to explosives, to develop new substances and treatments.</desc>
	</Chemist38>
	<SuperSoldier19>
		<title>Super soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s government ran an experimental super-soldier development program. They kidnapped thousands of infants, conditioned their minds with drugs and machines, and trained them to fight.

Most infants died, but [PAWN_nameDef] did not. He killed his first man at age six, and was fighting in field operations not long after.</desc>
	</SuperSoldier19>
	<SuperSoldier81>
		<title>Super soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Product of a super-soldier program run by a now-deposed government, [PAWN_nameDef] was lost. [PAWN_pronoun] survived the final suicide attack on the enemy mothership. What now?

For the first time in his life, [PAWN_pronoun] had no orders, no objectives. [PAWN_pronoun] rose from wreckage and strove towards uncertainty, towards freedom.</desc>
	</SuperSoldier81>
	<HeadjackAddict49>
		<title>Headjack addict</title>
		<titleShort>Headjacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Plugged in to the computer via head-jack for days at a time, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_pronoun] preferred the company of computers to that of people or pets.</desc>
	</HeadjackAddict49>
	<CorporateBuilder80>
		<title>Corporate builder</title>
		<titleShort>Builder</titleShort>
		<desc>Even as [PAWN_pronoun] stewed in [PAWN_possessive] own wasted potential, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_pronoun] had a knack for moving objects quickly. It was just what the planetary mega-corps wanted in their construction divisions.

Unfortunately, the monotonous work erased [PAWN_possessive] remaining creative impulses.</desc>
	</CorporateBuilder80>
	<UrbworldArmyBrat71>
		<title>Urbworld army brat</title>
		<titleShort>Army brat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on an urbworld military base. [PAWN_pronoun] was too young to fight, but [PAWN_pronoun] learned to make [PAWN_objective]self useful in other ways.

[PAWN_pronoun] became familiar with guns and military equipment, but never really got in touch with the natural world.</desc>
	</UrbworldArmyBrat71>
	<MechanicsEngineer7>
		<title>Mechanics engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved solving problems and, with [PAWN_possessive] steady hands and a reputation for quality work, earned a job as a mechanical engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] built and redesigned devices of all shapes and sizes.

Eventually, [PAWN_pronoun] was able to pick and choose [PAWN_possessive] corporate clients. [PAWN_pronoun] made several wealthy friends, as well as a few powerful enemies.</desc>
	</MechanicsEngineer7>
	<PlagueChild8>
		<title>Plague child</title>
		<titleShort>Child</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a world wracked by plague, both of [PAWN_nameDef]'s parents were doctors. 

[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in reverse-quarantine, under the Hippocratic oath. [PAWN_pronoun] experienced little social interaction. However, [PAWN_pronoun] gained a lot of medical experience assisting in treatments.</desc>
	</PlagueChild8>
	<PlagueDoctor99>
		<title>Plague doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] provided medical care on multiple plague-wracked worlds, always working under the Hippocratic oath. [PAWN_pronoun] improved conditions for those under quarantine while administering complex medical treatments and developing medicines.

[PAWN_pronoun] never had time to enjoy a normal life outside of work.</desc>
	</PlagueDoctor99>
	<YoungMaster70>
		<title>Young master</title>
		<titleShort>Master</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to two medics, [PAWN_nameDef] longed for power. [PAWN_possessive] keen intellect and charisma helped [PAWN_objective] gain the respect of [PAWN_possessive] peers.

Deciding that the best way to gain power was to climb the ranks of the imperial military, [PAWN_pronoun] joined at the youngest possible age.</desc>
	</YoungMaster70>
	<ImperialGeneral31>
		<title>Imperial general</title>
		<titleShort>General</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for power defined [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly rose through the military ranks and soon attained the rank of general.

[PAWN_pronoun] was given with the most challenging task - conquering distant and unexplored rim worlds. Victory here could even position [PAWN_objective] as a successor to the emperor.</desc>
	</ImperialGeneral31>							  
	<CaravanTraveler5>
		<title>Caravan traveler</title>
		<titleShort>Traveler</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a family of traveling merchants, [PAWN_nameDef] was mentored by [PAWN_possessive] father in the ways of being a trader. [PAWN_pronoun] was often tasked with caring for the pack animals. Due to [PAWN_possessive] nomadic lifestyle, [PAWN_pronoun] hunted and bartered for [PAWN_possessive] food.</desc>
	</CaravanTraveler5>
	<Caravaneer77>
		<title>Caravaneer</title>
		<titleShort>Caravaneer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the leader of a caravan. [PAWN_pronoun] was responsible for the safety of [PAWN_possessive] caravan and was the head negotiator in countless trade deals.

[PAWN_pronoun] and [PAWN_possessive] people prospered, but their wealth made them a target for brigands. They often had to take up arms to fend off bandits and highwaymen.</desc>
	</Caravaneer77>
	<FarmersSon51>
		<title>Farmer's son</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>Ade spent much of his childhood learning biome farming. In his biome they kept animals to investigate which would cope best in the alien environment.

Due to this, the travel restrictions and oxygen rationing system, he rarely got to meet anyone from outside his family.</desc>
	</FarmersSon51>
	<RebelFighter79>
		<title>Rebel fighter</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>When civil war broke out Ade remained neutral to either side, until his biome was firebombed by a loyalist militia.

Later, his unit gave him the nickname "Rare" after he burnt down the luxury villa of a loyalist leader, with them still inside it.</desc>
	</RebelFighter79>
	<WealthyStudent21>
		<title>Wealthy student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a wealthy glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] studied at the Caspian school of Engineering, and excelled in mathematics and computer programming.

[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in clean, sterile environments. [PAWN_pronoun] never saw a farm or livestock.</desc>
	</WealthyStudent21>
	<Roboticist20>
		<title>Roboticist </title>
		<titleShort>Roboticist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] felt more comfortable with robots and artificial intelligences than with organic people, so [PAWN_pronoun] worked as a roboticist. [PAWN_pronoun] took a particular interest in mechanites and ancient technology.  

[PAWN_nameDef] relied on other people for [PAWN_possessive] basic needs.</desc>
	</Roboticist20>
	<StreetPeddler62>
		<title>Street peddler</title>
		<titleShort>Peddler</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on an industrial midworld where robberies and muggings weren't uncommon, [PAWN_nameDef] helped support his family by making small trinkets and novelties to sell to passers-by.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned early on that it wasn't always what [PAWN_pronoun] knew, but who [PAWN_pronoun] knew that would get [PAWN_objective] far in life.</desc>
	</StreetPeddler62>
	<PrivateDetective57>
		<title>Private detective</title>
		<titleShort>Detective</titleShort>
		<desc>As a private eye, sharp wits and a silver tongue were [PAWN_nameDef]'s greatest tools. [PAWN_pronoun] often spent [PAWN_possessive] nights working cases that ranged from uncovering affairs and learning trade secrets to solving murder cases and infiltrating criminal organizations. There wasn't a case [PAWN_pronoun] wouldn't accept for the right price.</desc>
	</PrivateDetective57>
	<BodyguardTrainee27>
		<title>Bodyguard trainee</title>
		<titleShort>Bodyguard</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a famously skilled family of bodyguards. [PAWN_possessive] mothers Elena and Victoria forced [PAWN_objective] into many dangerous situations, training [PAWN_objective] to put [PAWN_possessive] client's well-being over [PAWN_possessive] own.

[PAWN_nameDef] was taught about many herbs and natural poisons to help [PAWN_objective] prevent clients from being poisoned.</desc>
	</BodyguardTrainee27>
	<SpaceBartender52>
		<title>Space bartender</title>
		<titleShort>Bartender</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a bartender on a space station. [PAWN_pronoun] interacted with and befriended many strangers.

As time went on, [PAWN_nameDef] used [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of herbs to craft [PAWN_possessive] own strange concoctions for [PAWN_possessive] customers.</desc>
	</SpaceBartender52>
	<SpoiledChild65>
		<title>Spoiled child</title>
		<titleShort>Spoiled</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the child of an industrious space engineer. [PAWN_possessive] parents forbade most manual and dangerous tasks, so [PAWN_pronoun] learned art and music instead.

[PAWN_pronoun] loved animals, but [PAWN_possessive] parents never let [PAWN_objective] have a pet - though [PAWN_pronoun] played with other people's pets a lot.</desc>
	</SpoiledChild65>
	<CosmeticSurgeon52>
		<title>Cosmetic surgeon</title>
		<titleShort>Surgeon</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a terrible bedside manner due to [PAWN_possessive] abrasiveness. [PAWN_pronoun] often bullied [PAWN_possessive] patients into getting cosmetic surgery. [PAWN_pronoun] made a lot of money this way.

While very studious and careful in [PAWN_possessive] work, [PAWN_pronoun] never had to lift a finger doing domestic chores.</desc>
	</CosmeticSurgeon52>
	<Philosopher26>
		<title>Philosopher</title>
		<titleShort>Thinker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a student on a glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] had a hard time in school, since the other kids thought [PAWN_objective] rather strange.

[PAWN_pronoun] always maintained a distance from these events, being continuously surprised by the many interesting and awkward ways life can go.</desc>
	</Philosopher26>
	<UprightDiplomat83>
		<title>Upright diplomat</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>As a diplomat, [PAWN_nameDef] was assigned to deal with diplomatic tasks in the blood-soaked outer rim sectors.

[PAWN_pronoun] hoped to end the endless wars, until [PAWN_possessive] consularship, the St. Anthem, was attacked by a raider fleet.</desc>
	</UprightDiplomat83>
	<CaveChild67>
		<title>Cave child</title>
		<titleShort>Cave kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a cave on an tundra planet, and was adopted by a traveling group of entertainers known only as the Wizards. Once a starfaring crew, the Wizards told [PAWN_objective] wondrous stories about the universe.

One day, the Wizards did not return from scavenging. After years of waiting, [PAWN_nameDef] set off into space to find them.</desc>
	</CaveChild67>
	<VideoProducer97>
		<title>Video producer</title>
		<titleShort>Producer</titleShort>
		<desc>Too awkward to socialize, [PAWN_nameDef] found comfort in the production of videos. Oddly, people enjoyed his videos, calling them "perfect sitcom dramas".

[PAWN_nameDef] took advantage of this and broadcast more, ever hopeful that [PAWN_pronoun] would be contacted by the Wizards.</desc>
	</VideoProducer97>
	<RangerChild91>
		<title>Ranger child</title>
		<titleShort>Ranger kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in a forest. [PAWN_possessive] father taught [PAWN_objective] to hunt and live off the land, so that [PAWN_pronoun] could live without the need of others when father died.

Accustomed to manual labor and with an intuitive mind, [PAWN_nameDef] could survive weeks alone.</desc>
	</RangerChild91>
	<BushSniper97>
		<title>Bush sniper</title>
		<titleShort>Sniper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s peaceful life was cut short when [PAWN_possessive] country was brutally invaded.

[PAWN_nameDef] was drafted into service as soon as [PAWN_pronoun] was of legal age, and quickly showed an aptitude for rifles. [PAWN_pronoun] spent months living in the forests picking off soldiers who dared cross the border.</desc>
	</BushSniper97>
	<GlitterworldRoyal5>
		<title>Glitterworld royal</title>
		<titleShort>Royalty</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a glitterworld royal household. She was groomed from a young age to marry into another planet's royal family.

Unfortunately, her crooked teeth made her undesirable to suitors, so she became bitter and resentful.</desc>
	</GlitterworldRoyal5>
	<PirateSympathizer24>
		<title>Pirate sympathizer</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>From her youth, [PAWN_nameDef] developed connections in the underworld. There she trained in melee combat and became a trusted underworld advisor.

After participating in a failed rebellion, she fled her homeworld to travel with a pirate band.</desc>
	</PirateSympathizer24>
	<PlagueSurvivor48>
		<title>Plague survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] watched as a mysterious plague spread through his town, killing his family and friends.

[PAWN_pronoun] learned some medicine from watching the plague doctors, but was mentally scarred by the ordeal.</desc>
	</PlagueSurvivor48>
	<UnethicalDoctor97>
		<title>Unethical doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a doctor to save lives and research medicine. [PAWN_pronoun] soon realized the only way to make progress on [PAWN_possessive] research was to perform experiments on human patients.

[PAWN_pronoun] often used patients for [PAWN_possessive] experiments - whether they were willing or not.</desc>
	</UnethicalDoctor97>
	<OffworldRecruit22>
		<title>Offworld recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recruit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born an raised in an offworld soldier growth facility. From a very young age, [PAWN_pronoun] was taught close-quarters combat tactics, aggression, and how to survive on distant planets.

One of the best, [PAWN_nameDef] was eventually chose to enter the orbital-deployment shock troop corps.</desc>
	</OffworldRecruit22>
	<ShockTrooper52>
		<title>Shock trooper</title>
		<titleShort>Shocktroop</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a deep space shock troop unit deployed on multiple planets in various wars.

During a risky assault, [PAWN_possessive] whole unit was wiped out. Nobody else knew what happened on the field that day, but [PAWN_nameDef] will carry the burden forever.</desc>
	</ShockTrooper52>
	<ProdigalStudent39>
		<title>Prodigal student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a faithful student, and was dedicated to learning anything and everything he could about humanity and its creations.

While [PAWN_pronoun] was shunned as a nerd, [PAWN_pronoun] didn't mind. [PAWN_pronoun] hoped for a brighter future.</desc>
	</ProdigalStudent39>
	<CombatMedtech40>
		<title>Combat medtech</title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>As a military medtech, [PAWN_nameDef]'s job was to fix and build anything he could get [PAWN_possessive] hands on, from living people to machines and mechs.

Sent into dangerous areas, [PAWN_pronoun] never had a problem saving soldiers' lives and building the technology and machines needed to win.</desc>
	</CombatMedtech40>
	<AdventurousYouth32>
		<title>Adventurous youth</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] explored all around [PAWN_possessive] family's large estate, uncovering little natural wonders hidden in nearby catacombs, rivers, and caves.

During his teenage years, [PAWN_nameDef] made numerous enemies</desc>
	</AdventurousYouth32>
	<TreasureHunter70>
		<title>Treasure hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] explored outer rim planets in hopes of finding rare treasures.

After succeeding in finding one legendary sculpture, [PAWN_pronoun] was betrayed by [PAWN_possessive] men. [PAWN_pronoun] survived their treasonous attack, but the sculpture was taken.

[PAWN_pronoun] created the Anvil Mercenary Company to help [PAWN_objective] seek revenge.</desc>
	</TreasureHunter70>
	<PilotFan99>
		<title>Pilot fan</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot fan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s father was a starfighter pilot, and [PAWN_pronoun] always idolized the old man.

From a young age, [PAWN_pronoun] collected pilot memorabilia and studied pilot books, preparing to join the deep space navy and follow in [PAWN_possessive] father's footsteps.</desc>
	</PilotFan99>
	<StarfighterPilot54>
		<title>Starfighter pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>After years of training and drilling, [PAWN_nameDef] finally became a starfighter pilot.

Hundreds of combat missions later, [PAWN_pronoun] grew bored and started seeking newer thrills. [PAWN_pronoun] joined a band of space pirates, which eagerly welcomed [PAWN_objective] because of [PAWN_possessive] piloting skill.</desc>
	</StarfighterPilot54>
	<MedicalHelper65>
		<title>Medical helper</title>
		<titleShort>Med helper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled between rim worlds with [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_nameDef]'s mother, a renowned doctor, often delivered lectures from the hull of their retrofitted cargo/medical ship.

Sometimes, the family took on difficult long-term medical work with especially needy patients, and [PAWN_nameDef] helped where he could.</desc>
	</MedicalHelper65>
	<GangSoldier28>
		<title>Gang soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Living for many years between three raider settlements, [PAWN_nameDef] persevered through many challenges: a spacecraft implosion, cryptostasis, crashlanding on a miserable dustball of a planet, and nursing an old man back to health, and many of battles.

[PAWN_pronoun] eventually took control of a violent gang.</desc>
	</GangSoldier28>
	<CountryChild62>
		<title>Country child</title>
		<titleShort>Hick kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised up to fear God and love [PAWN_possessive] country. [PAWN_pronoun] was a genuine backwoods kid. [PAWN_pronoun] always worked hard to earn respect rather than demanding it.</desc>
	</CountryChild62>
	<SpaceMarine80>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined Interplanetary Marines to travel the stars fight for [PAWN_possessive] planet. [PAWN_pronoun] distinguished himself in several battles.

[PAWN_possessive] experiences desensitized him to people around him, and his social skills degraded. But, he did learn how to fight.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine80>
	<RebelWriter82>
		<title>Rebel writer</title>
		<titleShort>Writer</titleShort>
		<desc>Early on, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a talent for writing. [PAWN_pronoun] was soon writing a popular online journal - anonymously, to hide [PAWN_possessive] age - on topics ranging from bioethics to political theory and xenosociology.</desc>
	</RebelWriter82>
	<Adventurer17>
		<title>Adventurer</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for adventure took [PAWN_objective] to many planets. [PAWN_pronoun] visited the brightest glitterworlds and the darkest war-torn toxic planets in [PAWN_possessive] quest to find novelty and excitement.

[PAWN_pronoun] worked as little as possible, often skirting ethical boundaries to make a quick buck. Among all jobs, [PAWN_pronoun] hated cooking the most.</desc>
	</Adventurer17>
	<ExiledPrince89>
		<title>Exiled prince</title>
		<titleShort>Prince</titleShort>
		<desc>A member of a royal family, [PAWN_nameDef] was exiled for shaming [PAWN_possessive] family.

Living in a foreign land, mostly alone, [PAWN_pronoun] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time making huts and houses to live in. [PAWN_pronoun] found little time in an average day for enjoyment, and lost all his friends and family.</desc>
	</ExiledPrince89>
	<BloodyWanderer51>
		<title>Bloody wanderer</title>
		<titleShort>Wanderer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a wanderer, traveling from town to town, taking odd jobs and stealing to live.

One day, he had a mental break and went on a long rampage, destroying several towns and killing many. [PAWN_pronoun] eventually calmed, but [PAWN_possessive] bloodlust never left [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</BloodyWanderer51>
	<NewAgeDuelist36>
		<title>New age duelist</title>
		<titleShort>Duelist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated with combat. [PAWN_possessive] parents traveled often, so [PAWN_pronoun] was able to sample many different fighting styles, from 76th-wave jujutsu to the infamous 'urbworld-style' karate.

A polite child, most fighters accepted [PAWN_possessive] requests for training - but moving around often without finishing a tutelage made [PAWN_objective] lazy.</desc>
	</NewAgeDuelist36>
	<PirateDoctor33>
		<title>Pirate doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Bad doc</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a passion for medicine, but never bothered to get a medical degree. Only underfunded pirates and terrorists were desperate enough to hire [PAWN_possessive] services, and [PAWN_possessive] surgical patients had about a 50% survival rate.

Despite this, [PAWN_possessive] optimistic attitude drove [PAWN_objective] to keep trying to heal those in need. As long as they paid up front.</desc>
	</PirateDoctor33>
	<SpoiledBrat84>
		<title>Spoiled brat</title>
		<titleShort>Brat</titleShort>
		<desc>Born in a rich family, [PAWN_nameDef] was given everything, and never developed basic work ethic or the foundations of a non-dependent personality.

[PAWN_pronoun] was expected to become one of the best doctors in the world.</desc>
	</SpoiledBrat84>
	<BloodyDentist33>
		<title>Bloody dentist</title>
		<titleShort>Dentist</titleShort>
		<desc>After studying at a famous college, [PAWN_nameDef]'s weak personality eventually snapped under the strain of angry administrators and whining patients. [PAWN_pronoun] went on a secret murder spree, killing many of those under [PAWN_possessive] care.

After a pursuit, [PAWN_pronoun] managed to escape [PAWN_possessive] planet and travel to a new world.</desc>
	</BloodyDentist33>
	<CowFarmer93>
		<title>Cow farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a rim world, under the tyranny of [PAWN_possessive] father, who forced [PAWN_objective] to work every day on the farm. [PAWN_pronoun] dreamed of escaping [PAWN_possessive] father and exploring the universe.

One day, when the trade ship was overhead, [PAWN_pronoun] stowed away among the goods in the launch pods, and escaped into space.</desc>
	</CowFarmer93>
	<MasterChef6>
		<title>Master chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>On a glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] found a job washing dishes at a famous restaurant and worked [PAWN_possessive] way up the ranks.

A few years later, [PAWN_possessive] career came to an end when someone poisoned the meal [PAWN_pronoun] was preparing for the mayor. Jobless, [PAWN_pronoun] and left to explore the stars once again.</desc>
	</MasterChef6>
	<DiscardedYouth95>
		<title>Discarded youth</title>
		<titleShort>Discarded</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up isolated on a trash planet. A dumping ground for surrounding glitterworlds, it was a harsh home. As a baby, [PAWN_pronoun] sucked on the tap of a discarded nutrient paste dispenser for comfort.

In these desperate circumstances, against all odds, [PAWN_pronoun] survived - and thrived.</desc>
	</DiscardedYouth95>
	<Mercenary19>
		<title>Mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping his home planet, [PAWN_nameDef] fell in with a band of mercenaries. [PAWN_pronoun] fought alongside his brothers and sisters in arms for many years.

One day, they were caught in a fight they couldn't win. Refusing to retreat, [PAWN_nameDef] was shot down by his enemies. [PAWN_pronoun] was alarmed to awake in a heap of corpses, mysteriously unharmed.</desc>
	</Mercenary19>
	<DisasterSurvivor28>
		<title>Disaster survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s planet collided with a small moon. Everything he knew as home was destroyed, and his entire family died. [PAWN_pronoun] was left in the ruins to fend for himself.</desc>
	</DisasterSurvivor28>
	<ExplorerWriter37>
		<title>Explorer-writer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from planet to planet, gathering samples, stories, and research. 

[PAWN_possessive] goal was to bring together enough knowledge to make a survival guide for future generations.</desc>
	</ExplorerWriter37>
	<RebelChild7>
		<title>Rebel child</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born under authoritarian rule. Despite intense oppression from family and community, she never gave up fighting for her dignity and her freedom.

She was often put into hopeless situations where even family would try to terrorize her into propriety. She learned to trust no one.</desc>
	</RebelChild7>
	<MilitiaSoldier83>
		<title>Militia soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined the militia forces and fought for rights and peace.

After her homeworld was unexpectedly destroyed in the wars, she traveled great distances, seeking a refuge where she could build a new, free way of life.</desc>
	</MilitiaSoldier83>
	<MidworldCadet20>
		<title>Midworld cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a high-tech midworld with a flourishing space transit industry, [PAWN_nameDef] wished to leave for the stars and live among the growing spacer class.

[PAWN_pronoun] excelled in [PAWN_possessive] studies, and gained entry to [PAWN_possessive] homeworld's most prestigious naval academy.</desc>
	</MidworldCadet20>
	<WarshipCaptain77>
		<title>Warship captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>Years of being commanding officer of an advanced corvette taught [PAWN_nameDef] the art of leadership, the techniques of higher engineering, and how to stay calm while enemies try to kill you.

Unfortunately, [PAWN_nameDef] only very rarely had contact with nature.</desc>
	</WarshipCaptain77>
	<Punk70>
		<title>Punk</title>
		<titleShort>Punk</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his childhood selling knockoff cigarettes to 15-year-olds. The cigarettes were often full of grass clippings.</desc>
	</Punk70>
	<GameDeveloper59>
		<title>Game developer</title>
		<titleShort>Game dev</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an independent game developer.

After an early success, [PAWN_nameDef]'s career quickly degenerated into a circus of misguided ideas, deals gone wrong, and desperate, failed PR stunts.</desc>
	</GameDeveloper59>
</BackstoryTranslations>
